hard
This is also on screen and can be spoken about.
Is this thing on?
You are watching this.
Okay, it’s good.
You have been chosen.
I decided it was trustworthy.
I’ve decided you’re worthy
of being confided in.
I’m leaving this record of my
will behind for the next generation.
That's why now.
This record must be kept.
That is why I have to
create this record now.
If something should
happen to me, I—
This Foundation is a sub-structure of humanity,
Medicine, government studies, high school studies, etc.
As you all know, this foundation
was created to support various fields,
What's your mood?
Yes, that's the impression.
All with the goal of contributing
to the welfare of humanity.
That’s how it looks on the outside.
All the things that steal Shiv from the world,
Right, that’s the cover.
There is a secret to why I established
this foundation here in the USA,
The Stone Mask.
The mood is,
The Foundation's purpose in death,
That is to do the secret of the stone screen.
And today, I am recording this.
A story awaits behind the mask,
And there it was,
The true purpose of the foundation
is to solve the secret of the Stone Mask.
This is so that they can follow the lead.
That’s why I’m here today, to leave
behind a record of the tale of that mask.
And also to tell you the story
of the golden spirit I once knew.
Dear Osamu,
Blessed man,
The power of life,
(Chief! Chief! Chief!)
Appearance.
Blood be life, life be power
(Power!)
We are sunlight and sweat
The power in this hand
Widespread
(We, Aztecs, have drawn the sun’s wrath!)
This story awaits in the Stone Mask
The two are the boy's favorite fateful adventure
The mystery of this disappearance
lies in the Stone Mask.
1868 Years Old Ronto's son
Watcher!
It's Ikeame
I won't leave again
With that, let’s pick up the narrative
on the outskirts of London in 1868.
I'll finish you up, Ikeri
Today is
I'm sleepy
I don't understand the sun
Who is it?
Isn't it the birther who is the self?
Your voice is sweeter
than birdsong, Debbie!
It's coming
The first person will go
wait a minute
Okay tease
hang on
Hurry, hurry
Wooooooooooooo!
That carriage has gone and wrecked itself!
No one’s swarmed it yet! Alright!
First come, first served! Let’s go!
What are you talking about?
It's a rich man, it's a fast one, so I'm going to look for him.
I said wait!
It's a beautiful necklace. Thank you.
Look at that fancy carriage,
they gotta be nobles!
This bloke must’ve died instantly.
This box’ll have somethin’ good...
The valuables are gone, Yuriya and I are scared
It's a hole in the hand of a certain person's house. It's a hole in the hand of a certain person's house.
Look, find it
Just one night
No thanks
Brother, do you believe me? What were you doing?
Nice teeth!
Passion
Oge
Did you buy it?
Let’s take some of those upper teeth.
What about Red?
Morning
I helped
Is this also a dream?
Race saved my life
My name is
Used
So this too is fate...
Naroruhodoromonchya, no offense, but Brand!
Ah, Dario, beat Brando!
Time passed, and in 1880
The time was filled with enthusiasm
Let's talk, it's terrible
I'm getting on well
People were dreaming
It’s an era filled with frenzy.
Take him in your hands
People were reaching out
(Like the ground before a storm,
we’re thirsty with desire)
I don't watch it, but it's out of date
When will ordinary darkness come, I'm waiting
That voice, even
A suspicious voice
Come on, find out who I am
Press the middle button and listen carefully
Let me explain
Kupy's Wamoerea
This More Gutary
O'Cataly
Why does Tsugumono
While leaving it to high school students
I'd like to tell you guys too.
To the people, to this country, to Basa, to this era
This will also tell you what is happening
While I’m passing down this
story to the future generations,
Let me teach you more about Pee's
While I’m passing down this
story to the future generations,
Don't be thrown off
Hakumeyuno
This is so nostalgic
(The world is speeding up)
Oath hai ga ga
Dinosaur Light Song
Sugar block
(So don’t let yourself be thrown off!)
The
Heaven's deadline
Skill Reference
Love, if you will
Failure
The factory of the world, Great Britain
This is my place, just mix it up
, properly 'me' no more
and there is no
Sunlight yellow!
The hymn of humanity!
Midnight blue!
what is it
How do you feel?
merged e me
Rip through the wasteland!
Behind me,
I'm in a car rush
yeah
oh!
hang on!
Killing him!
Hey!
Makusuki!
It's crazy!
Makusu!
ah!
oh!
What should we do?
I'm not going!
I'm really going to do it!
Go!
nice!
C’mon, let’s go!
This idiot
oh!
Little puke stain!
Don’t let this brat go!
What’re you looking at, smart-arse?
Yours is the best
I don't want that to happen!
Masseuse in the front
I haven’t seen him since
his pub went under!
Oh no!
He croak or somethin’?
a
Medicine
The medicine is now
Word’s going around that
yer mum died in the plague!
Oh no
He should have sold her off
before she kicked the bucket!
I know
Hey
Since I disappeared as a new
Dio! Can’t you hear me?! Dio!
What is it, Father?
Nah, I don’t need that.
Oh... Do you need your medicine?
I haven’t got much longer. I know it.
It's a rule
I’m worried that after I die...
Okay?
My only child will be all by
himself. In that case... Dio,
Go to that guy
Take this.
That's nice
It can be stuck even if you cut it properly.
“Joestar”?
And he owes me one.
Okay, Dio
Go to him.
Dio
You’re a smart boy.
Stolen
Keep going
That's right
Unbeatable
I feel nauseous
It's hell now
Hakie wo Moyoko
They keep taking from me,
and it’s driving me mad
This place reeks of all these deadbeats
He hugged me
Nedio
This place reeks of all these deadbeats
My mother kept saying that
It was terrible and he died.
openly
She held me and taught me to be proud
She kept on saying that,
until the illness took her
“Hey Dio, look up at the stars”
Do you have it?
Just like that...
It happened
Blowing in my ears
The worst father
Not losing has always been losing
Under this cloudy sky
I was already running and dying
Let's receive Issan now
Use all
Under this murky sky,
Now, I’ll go take this “inheritance”
It happened
You have it
Boredom in that sky
That means I’ll start from here
Usually
Come on, I already have some good ones
Come on, I heard your family trades in medicine for your wife.
My father is a proper doctor.
I don't know. But the high stars.
You’ve got something good today too, eh?
Oh yeah!
Hey Erina, I heard that
your old man’s a quack!
Oh, do it!
Don't act all high and mighty just because you're in front of my house.
Hey, is anyone doing this?
It's Jouster Keljouna.
Stop right there!
I hate when guys try to
act cool in front of girls!
If he’s that Jonathan kid
from the Joestar family,
Ah-ha!
Dear breakfast!
Um, are you okay?
Leave me alone.
Snotty little rich boy! You think
you’re so high and mighty?
I didn't do it to be thanked by you.
I'm aiming for true passion.
You were a girl and it was a problem.
So I just stood up.
I did this because I wanted to.
Okay, let's go!
My goal is to become a true gentleman.
Jona-san Jowstar.
Let’s go, Danny!
Hey, Dani!
You...
You're Diopransola!
That's you, Jona-san Jouster.
Everyone calls her Chocho.
Looking forward to working with you.
This is my friend Danny.
Let's go.
It's okay because it won't sag or fall off.
friend?
Ah, Danny! I’ll introduce you.
Oh, and don’t worry about him biting!
Yeah!
I've been waiting for you, Diopland.
Danny! What was that for!
We’ve been waiting for you, Dio Brando.
What's wrong, Jojo?
From today on, you’ll be
living here in our mansion.
Maybe you could live your life like Jojo.
You’ve travelled all the way from
London, Dio. You must be tired.
BLADDOG!
It's the Cape Archer!
police?
Is something wrong?
The Jowstar movement is a long-standing friendship.
I heard Danny cry just now.
Oh, no!
Although, I could hear Danny
whimper a moment ago...
-He came at me so suddenly.
JoJo, I'm already happy with Danny.
You’ll let this Danny matter go, right?
It's a year like that.
JoJo has lost his mother too—
and you both are the same age!
BLADDOG!
JoJo!
Mister Brando!
So, this is my Geass game!
Don't touch my bag.
I'm driving.
Well, your hands are sticky like a dog's.
I was just trying to carry it for—
Your hand is covered in dog drool.
Alright JoJo, I’ll tell
you from the get-go.
What are you two doing?
They are trying to curry favor with humanity and ignore their enemies.
The way they grovel and suck
up to humans disgusts me.
I'll get to work on the jaw now.
Thus, the two proofs met and the two players began.
Hitaka Jojo.
Dioc.
Okay?
I aye raa
A little dancing,
Still no good, get it on your hands.
This is why we study, acquire knowledge,
To prevent us from connecting with each other
And arm ourselves with logic!
Under the guidance of
the goddess of familial love
Being reborn and illuminating
For the sake of heading
the house of Joestar
What’s this, JoJo? JoJo!
This is the sixth time
The same mistakes once again
Because I liked reading books
This much
It’s just because I love reading so much!
Ikane
We are
Here as a high memory
real
Check it out
That's not enough
Pesh thing
We behave like true gentlemen
Don't do horsetail
Nothing is always
Without passing by the beauty
Sit up straight, use your knife with grace,
So that your mouth always remains spotless
To be loved
Really high
Azukasa
a little bit
(The proud Joestars!)
Do you believe it?
Look at it
Do you call yourself a gentleman?
Perfect supporter
Shockley, too.
Aventine
That's it
Riwo
His manners are perfect!
I
Embarrassing
You
I am embarrassed by
how much I’ve spoiled you
Such
I am embarrassed by
how much I’ve spoiled you
always
Correct the festival
Ikane
We are
Were you born?
As a memory
Philosophy
However,
The exit
Bear in mind, as honourable nobles,
This is transmitted to England
There are two models
One day
Their master
By the enemy
Captive
It became
The enemy is
Huge power
have
The two models
fear
The enemy was afraid of the
two knights, who had great power.
Instead
You guys
Once menarche occurs
At one time
Life is
“If you two will be executed in her place,
I will guarantee the life of your master.”
where
To the two of them
It's a problem
yes
Here is my question for you:
Captive
It became
The two models
Corridor
Railway City
First
What was the first thing they
saw through their prison bars?
In front of me
Will it be a draw?
Or
On the diagram
Shine
want
I wonder
Which one?
think
I wanted
Draw?
I
Draw
I was watching
I think
Why
I think they were looking at the mud.
For the Lord
Death unexpectedly
In the end, they had no choice
but to die for their master.
If I die,
In the end, they had no choice
but to die for their master.
you can't
that's why
no matter how
You can’t achieve anything if you’re dead.
Alive
Something
Nasaneba and
I thought
I
I was looking at the stars
I think...
I think they should have stayed
alive and done something!
Two people
It's a kiss
They were looking at the stars!
It will be engraved
So
How did you live?
So what!
Cherish it
in the end
They
Himself
Nothing in hand
Not included
But they—
解鋼
Helplessness
They
What I saw
It's a draw
They
Teaching
Alive
What
this
What they saw was the mud!
Their lesson is to teach us what
we can achieve by staying alive!
Thank you
you
It's a rule
It's a thing
Take it away
Listen!
To fulfill that responsibility
Alive
What to do
So isn’t it your responsibility to think
about what you’ll achieve with your life?
I
Both of them
That far
At this time
That’s enough, you two.
People
A country of eyes and colors
live
So
Reach out
What you can see is
Do you want
Or
Which one
Both
Do they see the stars? Or the mud?
Lyrics
Don't you want to drive?
It's spose
moreover
I came with you
Eskikar
Hive Zekiar
a lot
It's the voice.
Today is exactly
Shukyo
If you lose
yes
Basso
Everyone
That far
The Winner is
All eyes on are on this ritual
where triumph goes to the victor
Who
Decide who is the king
Return
Everyone, gather around!
The winner is a sweeping hero
So
Come out
-Shall we tell our new friend
how we do things here?
Let's do it!
Alright, let’s do it!
It's Hong!
It's Feeket!
Yay!
Nodknocky!
That’s the bell!
Ah...
thing!
Y-y-y-take ra!
Feeket!?
Hey, how are you?
D ص PAR!
Ichikowa
Our king! Our king!
I think my finger went in his eye.
Dio, you were amazing!
How do you move like that?
So why don't you stop!
Hubber, everyone!
Why is Dio always trying to bring me down?
It feels like he’s invading my life.
Hey, Danny, my heart aches
And I’m filled with worry
What if I were to die today?
Would anyone cry for me?
You’re always so understanding
Thank you for staying by my side!
If mum were still here,
would it feel this way?
Would she love me this way?
You’re...
My hanky...
Hey, what's the flower pressure?
Hey, I’ll be back here tomorrow too,
Has it caught your fancy?
Please excuse me for
grabbing it without permission.
I don't care
They say this Stone Mask was
unearthed in some Mexican ruins.
Mexico...
When girls were just born
We bought it from a London art dealer,
around the time JoJo was born.
On the way back,
we had a carriage accident.
That was the time your dear
father saved us, you know.
Are you interested in it?
Oh, no. Not especially.
that
JoJo is always out playing
with Danny, isn’t he?
Danny's attitude towards women
Friendship? With a dog?
I had bought Danny when JoJo was young.
I won it.
At first, he was afraid
of unfamiliar people,
And he didn’t get on well with JoJo yet.
But one time, JoJo was drowning in a river.
My voice is all alone and no one can hear it
Just when JoJo was about to drown...
A figure, hearing his screams,
flew down to the river.
Danny jumps into the river
He dove in and saved JoJo’s life.
I know what life is
Danny was brave to have risked
his own life to save another.
Young JoJo was moved by Danny’s bravery.
Danny's feelings
Since then they
That’s when JoJo truly
became friends with him.
Eh? Ah, that’s right.
Dangaso too
ah
it was
Erina!
Butterfly
The two resumed
love
Love! That wonderful curiosity
that guided JoJo’s actions.
I took a few actions.
The two who are waiting to win
I was in love
Danny
Be well behaved
Hey JoJo, what are you carving over there?
What are you hiding?
no
It’s nothing interesting.
When you say it like that, it makes
me want to see it even more!
I won’t laugh.
I won’t tell, so show me!
No.
butterfly
Elina
Just call
Feelings
Relax
What kind of music
The sound
Any musician would fall
in love with its melody
What's going well
already
To be laughing like this
Morning or quite
Bab
The sky gets higher
Erina
butterfly
Our happiness is right here
The clouds are proud, and
the wind’s a little sweet
butterfly
Erina
There aren’t enough words
This one
For these ever overflowing feelings
forever
One word
I'm happy
I want to hear your voice
say, “it makes me happy”
Here
tickles
you
People who can't hear
I don’t know why, but I’m drawn to you
Then find a reason,
let’s make it our reason!
Put on Jariun
Then find a reason,
let’s make it our reason!
My hand,
Touching
be confused
It gives me a little courage
to move forward to tomorrow
To be continued
It gives me a little courage
to move forward to tomorrow
Trembling
Our hearts are resonating,
beating in time
surely
compete
Hawatsu
Preconceived notions
It’s already this late!
We have a guest coming
tonight, I have to hurry home.
Elina
Yes, JoJo!
Huh, okay?
Huh
compete
Suyoku
you
Jonathan Joestar
here we go
Ugh
You’re Erina Pendleton, right?
Today is
What do you...
They were just playing
something
wall
Ugh
Udo Yaa
here we go
Cling
today
What can't be done on broken ground
Do a transformation and get out
Have you kissed JoJo yet?
Not yet
The first person you kissed wasn’t JoJo...
This is Dio
You know what this sort of thing
means for a lady’s reputation, right?
You bitch!
This woman!
Are you saying soroagaarau on purpose?
Wow!
Oi, why’s the booze gone?!
Who do you think puts
food on the table? Stupid bitch!
Namaruka
yes
Father, mother’s clearly not well!
Oi, you hear me?
Kanaki Koiyori
I’m sorry! Please forgive me!
I’ve hurt you. I’m a good-for-nothin’.
Please forgive me!
Izawa Hiamatress
宙zech
You got money from that
factory job, don’t ya?
Please, leave some money
for medicine at least!
Eni
You’re really gonna
disobey me, you bastard?
You really expect me to
work my arse off for you? Idiot!
at least
You really expect me to
work my arse off for you? Idiot!
You’re all trying to make a fool of me!
That’s it. That noble, Joestar.
Magara
Crack
Well, my breasts are always twisted and swaying.
I noticed it too early and stepped on it
Yes, it's Joes.
You and I are different!
Follow
I am
With you
Haa
What in the world have I ever done
to you?! Can you tell me, Dio?
Hurt her
Haa
I want to go
I admired you!
Why?
Oh
Haa
You are amazing
Much more than me
I respect that.
But now there is a single
flame that burns in my heart
One thing is for sure
Aren’t you using my name
Oh no
Haa
Many people's names
Easy to wear
A small person
I heard that
My love
you
Kyusana
I'm the one
I don't care
nine
Haa
Stand up to it
No shoulders
this
I can't lose
Oh
Emotions
Dominate
Not like him
Slippery Heart
Her name
Get it back
Oh no
Come at me!
I'll make you understand
Oh no
Haa
you
I miss you
Get to know
That's a good impression.
Haa
This heart
You
Give it to me
Only
Oh no
You
Until Naku
like this
Lost
Don't bend
Haa
often
too
To me
Bukase
surely
Konoha
Better
Like this
Like winning
Cheap
This me
this
Looks good on you
Me, the great Dio!
Like winning
Cheap
This me
What on earth is going on?!
Haa
One
What's going on?
Both of them
Give a penalty
Go back to your room
Haa
I underestimated JoJo.
I have to become stronger...
His explosive power
I have to control my anger and stay calm...
So that I can take everything from him!
I need to calm down and control my mind more.
To get it all
But
Ah, it burns!
Someone! Someone please help!
Are you going to try to go outside?
Oh my god
Someone please
Hmm
Then Pan Seventies
First place
Bistriest
Ride behind
Aprekaeru Korori
What about artificial?
London’s peace has one
of its fingers broken
The map of London
paints a stark contrast
Chaotic days mix the old and the new
Melting Up Ten
Listening to British culture
Chaochao
Wartwack Osaka
Top Runner
Cattrell Dawser
Rowan peas on index finger
I'm sleeping
Port Levy
You’re... You’re certain,
that it was the Stone Mask?
The one excavated from Mexico?
Focusing on the darkness
It was quite a while ago...
That's Portobello
Port's own market
Is that correct?
Stone Turtle
Excavated in Mexico
And bought it from me at a high price—
Some gentleman’s wife
fell in love with it,
And bought it from me at a high price—
Yes!! Finally! I found it!
But there's no doubt about it
Now, where could I find this gentleman—
I don’t trust you...
Who the hell are you anyway?
Okay
I did it
I bought it
in
Where is Soroshinshi now?
It seems a bit suspicious
All the way from Italy?!
What is it?
Wait, he said he was
a nobleman from up north...
My name is
Seteri
Thank you.
By the stone turtle
I'm from Italy
Just a little word of warning...
The sun will be setting soon.
I'll do some research
Please wait
April
Ha
I'll give you a little China.
Will the sun soon set?
You'd better not go beyond that street.
Kiri appeared
The sun stops
Until then
When I'm in town
topknot
Please drink it
I don't know you
Kiritomo Sky
Not yet
chase
Second-rate
Reach out your hand
Voices around
I don't want to fall
Laughter and no laughter
Is comforting to us
Thrown away in the dump
Better
Talking about Autumn
Legs
(Jack the Ripper has drawn first blood!)
Worth going
Something's wrong
I'm sure it's because I'm dry
Until then
surely
Itchy
give
Kisakisa
Seriously awesome
Hated and scorned
Hateful Agebokoe
Right now
Immediately
Magical
That's it
Inagein
Ageing
Save Trafalda Stare
I can hear
Iodine
Shoot
Canelo
From the high party
The rich
My eyes still smile
Kirino
Shokiri
Kirashiyo
Firmly
Red
surely
Kobotuya
The flow also came
That's it
Kut
Hii
butterfly
Trafalda
Nun
Choyo
Firmly
Red Ant
So
Sasa is
What is it?
Woah!
Hey
Oh
Uuuuu
Just bring my smile back a little closer
First delusion
Dark dark girl
Ba be rinen
Silence
Get your mind back
Recruitment is against
Night night night night night Shalal ...
(In perfect harmony, they
make the best partners!)
I want to meet you, that's it
Just a little
The final match of the
season ends in victory!
Chochocho Maca's family car
So it's the last game
Winning the championship
a little bit
It's on the bottom right
Thanks to your parts
First, let's tell Dad about this victory.
Magician's Palace
Thanks to you
In the school scene
Can you tell me about your friendship?
thank you
Ever since you started
calling him “Father”
Let's go home together
Like water you don't ask for
Time passed
You
With Dad
Seven years spent studying diligently
To me
Those familiar words
think
7 years
Checking your calculations
You are
beautifully
It was believed
Make my Elio come true
Friends
think
Elinae's
Ayamachi
You are
I was eating
Danny's replacement
You are
He supported me.
Ahead of me
Your back
there were
7 years
Where
walked
However
Why am I
To you
How are you feeling?
Thanks to
Ah, well! I’ve got some big news for you!
Seem to have won!
If it continues this long
teeth
I'm getting old
Not yet
ah
oh yeah
And JoJo has become
a splendid gentleman.
Skilled
Dioplant
they
His recent archaeology thesis is superb!
And Dio is projected to graduate
top of his class in law school.
Joe was Dibbala Singh Singh
It was a brilliant stop in the field of high school studies.
Dio-kun is the number one in law.
Graduation
I can’t get rid of this cough...
Danda-sama
I just got home
I object!
And Jojo too
Are you okay, Dad?
They say it’s a problem in London too.
Today the doctor recommended I be admitted to hospital.
I give in.
The shaky hands and chest pain,
they’ll likely get better before long.
Enough of that. You two...
Congratulations on your victory!
Inspector Archer here told me.
The swelling in my hands and the pain in my chest will subside.
Congratulations to both of you on your wins
Oh no, silly me!
I truly am proud.
Cave
we
I just want to see your happy face
I could have just stoned it.
I'm here
I was born poor...
wonderful
There are already few
Inspector, thank you for always visiting.
But this is Liverpool!
Be what you want to be
To me, born of poor origins
There are men like him without
any humanity everywhere.
thank you
So I'm going to use this cable.
Thank you for always coming.
thank you
The tip of the cut is exposed.
It's the sound that has made lies a part of the world.
No, this is Liverpool.
anywhere
Like that guy
There are people who don't have the full amount.
So
do
staff
It's a living mechanism that responds only to
Who and for what purpose?
Thank you again, Master Dio—
Maybe I can make something happen on my way home from here
Thank you. I’m getting too old for this.
I am
Dario Pland
I'm always sorry
Rio-san
About giving medicine
Speed
thank you
I
Can’t you hear my voice?
perhaps
You will die
Can’t you hear my voice?
Hands waving
The voice calling for you?
My voice
A voice calling you
My mother died.
Two of my fathers
yes
Those shoes and
What
Pawn
He’s the one who killed mum
yes
Until that day
He died.
Zexal
I was separated from my wife by the moon.
Yes.
How hellish that your blood
is flowing through my veins
Right now
Lowering scum
Battle and
Aha
Hardness
Threw it
Assembled
Because I don't need it anymore
The match is
Without love
All those who were killed
Stolen
Shall I enter?
Name
It's different
On the body
Flowing
This hell
Zexal
white
This hunt
All
In these hands
Win
Human
To the End
Be prepared
Covering the wall
Enough
Dio!
Father
With the past
Sleep
all
Perfect
world
Get in and out
Come out
What is this non—
What on earth are
you trying to say?!
Name
Your
It's a letter from your father.
Death
Magi
Your father's
Symptoms
It's written in detail
Wow
Then you doubt our very friendship.
My
My father and symptoms
As a gentleman,
You
To Dad
was carrying
What
I’ll never speak of this again.
Swear on that guy?
you
Go
Swear on that guy?
I want to say
This medicine
Swear on it.
Excellent
This medicine
Give me the medicine back!
What to say
Our
Friendship
Doubt
As a belief
Your
地獄
My
Concerns
I won’t ever let you go
near my father again!
I’m convinced now...
I
Never again
I’ll protect the Joestar family.
close
From the very beginning
somewhere
Until the end
Infection
this
It’s too late to turn back now.
yes
I hated my father
Above all, I was suspicious
It got cut
Joe John
I’m going to London
for two or three days.
no
It's okay
No no no no no no no no no
No, no, no, no, no
I don’t know what’s going on...
A perfect world
But I trust my son!
no
How about it?
What's going on? Yes, Master
Speaking out loud like that
Well, I'll be doing my second and third thesis. In the meantime, I've decided to give them a perfect tour. I will not be receiving any medicine or medical treatment except from them.
I’ll make it appear as if he had
an accident during his research.
Seven years ago, this guy reacted to me, what happened?
8 years
Use this,
Time’s nearly out, so I gathered
my resolve and took off!
Gradually
Your research will kill you
field
(Ogre Street, we devour anything we can)
Looking up at Koshio with the results already in mind
Master is the coldness of the world today Listenomuuran Build
(Ogre Street, we devour anything we can)
(Ogre Street, here everything meets its end)
The country in front of me is on the other side of the world, there are reasons why I can't move forward
Got no problem with you bein’ naïve,
I’m just showin’ you the simple reality
Hey hey hey,
how about it, rich boy?
Want a taste of the
edge of this knife?
Who's coming? I'm the one who's good now.
This is Ogre Street!
Ain’t it obvious that we’d cheat?
(Ogre Street, go on and leave it all behind)
I don’t care if I lose four fingers!
Treplatzitzcuiscocoscue
Hogar is the problem.
Just tell me the simple truth
I'm going to rip this Kilean Ajibainar off the spot.
You said you’re fine with
losing four fingers, hah?
(Ogre Street, why don’t we
put that resolve to the test?)
Bowery, life is Ongar
(Ogre Street, why don’t we
put that resolve to the test?)
Hold on! I only came here
looking for a poison seller!
Quit bluffin’! Let me have a
go at this soft little rich boy!
Hoga Street Now I know our image chronology
There is in the family
You lose a finger, that's average.
Hoga Street Scatsl is in love
I came to look for Dr. Equol.
Don't miss out, ruin the rich boy
I thought you must have a father,
or mother, or siblings too.
I made a mistake, but I'll put an end to it
Gantdown Slis Hwaga Street
Stop it
If you lay a hand on that parent and child, you'll have to wait a little longer.
Why didn't you kick it as you pleased?
I came here for the land
That's why Kelsim thought you must have a father or siblings.
(You, who have the courage)
(To see the stars down here in the mud)
If you're not careful, you'll get caught out. Be careful.
(Light up the darkness with
your unwavering heart!)
Why did I like you?
Let’s toast—to our meeting!
It's a hidden flame
Gantdown Slis Hwaga Street
Quickly take out the
See which run
This courage is what I'm talking about
With my pure heart, I will light up your darkness
February is over and it's a complete disaster
This plum blossom, this encounter,
Up
leisure
Please get it today
JoJo...
Huh...
…
Oi, are you listening, you stupid brat?
Didn’t you hear me?
Which one?
…
Just now?
Are you stupid? Oi, Dio!
What did you do to my mate?!
My voice
I’ll kill you!
Is another man’s fortune!
Interesting, this is a good
opportunity to try it out!
Become the richest
It’s a live human experiment!
Dio Dio Dio Dio Dio!
JoJo!
This is what I'm hearing
Kitsutsu's face is blue
I’ll find the answer to your
research myself right now!
I gave Bamma a good sleep.
I'm sure
This face
Back of face
Wow
It's not even possible that it will be born
Inside
Earthquake Floyd
Delicious
It's your fault
Wow
Was I hallucinating?
Pukula
Should I do it or paint it?
This mask is just some ancient
sacrificial torture device.
Also, the company
Let me come over
It's a journey of success
Hehehehe
Well then
Your research is dissolved
I'll do it
Do it
Ah
, not easy
What
I’m thirsty, thirsty, so thirsty!
He’s sucking my blood!
Dead
If this much koshin is stabbed in the head, it's only natural that he'll be punished.
I don’t want the morning sun
to be the last thing I ever see!
Not dead
Mamachi
What is this guy?
Sue
m
Change
Undevide apply
Dragon
then
in
Also
already
ambitions
I'm excited about you
graders
Are you flying?
andin Glish
ootlands
stay
maybe add orca Bureau
If there was nothing like that
me
Please use the foyer.
In sunlight
This is my cross to bear.
This is
This happened when you were a baby.
So, Deo
I arrested the man who
was caught pawning it.
Support us right away!
Use your hair
thank you
Hey
That way of asking
Bring Wyche.
Chocho
It's great
Tears welled up in his eyes.
picture?
I...
I arrested the criminal!
He’s certain to be exiled!
For you
I'll tell you
You
Here he is! Oi! Wake up! Brando!
surely
Dario Brando isn’t some saviour,
But a thief!
No notification was submitted.
Finger speech
A man who fell in and out
Corresponding
Even knowing this,
Lord Joestar adopted Dio.
Jostar Kyoga
Why?
I was moved to tears by
what Lord Joestar said next.
Something special made in pairs
I was moved to tears by
what Lord Joestar said next.
picture?
this is
This is a finger spelling I made with my wife.
Today is
My wife
Did you find it?
That I gave him this ring?
I
This is what I gave him.
Would you like to wish me a happy birthday?
Recorded items
But it’s a memento of your wife!
Understood
curler
Hey
Woody
Planned
Stop
Well then
Dario Pland is
Even with life and onjin
Nothing
Just
It's Nust
Just a lie
That
I know
Dio
If I were suffering from poverty
Why
I
Today's
At that time
If I were suffering from poverty
Tears
you
he
Didn't I say this?
This sign language is
When the stars in the sky
shine, they start to tell a story
There was a picture
Ugh
Yes.
this is
What I gave him
He is innocent
Yao's wife
It's hard
Mr. Pland
yes
This is yours
Let’s pray that this light
will illuminate the darkness
hand
To my family
Please buy me something
Just a lie
Why that?
Deserveo
If I
In a strange way
suffering
If we had met
The same thing
Did you?
picture
Let’s embrace that courage,
that loneliness,
The stars in the sky
Light Yes
Eventually
That pain
This friend
Shibi
Darkness
There’s a meaning to it all
Prayer place
thank you
you
You're too kind
This evil and
It's warming in my heart
Maybe so
But
That’s why...
Something called destiny
from
People
Tell me
Forget
That courage
Will shine one day
Let's hug
Orimo
I will defy fate!
To everything
Garu
I
Inspector.
He can still be stopped.
For your viewing pleasure
Good
it is
someday
Kakaya
Gudarou
There is another
On the tray
I
Shichizuki
Aki's Ambulance
a
bothersome
Noroi
nine
I
Waiting for Dio
still
Can be stopped
You
I heard Nauwa-san
Frosia's man
Already the wall
I crossed the seven seas
with my respected father
And the man
My beloved father, the voices
of my friends, my youth
Can't enter
I heard
It's the same as 30 years ago
Just like back then
Park of Memories
nailed down
Kusabi
Systemic training
That morning sun
Yes, tomorrow...
It was red
Full of passion
Longing for the road world
My respected father
Hit the rolling sea
My beloved father
Voice of Things
At my exact moment
Day 1
From this hand
Take it all away
Including force
To get it back
Tomorrow for sure
Even if you open it, I'm thinking
Although you might not believe me,
One day
It will become irreversible
This hand...
Therefore
To turn myself in to the police.
It's a shame, really.
You may not understand, but this is the truth
What I did was terrible!
You are that kind of guy.
Don’t believe a word he says!
It's the last one
Can you give me some time?
Allow me to introduce myself!
I
I’ve met all sorts of horrible
people throughout my life.
Born into a poor family
I got a palm.
This man has confessed already.
When words
I’ve heard everything I need to.
I will return to my bed to rest.
I am
Anyone
I don’t want to see my son
being taken away in handcuffs.
I am
He was born with an innate destiny.
I've been driving since it got stuck.
I've seen a lot of different people
So you can tell by the smell
This guy is Bakise
Really! The boy is already gone.
To be human is to have limits
And still the more I try to plan,
or
I don't want to see you get caught
That man won't give up
This frustration, it’s unbearable
Sores!
Girl, girl, I got it!
You'll be released, but at least
I want you to take over
We've been together for seven years.
Be careful!
Understood
I'll take the lead
For humans
There are limits
I am
I understand now
Yes, Joestar, even
your purest pedigree,
Can’t wash the filth out of mine
To break free, from this cage
I'm so frustrated
The Stone Mask?
The empty logo
With a glance next to me
My humanity!
No matter how much I write
Follow these eyes
Do you understand?
That smiling sky
I want you to know me
This hand is out of reach
Shoot him!
On that beautiful day
This dumping ground will never disappear
So now is the time
Father! Father!
Light
One
I am
Mom
Life
It opens
Right
Yes
please
Hahahaha
Yes
Initial battle plan
I'll take your mother's finger
Firmly
I knew I made a mistake, back then.
I've been hard on you
Maybe when I got home I felt it was fair.
Shoot
It doesn't seem bad
Gradually
The last one
In my son's arms
father
Do it.
After all, at that time
You always remained a
gentleman, until the very end
Survey
Whether it's a hearing or not
I was always told
Proudly
everytime
I said I'd save you
I believe
I’ll engrave your will into my soul
I'm powerless to have been unable to protect you
What do you believe?
Open the door
What is pride?
What's the purpose
This Joestar blood
flowing through my body!
Survey results
Always in judgement
continued to exist
Proudly
Yourself
Rishiki
The voice of darkness
Inspector! It’s an emergency!
Look up at the stars
Put everything into it
Inspector!
Dance your heart out
Dance and shine
What the hell?! He came back to life!
Even though we shot him into Swiss cheese!
Survey results
Everything is connected
It all makes sense
I don’t get it! I can’t make heads
or tails of what’s happening!
A single drop of courage
It's Keiban and Daiyan.
what up?
That's the corpse
Dion's body is missing.
It became
Satsuma
Get away from the window
Massage
Keiban
What is this guy, he's come back to life
Even though I was interrupted by forgetting
Be careful
I have some bookies.
Tomare
Utero
Don't be silly
It's early
If that’s the case...
It was what was happening now
Haa ...
Are you waking up?
Suddenly puffed up...
Hiriamado is hard to laugh at
You're J…
I've got such amazing power
From someday
Your father's power
A quick fix to the running.
Let me enjoy this amazing power
for just a little longer!
What do you think?
I can only get a bad taste from Misonoru
If it stops
If you peel off the head completely
Stop it!
Menoeka!
Already
It's stronger
Crab Cui Crab Cui
a!
What?
I'll enjoy this wonderful power for a little while longer.
I don't know how far I can go yet
Both specialists
Don't give in to useless longings
Is that an invitation, JoJo?
If you let it bloom,
(The flash of flames,
scattering the light)
Well, don't hide in the shadows, come out
Kisamalabop
Let it be my life
JOJO: Please give me strength
DIO: For giving me strength
It's organic
I can't beat this day
Speed ​​Low
I always walked in your shadow
Confusing
Don't run upstairs
ah
And Father is dead!
It's going up
Well then
I'm here
Do you understand?
Ladies, ladies, you first
The more you run, the more light you scatter
Today is your strength
Finish eating
It's useless, it's useless
That a stronger fire could overpower
that demon’s healing ability.
This flickering
Not from afar
Let's give one
Damn it! Mr. Joestar!
From now on, always
From your back
On my back,
There was someone in front
My player is Kimetomo
Final exam
He also decided on his own
Women
Women's Palm
You are burning
I'm dead
I lost it immediately
This body is immortal.
That too
Burning
Heat it up
That is
The only one dying will be you!
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
More firepower
That Mamoru's recovery power
After placing it
more
More firepower
Throw away
The knife you stabbed Father with!
If you do
With this final bit of strength
Shit
Jasasasa
It's your fault, I almost fell into the basement
Where do you approach? I've grown fond of you
As I thought, this crying that won't let go was there
You're the type who stands up for yourself
My chest is insecure
I'll do things I hate
The one I saw was one I hated
Let's go live a life that will make you feel like a child
There was a lot of excitement.
Can you hear me?
Janshah
Refreshing
Much more bizarre.
He beat Dio,
Three days later...
That was a 13th century mistake, not a 16th century one.
We must tell the story accurately
It was a great loss for someone in that position.
The mask that man wore!
it was good
I am the storyteller
JoJo, can you hear me?
And I continued to do
My voice calling for you?
Refreshing
I did a complica
The story so far seems like a fairy tale
is definitely a reality
And it gets weirder from here
Yeah, strangely.
At that time, the mansion was almost completely engulfed and collapsed.
But Chosa was still there
I was attacked by Dio
But I lost everything
Then see
You slept for three whole days!
The mansion! Everyone is—
there were
I can hear the voice of your face, the voice that reads you
This is my father’s hospital.
This is me, but...
It’s really been too long.
I was weak back then,
I couldn’t run to your side
That's why I came
I have enough vocabulary
Please come on the 5th.
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Can you hear my voice?
listened to each other
Once again, when I see a vivid person
Your voice
I
That little bit of courage
to move towards tomorrow
All the mansions
Please stay calm now
We've passed the statistics, but times are still tough.
I can feel you there
You've been nursing me
You are Yamasaka
But they look similar
Who do you think looks like me? Erina Pendleton
Now our hearts
resonate, beating as one
Female Joestar
Why
This is my father's hospital
India moved too far seven years ago.
I recently planned
It's really been a while
I was weak
It wasn't my first time with you
It was me who was young
I couldn't face you
That voice remains unchanged
This voice remains unchanged
Vivid reverb
The sky gets higher
Erina JoJo
It was the same method, another woman—
(And she had her guts ripped out!)
Elina
sorry
My mind is shaking and I lose consciousness
The truth of the
matter is out of reach!
(Like it’s made of fog)
Eye to eye
If you touch it, it's there
Plainness is courage
Moving on to tomorrow
Hand in hand
Touch and there
When our eyes meet
Oh, it’s already so late!
I have to return home soon...
overlap
attract
fit
That day
You’re talking with him right now!
destiny
yes
The encounter of people
Maybe it's decided by fate
Kitty Dwagon
Cool!
Who goes there?
lover
See you again soon
It's a camera
Heaven and earth are the same woman
A girl
Early afternoon
Its Appearance
The agreement is mutual
Oh, I must heal these wounds,
and for that I’ll need lives!
It's going to happen. He's going to appear.
London is also popular
It's getting chaotic, I don't know anything about it
Black people don't eat
However, very rarely there are
those not constrained by goodness.
What do you know about me?!
Chasing the ripples
I wanted to convey
This mod official
Those women who
indulge in pleasure
Women who are
dripping with ecstasy
Go and spill more guts! There’s
no need to be afraid anymore
Me, afraid?!
That’s right!
I’ll give you pleasure greater
than you’ve known before
Even though we're talking
Play until the end of the night
Relax
Who is it?
you
I liked it
A life that forsakes the sun!
I don’t need it anymore!
There's no more of that
Reborn now
This is Dio’s World!
I have to heal my ache
So I feel less fulfilled
Don't you want power?
Solve the Wonders
I'll give it to you
Man is bound by all treasures
I fear great evil
But very rarely
Without all treasure
There is an evil elite
Me
You are
How about it?
The Stone Mask...
To you
I want to believe it turned
to dust like everything else.
Yes.
So you
It has to have been.
I can dance to your heart's content
Such
Covered in the distance
Lose too much
What’s wrong?
Who’s that?
It seems like it will change
Has he been here
this whole time?
Yes.
Well then
Jonathan Joestar!
More spinning than ever before in my hands
This is
Such as
do not have
It's crowded
The Stone Mask?!
You
Come stretch
Jack
Zalipa
This hand
Anyway
Atanosa
Of air inside your lungs!
Together
That's not right
There
To this time
I am Baron Zeppeli!
nine
My
Restoration
That's it
Your
It's a hobby
Who are you?
Kekari
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
Messy tears
became
Like this
Ban Duan
The power that this breathing awakens!
他の棚同城細相信台
yes
It's okay
Are you okay
let's go
Huh?
what happened?
Who is it?
I've been here for a while now
Jora-san Choustar-kun
Huh? And
Miss Elida Pendleton
I'm surprised I survived
The ripple’s power
passes through the frog
Isukamen!
Wait!
Jola-san
Oshipa
Keep it open
By air
Wherever you go, you'll be disappointed.
Becoming a mites
That's lame!
The air seems to be tight
No appearance
I am Separi Danshak
All I have is courage
The power of the ripple gathers that small
amount of energy from all over the body.
I'm your friend
Your breathing
To him
Breathing created that power?!
Yes! The power of breathing!
I'm your perspective
Jora-san Jowstar
What is it?
What's that pain?
Yes, I know it all
Appearance
Give me one
So too are you and Dio!
Follow me
Just now I
Eyes change
The man wearing the mask, Dio,
walks in the darkness even now!
I love you
So that I can destroy it!
This breathing
The place to wake up
We must destroy it!
Smart
Will I get my hands on it? Our fates
Country Petunassau
The concussion
Hackopping
Tyaeaars
Energy is generated
The name is
Hamon Energy
Horororororororororororororororororororororororororororo
Hamon's attack
Thank you
To fight... That is my destiny!
Dropped
This is
The Stone Mask’s bone needles
draw a strange power from the brain,
Kokum brings
The Stone Mask’s bone needles
draw a strange power from the brain,
Smart
Cocuille
However, the ripple also derives its
power from the flow of the bloodstream.
Carrying heroes and adjusting responses
The bond force converts that small amount of energy into
Ah, let’s put it this way.
This is made possible by a certain breathing routine.
Breathing is the power of now
Yes, the power of breathing
Yes, I know
Thinking about it
If you hit them with another
ripple, they’ll break apart!
And that wave of energy
Dios
Kamen is owned by someone who hasn't changed.
Has the same shape as the light of the sun!
We’re already out of time.
I followed Kamen
Destroying and eating
Dio is alive
Just catch cute
I can’t get you involved in this!
In the hands of destruction
Well, is there any more?
Yours
Your world
I swear I’ll come back here again.
I finally found it
Tattered and worn
Do you accept it?
Eyes working hard
Everything was discussed
Sma
destiny
fight
That's my destiny
You mean me?
I nodded along, to your resolve
Leave the humans to rest
it is
You must take blood energy from others.
To the sorrow you held
Mizukaru's blood flows
Stars are drawn together
Yeah
Guided by this hapless fate
As I wander here, mired in mud
What do you think I should do?
I'm starting to understand
Jamon
If you hit another Hamon
They'll explode
And the tears of energy
It has the same shape as the sunlight
Tell me, why am I left in solitude?
yes
There's no time
Even if it doesn’t reach you,
even if it won’t bring you back to me,
woman
Dio
Energy
I won't get involved in anything that gets you involved
Because you left for my sake
I'll definitely come back to this place
This is
Is it a female jamon?
Yeah
Haa
Clouds flow
The wind carries my thoughts
Measurement
go around
I nodded.
To your resolve
In sadness
Shining stars
Guided by this hapless fate
I got stuck in the mud
I will live on!
Left behind
Living the dream
Wait by the window
Loneliness is
For whom?
Even if it doesn't reach
Even if it doesn't shine now
I want to scream
I
Even if it doesn't shine now
Wang Chan, you’re alive?!
I
Because
you
There is light
anytime
Don't let your destiny lead you
I
Spending my days
Let's live
Why are you so strong?!
While
This place
Someday you
He'll tell you
Proudly
I wa-ha-ha-was looking for you too!
Your everything
Acceptance
Destiny and Love
yes
What was that, you old fart?
Time for a taste!
Daylight
Your
Don't let your destiny lead you
The stars
Daylight
Where
Even if
I
Me
Live on
Alive
Go
Kiev
Otsuku
Going
Go
Wear
Wihaha
Weано
Wear
What is that disease?
Maza KAL
Dion too
Spain
Wearcon
You
Stone Masked Secrets Too Dead!
That's it!
Sioster!
Aa ...
Oooooohhhh!
I was looking for you too!
They became vikings with backbone!
Dio was there!
I'm willing to rip off your value!
Licky?
Lick lick!
Lick lick lick!
Vero up and down?
picture?
The pain of losing friends
What's with this weirdo Pojnock?
I'll come when I get there!
You need to listen to that pain!
We we we we we we we we we we we
Nadada și Ichinyo Tiny many
Staining the darkness red
Daizara doesn't have a phone
Gon!
My body...
What was that?!
見事だ、少少
My father and I once
crossed the seven seas
yeah…
what up?
JoJo...
The mask burst with light
So I wanted power
But that's...
And all 58 men of my
crew were massacred
The man in the mask came forward
Things like this will go down like a ride
What I saw in that moment, illuminated
by the salvation of the morning sun, was—
A harsh coming will wake you up
Because I know the pain
Under the red light of the
morning sun, my father disappeared
Miyatsuka is different.
You
My soul’s clock has been
frozen in that moment ever since
pain
We embrace this pain
ZEP: I’ve been chasing after it
JOJO: So that it won’t repeat
Pain is life
Red
We embrace this pain!
Believe me
I was always told
My father's back
everytime
I still don't know what to believe
Heart-warming
Dosuta no Chi
Hot
The day screen
Emits light
Perspective
I believe in the power of the ripple.
Holding this pain
The screen is not a word
I happened by chance
Tonight in my memory
nailed down
rust
I will win
My Father and the Seven Rabbits
I handed it over
Quiet Leg Night
That screen
Emits light
50 First Time
Jonathan Joestar!
He had been murdered.
The masked man comes
Protect the darkness
Love you
At that time, the morning sun
Is that Mr. Horse?
It was my insect
In the red morning light
Illuminated floor mat
disappeared
At that moment it stopped
Hey yo yo! We’re coming
to collect payment
Catch up
Don't look back
Approaching excellence
We drove, no stopping sites
Tomorrow is the day
With pain
While the sun’s out
and
Back to school
Right?
You play with life, that’s bullshit!
I haven't forgotten
yes
Now’s the end, ya gonna get hit!
let's go
Let it clear up
I
T-The horse!!
Surprise fall
It's a horse
good
Ah, okay.
Wow, across the street
I will fight!
Stand down, you two.
Don't invite me to 'Mytuke'
yeyyo yo yo harai ni imuka ouzhe
I occasionally watched it.
Reprate Ilashala Association
Ace Case Bead Wargo
You're a weak little Jousta
Of course I'll be your guide
There is no guide
Juul Lauction
Shaodar
You’ve heard of fleas, yes?
They come after us humans
even though we’re giants to them.
Opposition Party Email to City
Could you call something
like that “courageous”?
This Wind Knight Roto
“Fear” sends your breathing awry!
Wind Knight Roar
Inrenga Show Tideion Ast
Dayon Arbunchiri
Code Oak Ostana Chili
The greatness of humanity
is the greatness of courage!
Dioteme
thank you
This information is from me
Yes... I’ll eat every
shred of you in one bite!
Dio will realize his empire here.
While there is Dio
Yes... I’ll eat every
shred of you in one bite!
I can see the tunnel
This is the entrance to the city.
The projection area is as planned.
There’s a hidden passage in the tunnel!
Why stop place
Be careful
Yes. Dio’s surely at the end of the trail.
Look!
No no no rail
Summoner's magic is a demon bon
I fight
Get your revenge on the past,
let’s rewrite history
Upend righteousness,
go for total victory
Various drinks
This recruitment is for us humans
Children on the right path
Can you call that a yuke?
Goddess
Something I want to say and talk about
Now raise your voices,
from crushed throats
Who is it?
Eye Base
Hamoho Country is an organic acid
Human oxidation is organic oxidation
Crying out from the mud,
conquer the stars
How strong is
(Now is the time to raise our voices)
Drink and drink
Dolly
Hot Hot
Yackoma
Covering the other side
Cover
why?
Small tree trainer
Kutcha
Hide in the tunnel
Wait, Dio!
This is Kisstats' training ground.
There are various tricks
And there's a big deal at that time.
He is thriving
My world is in the palm of my hand now!
This too
azz
so
surely
vague
I will dominate history too,
Be aware
Kun
Retreat
Sleeping Kissachi
Huh, uhh, realized?
Answer: Law, I want to make you my own Law
Now let's reveal the truth behind the parliamentary
Fuji Ha Well He vomiste
My world, this world!
Long clouds hang over this country. Now is the time to speak up.
A cry from the sky continues
So much that there’s a hole in my cheek...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Your cheek is melting,
And your tongue is sticking
out of the hole? Really, Jack?
The sun has set.
I’ve been building up my
courage for this moment!
It's scary
Put your training to use.
It's scary from the sky
This has taken my world away
(We’ll feast! On your blood and flesh!)
Even my mouth is still open
Hair Child and Varialli
Make history solid
This battle will be an exercise—
SPW: We’re not here to play around, have you lost it?
ZEP: You shut your trap!
JACK: I’ll kill them!
DIO: Ah—wait, wait—
It's scary
Search
All seems solid
Muster up your courage! When the time
comes, don’t let your breathing go awry!
Now, with the current
The greatness of humanity is
the greatness of courage!
Everything is connected!
There’s a meaning to it all!
It's shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking
The ripple of the wine!
Igu Shichiraku Intercom
I can feel it flow, I’ll find my
way through the darkness!
Body de jai
Data
With the power of the sun!
Because, oh, it's true!
Popping out
Pa-pow-pow-pow with unrelenting heat!
Kisamara's life too
When you're bossing
I've been preparing for that moment
So it's going to be a Dosukuro Eki
You have to forgive me as a human being
上書
It's a fighting mindset
I'm bored
At first
This is the power
that will defeat you!
By this bisabigi
Bu-go attack
It's Lesland.
Sakasei
Let's ride a bike
went
It's just a good thing
Finally, we meet.
Defeat that guy
I didn't come back later,
You are here
Hitakaze is a Viking
I'll book it and give it a go
That's dangerous
Yokkapinu
Hitatakawara Viking
Severe living activity is born
I wonder if this bath will have a buffet.
To purge this wound!
Won't open
Just how many lives did you
extinguish to heal that wound?
Courageous Participation
Humans are amazing too
The awesomeness of courage
All
Connect
resonate
Do you remember how many slices of
bread you’ve eaten in your lifetime?
Hmm
There's no cold
My Hallow
is
Vegetable warping
Shoes
Yana
Rug bespoke
Tears
I guessed that this energy of yours
is related to the flow of your blood!
It’s freezing?!
Cragbeshable
Society too
soon
Bullbearly
Instagram
Let's pull
Wrapped in cherry blossoms Wrapped in cherry blossoms
Then you won’t be able to use that power!
I can’t—I can’t catch my breath!
Breathing techniques? Ripple?
Grz
Gather at Gabo Japma Ra
Sun Feather From yourstag
This is the power that will defeat you!
Dio Brando!
a?
Looks like your companions
are just as weak as you.
But
JOJO: What did you say?
DIO: Companions...
Dare to face a stone wall
The story of the knights
your father told us that day?
Don't ride it
bard!
- If I can heal this wound
It was about the ones who served her!
The story of those two proud knights...
At Kisamara's command, I will disinfect this wound in the air.
I will regale you with
a tale of two knights,
Do you remember the bread you've ever eaten?
I'll let you sleep.
One was Queen Elizabeth the First
bread!
品積品積!
This shows that the length of the arms and the energy of the arms are related to the product.
I can control my body freely.
Tarkus’s strength cleaved
through rocks like butter
Breathe, breathe!
Help!
While wishing for a nest to rest in
breathe?
Conger eel?
While wishing for a nest to rest in
Hahaha
The two heroes would not rest
That's right.
Do you remember?
When it came to saving their Mary
Elizabeth made an appeal:
On the beard that was executed in the death knell
Mary Stuart
It was used there
This, we cannot refuse
Dad's
Now
In this, we hold no regrets
Jojon, Dion
Today, this tradition is passed down in England.
Let's talk about two Kishi
Your master isn’t being held in the tower.
Kishi's
The rest of the story
Once upon a time, 300 years ago
Let's cheer on the two of us
You’ve betrayed us, Elizabeth
Beautiful Mary Stuart
Mary gave me that turgid
They couldn’t cut through his neck!
Hahahahahaha
From now on
As though it were alive!
And that is the story,
Of those knights who lived
according to their hearts
Two without two
Until the very end!
I think about it
The Dearie Situation
Find peace
Use clothing
Flowing Time
It might be as you say, however—
By Elizabeth
The only thing to call
their deaths is useless!
It might be as you say, however—
The same can be said about the
fact that you came here to this house.
To save Mary
To stop the grace of the two
All people live in a prison called fate
You guys should mess with us
Save Shugun's life.
To Elizabeth
There is no denying it
Our difficult story
Because of this order
It's so easy to get caught up in it
I turned those two
This system is unacceptable
I bowed my head
It's possible that it's lying around here like trash.
I'll keep it cool
Because there is a semi-translated version
Wow
To Elizabeth who went behind the scenes
It’s the perfect form for
taking their revenge!
Don’t you think so?
With anger erupting
That's why it resonates
Kill them all!
Bruford!
Play me a fanfare with their screams!
I'll wait
The way you feel—
But I also bear my own burdens!
A goosebump-inducing proposition
I’ll savour every bit of his cartilage!
But they should have done better.
I couldn't do anything in the first match.
It can also be said that there is no waste.
That man’s pride...
I will stand to meet it, as a knight!
Would like to be the one to bring
an end to this brave man’s life!
It's all connected
Would like to be the one to bring
an end to this brave man’s life!
I want to believe
We’ll duel as knights!
Run away, you two!
I won’t let you interfere!
Gradually
Say it's your fault
A wedge driven into the
wasteland of my memory
The devil also created Bedbukhushki
Don’t come any closer!
Damn it...
This is what you look like
Come on, get real,
even at a time like this?
What an embarrassing sight
Don't you think so?
I’ll still be over here crying like a loser
A continuation of that day
Tarkus Bellaford
The secret name Fansuar
I'm tired
Is revenge your answer?
Is that what you take pride in?
Slow Idiom Kiss Bellaford
and Tarkus
I think that's a bit
Now’s the time, to let
courage resonate in my heart
But I also have something to carry
I must find the strength to stand up
I’m not scared of pain
The man's anger
Tomorrow is right now!
Old man!
In this Braford
I would like to draw every day of this man's life.
Okay, that's good.
Make a good list and get it
If it hurts, run away
Survey
And look the enemy in the eyes
Find the strength to
get back on my feet
nailed down
Wedge
Anyway
That morning sun
Like this
It was red
Osa
You live
Now
This pain means nothing to me!
I'm not good
Wait a minute
Don't mess with me
Even at a time like this
Why aren’t you moving?
Come
Carefully
Continue
Tomorrow for sure
Make Irumide
I kept chasing
Remember
You can feel pain!
That’s why...
Kisana
I stopped fighting you.
and
Once processed
That's what happened
That’s why you stopped your sword.
Get on the Tokoro Bull Bus
It's not pain
already
You are a great knight.
You are human!
Morning tomorrow
Tomorrow
Now
There
picture
Tokewa
Even if I return
When
I guess he did it
Kiki's
Looking back at the station
Is it urgent?
Don't wait for tomorrow
I start walking
Should believe
It should be said that
Tomorrow Now
girl
The Beat of Decision with You
Why is it moving?
When I looked into it
That
Hiding
Pikima
pain
No or
Just as I thought...
You are feeling pain now
pain
That's why I stopped being that Sarakai
Your ripple is more vulgar than frog piss!
Human
Watch out, Mr. Joestar!
Sennorakashi
This is a human being
Because there are similarities
What did he have to be joyful about!
How could you!
I feel now
Bravo
I will dedicate to you the words engraved on my prefecture.
Something like this
and
Let's go
To save souls
That you take my ripple
and continue on, JoJo!
Come
Affection
No way
To think he would defeat Kurokiko
also
I’ll vanquish your wicked soul!
Haybay Day
Drown in the murk of history, Tarkus!
I tempted you
What changes is not the outcome but the vile Hamon
There’s no time to be sad.
At the beginning of the season
Brami's brother
Loss of motivation and enthusiasm
驚
Lots of Ou
From now on
You showed me my purpose
Who I am meant to be
JoJo
Follow me for my last jamon
Into my spirit
JoJo!
Wow
always
Search Chokil
Add to the sound of the sir
That’s what I’ve come to believe
Carlton!
Oklaine!
Windows 4
Hey, Jebel, Jebel, if you're gone, I'll be sad, but one day I'll destroy my eyes, but hey, I'm happy with my life. Finally, I've entrusted it to you.
Hey, you're my hope.
Once again, the sun's rays are spilling out of my arms.
You taught me the meaning of my life, my destiny, and the greatness of being human - courage.
The light that was received would seep in. In my heart, I felt as if I was both dead and breathing at the same time.
From now on, I'm coming into you. Thank you very much.
Everything is connected, everything has a body.
This pain, this pain that I believed,
What your father gave you, what you gave you.
Don’t call my name—
There is one thing that is so certain that it is in my heart right now.
Embrace it, because this moves,
Look at the stars.
What do I want?
Light up the darkness and bring your return,
Come back,
happiness.
Can't you hear me?
I hear a voice calling to you,
They were a noble sacrifice for
the sake of the future that I designed.
Call my name.
Unlike you.
Of being human...
That’s why you rejected your humanity.
Laugh to live,
Use and take everything,
Disobey justice,
To all of Wasa,
Use and take everything,
The ends justify the means.
I will win,
Laughing,
I want it,
All of this is fate!
no one,
Such righteousness!
Well then,
And then died!
what,
The world you lost long ago,
Is this a sad world hidden by dead people?
As a gentleman, it pains
me to say this, but...
Lion
Even history
Now I, Jonathan Joestar...
For the sake of revenge...
You're just scared
Humans
That's why I gave up being human
To get it
Become my next meal!
All you need is results
I won
The only result is that you are in control.
My heart’s aflame
But
How did you live?
Paying to Fate
What did you leave behind?
Rumbling, rumbling, rumbling
To me
Just like Mr. Zeppeli taught me!
dead
Your
Utterly pathetic!
That's right
smile
Going out as a faithful servant
The current situation is
To tell the story behind
Ko how proprio
I transcended humanity!
None of you are on my level.
You’re nothing but a monkey, JoJo!
JOJO: No, for as long as I have faith,
DIO: Compared to me, Dio!
I'm good with tax
shake alone
hahhh
Finally, a name that stands out
What's left now
Like fire and ice
務 manual you
He put his hand in the
fire! If he does that—
Like fire and ice
merged
for that
pain
No problem
My lost friends, my father’s spirit
I've gained power, but this pain is gentle
This smile broke before, you're a sloppy person
“I was only trying to be friendly!”
Omelo, kill me
You threw me away and taught me the best, so I'll pour in the bargain sale in front of the meaning of selling you
Yes, I did it. I knocked my hand down. That's wrong.
It's a little rough, but it's a good hand
緊弱緊弱
Sasasa, no no
It's so tense, but it's actually deceiving you
JoJo
Now you too will come to me, and death will resonate with you
You ran away from humans
What's not making me spill right now?
This year just hit me
I have surpassed humanity
I can't keep up with you guys
I'm already curious, girl
If there is a picture of the day of death,
Stop that heart
Let's do it. Inlencer grows.
(In 1888 on December the 4th)
If you say that, you can just run away
Like right here
There was a small incident
(That little village, there was
a missing persons incident)
A very bizarre case
The place where I escaped
This very night
There are already people who have disappeared
(In 1888 on December the 15th)
Men were seen burning clothing
Yagaragaragaragara
Yagaragaragara
It seemed to be a stone mask
I'll make anything happen
Roughly
Megan
The meaning of our relationship has been stripped away
Yep.
Until I sip you
Osnagel's
My wife is tall
Huh?
That's why
Best of wishes!
Pokentique!
Waking up!
This Tio
still
Happy honeymoon!
America, how nice!
I wanna go there too,
And try to dig up some oil for myself!
That's disgusting!
Yo
Simple!
Simple squid
Inezy!
AEG!
Bissenmart Force
London Cress Article
small incidents
Sowing Knights Lord
Let my hand always be in yours
The Efrazy Case
Such a worrying incident
713 people
The person who disappeared
And then Kotzen disappeared
But the groans I heard coming from
No one yet
Not found
D.A.D.
D.S.M.R.F.D.
Wind Knights Lord Article
Well, let’s go and eat!
The day after the incident
Running under
Men burning down the district
Jonathan?
It was repeated so much
The screen of the day
AEG!
Sempraridasekaamshakoland
Welcome
At night
Up and down
second-mover
Female Female
The insertion
Married
The other person is
Pendrcon species
I have lured him here.
Einar Pendrkon
Philisarnasilas
Have you come?
Heading to America in the beginning of the month
Sirisana Sirus
Joster-san
Both of them
push up
I am
Always Hey Prussie
At this time
I can hide my hands anywhere
It's a ball
Harnem
Miya did sign language
That’s because I’ve realised something!
Someday I will too
Try guessing students in America!
Shhhh!
And you’re the reason why...
The world has slipped from my grasp!
Be enough for you?
Are one and the same in this world!
You and I...
How about it?
I'm happy you're here
This is the start of my mythos
Now, let's go to the craftsman
Intruder
Oh no, the guest has returned.
Erina! Not you too!
This ark is swarming with his followers!
【伝ir】
Shall we torture him to death?!
Wang Chan!
Here you go,
JoJo
Therefore I will split this stone in pieces before you.
I’ll take you as my own
Because I realized that
I’ll tie our futures together
There's no relationship more calculated than ours
I got this power because of you
Because you were there
I don't have it all
How far are you?
I felt it tear. Something
important inside me just tore
I will burn with you
JoJo
Because we are one
Please try, try, try, try
Everything is connected
There’s a meaning to it all!
No, John
Just like my mother
died for me, I’ll—
Only you
When the spirits scatter
If you do that
Elemental Creation
Only this child
My mythos begins here
Can you get the dial?
nevertheless
All people
JoJo!
fun
Need
Not given
That neck
Right next to the iron steps
Inaccuracy
I know what you’re like...
Long time
John
You
I figured...
My
This child
JoJo?
all
Dose
Dead...
Something inside me snapped, something decisive
Chomazo!
This is it!
Run away
Chocho
Until I burn with you
Until everything disappears
Flames run, everything is connected
Live for me
All live
But this fateful adventure
Will become an inheritance
His golden spirit
(Phantom Blood)
Sell ​​happily and live
But now something has snapped
Until you don't need it yet
Okay then
It's about you
Keep looking at the stars
I thought it would come
Speak
Talk to me
This guy
Dead
His noble life
(We’ll stop the flow of time)
(Even when the world resets)
Dead
(This bizarre adventure)
Of course,
Something in my eyes
Two in One
Feeling the friendship of a dog
That's right
Without you
Because you were there
something
Now I
want
Find
To your favorite destiny
Beautiful Mikade
In the stars
I drink
The two
That fate
It was terrible
Another breast
Quietly unknown
One saw the stars
Tour
Is it polar?
pick up the station
my frightenedzz
Speedwagon is so cool!
Yuishie, Yoishie!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuisi, Yuisi!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuisi, Yuisi!
The best thing about this park was that the smiles of all the customers were the biggest smiles. I felt that very strongly at the park.
I was truly happy that such a miraculous park had been able to survive to the very end.
Thank you for watching.
Now, Mr. Kong, please.
Great staff, great cast.
Then they brought the outbreak to the theater.
I'm glad to meet everyone who has watched the video.
I easily overcame the progression.
The players were able to go home after today's academy.
I'm happy for people.
I let it happen.
thank you.
And I was struggling as a single person.
My son!
That's amazing!
I'm so happy!
It's great.
thank you.
Then, I received the greeting I just mentioned.
Thank you for watching.
thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Everyone, please check out Fauci's Prround Funding.
thank you.
please.
Everyone, you all were wonderful.
It was wonderful.
See you at the theater from there.
Thank you very much.
He doesn't even know!
He doesn't know either.
MAMORU: It’s already over.
yes.
It was a huge hurdle.
I'm not sure if I can speak well,
This is Elina Tendul and her character Shimis Misha.
Thank you very much for coming to the audience today.
And thank you to everyone who watched the stream.
What should I say?
I was able to reach this great war retreat,
The strength of each and every cast member,
With the staff and
For supporting this work,
I think it's all thanks to you all.
Please do, everyone.
Please look at the stars, everyone.
So please have a great war.
yes.
It's your job to burn the speeder!
It was my first experience and it was really difficult for me.
But really.
It was really hard, but
Already, somehow,
To get support,
Thanks,
It was really hard, but
Already, somehow,
To get support,
Like supporting them,
Supporting each other,
Those words truly mean,
It just seemed to enter my body.
It's a really wonderful place,
Thanks to that,
I was able to cut it thickly.
So, I have nothing but the best to say,
With everyone here on stage,
As Kochi-san also said,
Not at all.
Although he's not here now,
The staff who helped me create it,
and,
This role,
For five months,
I really put it together,
I want to make it a treasure in my life.
Love women,
Thank you for taking an interest in Speedwagon again.
Including everyone who loves me,
Really,
thank you very much!
Shirae-san...
Good job, Dig putting is burning well.
I certainly understand.
Honchitsu,
To Sepulija,
RPM improved office
Wang's school committee came to the event.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you very much.
Really,
The first thought is,
There were a lot of different things that happened.
The two of them, Shotaro, and now, here
The one who finished the tree, and another Teperi,
Hiro-kun and I accomplished so much on our own.
Mom, this company is a one-lens camera for people.
With the determination to align
I came here with the aim of becoming a teacher of Wang's music.
Really, without anyone calling
Of course, I'm really grateful that I've come this far.
Medical support from staff
It is the result of your efforts.
Every single stage, really
I just want to omit it.
The applause of the Baraline and 5000 yen are us
Now the cast is
The truth is, it's your Hamon energy.
How much courage it gave us
I think that's what we really feel.
I was really close to Hantoshi and Okabetsu right now.
It really is like a family
It means that today will be a valley from tomorrow onwards.
Hey hey
Annie
A little Syriaria please
Just a little bit
I feel lonely though
I really love myself
This woman's world
And with these beloved members
In this theater
Being able to breathe the same air
That's right.
The one who touched everyone's hearts was
I have become a treasure too
I am proud to have been able to do this with you all.
Thank you so much everyone
thank you
It will end again
Blatzer
Please watch
I changed my boss's environment.
Another ironworker
Thank you for today
It's totally free
So many
As you have written earlier,
Right from here on
As in the title above
It was a strange adventure.
There are so many people like you.
Only the curtain of Hara
Born at the Imperial Theatre
The Imperial Theatre
The current theater is closing.
As a final review
By producing
Not Minami
Memories
Participated
My friends are cast members here.
It is staff
And the original author
The main cast members
And here are the books.
After five years of work
Apparently it was rewritten 17 times.
It was in this flow that I was born.
This work
Being accepted by everyone like this
Like this
Many musicals
We have some works from overseas.
Such works are
Zahiozic Zero is
On Broadway and in the West End
That's what we're here for
In books
While making large replicas
Let's fight
Japanese style
We provide information.
This work is
What you all saw
Exactly
From zero to one
Became Zahiozic
I think it's a work of art.
This work
Someday again
Inherited
It may be a big performance,
This Zahiozik
I was at Zero 1
The friends here
Really I
It's just for the time being.
Zayn
I feel like a son or daughter to you.
Only one person was different
Since they share the same father
One as a father
Mud and Stars
University
A work ticket
As a friend
from now on
At the Shibutoku Musical
I want to survive
Truly amazing
Two sons
Like this
I can have it
A little bit today
You might be watching from anywhere
Also serving
As a son
Nice to meet you
Truly amazing
Yesterday
As a father
I was able to participate
Hello everyone
If you have any worries
Finally
What is it?
Within myself
It's all connected
That it all has meaning
a little bit
If you think so
surely
Beyond that
There is light
There are stars
If you think so
I think it's that kind of work.
thank you
Well then
I will do my best
Where should I start?
Already
But anyway
I'm glad we met
Hotz
We
Entertainment and
I'm trying not to
Sometimes after all
There are times when it's difficult
There are times when it's scary
but
The Minister just said
As you said
Something
In the purely literal sense
Don't do it right away
In the truest sense
Do it now
That's what it means
I am this
I felt it at Campari.
of course
A lot of things happened
Something like that
Only in those words
I might not be able to tell you right now, but
And more
I
now
As a treasure
I was able to have
Above all
It
so
lots of
To humans
That you can enjoy it
After all, it's ours
It's the happiest thing
It
With this member
It can be closed on paper
I am happy
Women
Giant player fun
I welcomed
My father just now
As you said
We will continue to do so
Look forward
Surely soon
Each on their own path
Various expressions
I think I'll pursue it
Not yet
It will be useful
Dad too
Let's definitely meet again
and
Also this woman
I think it would be a good story if we could meet.
It's all connected
I dream of such a day
Today is really
To everyone
I want to express my gratitude
everyone
thank you
amazing
I'll say something good.
I think Bappy will decide.
thank you
Woman
I pushed the woman down.
This is Arisa Shotaro
everyone
Really
Those who noticed
I don't know, but
I
Because I'm this kind of person
Even if I stand in the middle
After all, everyone
Many people
For holding me and supporting me
already
Warm
Someone like my older brother
He was already a family man
People like
Because that's fine for you
You can go with that humanity
Just those words are enough
I really have come this far
But still
When I look around,
After all, this time everyone
After all
Cress
I've seen your face after all
Really everyone
too
After all, the curtain won't open
There were many things that caused me anxiety.
I think there is.
That voice also reached me
It arrived directly after all
However, I also received a lot of criticism from the people around me.
What's going on?
Ride and enjoy
There are various messages
I saw the power of seeing.
just
I
I really believe in everyone
I'm working hard here
Because I've been watching everyone
Watch it.
Feelings
I just want you to wear it
That's really the only feeling
Not
Together
There are so many different
Overcoming a big wall
already
Even if the conversation doesn't change
Invisible
It's a bond
That's already the case
Don don don don
That means we're connected
I've been feeling this trend for a long time now
After all
Makuha is open
Jonah Joshi's
What is the other Yuya-san?
Really
We've talked about a lot of things up until today
Yesterday's Yuya's war loss
Watching Hiro's wartime success
After all,
There was today
One more
I feel like I've really completed it.
I got into the mood.
I've seen some really amazing things
on second thoughts
I'm glad I worked hard
Really already
As of yesterday, I felt
So today, everyone
so
I can see that face in Chi-up
Really I
With a heartfelt joy
There are lots
As it was at the beginning
I
I think it's a historic evolution.
To the world
Really already
We all worked hard to create it
already
This guy
This guy gave it to me in the field.
Together
I want to keep up
already
try as hard as one can
Climb, climb, climb, climb up the mountain
today
Really
I think I was able to make everyone happy.
Thank you so much
Me too
Really
I spoke without thinking
Maybe
no
That's not true
Some people may think that
This is definitely
already
It's my feelings
Campari's feelings
I
today
It may be a mistake
I think I've made everyone happy already.
It's okay to think that
Me too
where
Everyone did their best.
everyone
thank you
I
To dry this
Also
I hope that I will be able to meet you all in person soon. I also hope that this work will continue to remain not only in Japan, but all over the world.
I want to teach with big dreams.
Thank you very much.
So, I hope to finish it again soon, and thank you for watching today.
Thank you for watching.
Everyone, everyone and a little bit of everyone.
Because there are a lot of things going on.
Thank you everyone!
Thank you for watching.
Artwork
Gabies
。
I love you