This is already on the screen.
It's okay to talk
Yeah
Are you okay
It's okay
You are watching this
yes
It's you guys
You have been chosen
I decided it was worth believing.
I have this record
I leave my will to those who will inherit it.
From now on I
Heading to the ruins in Mexico
49 years
Time that had stopped has started to move again
It has started moving
That's why now
This record must be kept.
If something happens to me in the future
no
Let's get back to the topic
As you all know,
This foundation is for the benefit of humanity.
Pharmacy
High school studies, etc.
It was established with the aim of providing support in a variety of fields.
On the surface
On the surface,
Please listen carefully
I founded this foundation here in the United States and have branches all over the world.
It's to pursue the secret of something.
What is that something?
Stone Mask
The Foundation's true purpose is to uncover the secrets of the Stone Mask.
And today, I'm recording the story of the mask.
And the story of the golden spirit that was there
So that you can inherit it.
It began in the 16th century
tribes of the central plateau of Mexico
The husband of the sun who speaks the voice of time
Founded by a tribe of Ahtecs
I have the power of life, eternal power, eternal life in my hands.
TRUE
What will become life next? I suck the blood of life, and life is power in my hands.
We are children of the sun
Afteca
was disliked
But one day the tribe suddenly disappeared.
All of this mystery lies in the Stone Mask
This story is about the Stone Mask
The strange fate of two boys and their adventure begins.
To do this, first
Speaking from the outskirts of London
Watcher
Ouch, the rain is on my heart
I need to dry it quickly.
I'll warm you up, Hey Kelly
I won't sleep until the morning today
You're really cute
Wait a minute, what's that?
Isn't that Basa?
No one has gathered yet. No one has come.
Okay, I'll be the first one there.
wait a minute
Hey, I don't want to get involved with you, sir.
What are you selling, rich Basa, aristocrat.
I'm going to find some treasure.
This guy is an instant death
It's a beautiful necklace, I'll take it.
There must be something good in this box
What is this, your evil mask, I don't need this
My husband is pregnant and the baby is alive.
Baby, I don't want to get involved with that
Find something valuable, something valuable
Don't have a nice ring?
What are you doing?
A person's misfortune is
It's about making someone happy
Look, find it
Kachulke
Good faction
Aren't you a good guy?
This guy sells for more than the stab shop.
The one who bites the stab is a nobleman, this guy is also a nobleman
Nothing wrong
Look, find it
Let's start with the top leaves
Did you release me?
My wife and son
His wife had already passed away
The baby is safe
baby
I helped
Is this fate?
I want to thank you for saving my life
My name is Joestar
I will never forget this kindness
It's not worth mentioning, but
brand
ah
Who is it?
Brand Tower Jazz
Time passed and in 1880
The time was filled with enthusiasm
A fierce storm
Burning with desire
The times fill
Now is the time
Grab the money in your hands
Time to leave
The base of the castle is also high
Open the horizon
Still in the Darkness
Crawl
Fill it up
To stop the hand
A voice, a familiar voice
here we go
He looked like he was going to ask me who I was
Let me introduce you to something you've never heard of.
Speed ​​is voice
Tell this story
Immediately
While leaving it loud
I'll tell you too
In the suite
This country now
This very era
What's happening
I'll teach you
This country now
It's exactly this era
Let the sound tell you the speed
Time is accelerating
Becoming stronger
Don't get dropped
of social revolution
The lights come on
I have hope
Let the light burn, let the light burn today too
Everyone comes to pray in the dark night
I need to be aware of that weakness
Between the light and darkness!
The front and back are separating
Challenge the world, grab the Setomi
A new era emerges for steam railways
Improving the World Freight Blitz
Four endless flashpoints
Social Structure Flight-in
Pollen: The Hands that Marked the Era
This festival of public opinion and darkness
Human Festival God Festival
Everyone's coming to the dark night festival
I need to be aware of that weakness
(Midnight blue darkness)
The front and back are separating
Challenge the world, grab the Setomi
A new era emerges for steam railways
Light Light Darkness
The front and back are separating
Light
grab
Wait!
I'll kill you!
what?
Ah, you damn brat!
Please wait!
Ah, shit!
Wow, I'm a brat!
Hey, what do you do?
hey hey!
Hey, there he is!
Kemeonela!
nice!
Stupid brat!
Tell me!
If I do something bad, tell me!
Do you understand?
This disgusting SEGA!
Fuck!
What are you looking at?
You idiot!
Hey!
Disgusting!
How's your dad doing?
I haven't seen it since the bar went bust!
Damn, you're dead!
I said it because it was trendy and sweet.
Your mamma is
It was Jodaba!
I wish I'd offered that woman for sale to you!
Oi!
Dio!
Can't you hear me?
What is it, Dad?
Is it medicine?
I don't need medicine
I have something important to tell you, come here
Dio
I've known for a long time
Memories after I die
It's all about you, my only son.
So
This, this, accept
Give
Joestar
He's an aristocrat.
Moreover, Osotoyoshino
He owes me a debt of gratitude.
Okay?
When I die, send that letter.
Go to that guy
They take care of me.
I'll be back at school
That's good.
Cut it properly and stick it on.
Dad
Are you acting like a father now?
Listen, Dio
You are smart.
I won't lose to anyone
Become the richest
Dio!
How about girls?
Ask yourself
It keeps getting stolen
I see
Of losers
Shake hands
It's hell now
Nausea
Still, my mother
Be noble
Let go of your pride
He hugged me
Hey Dio
Look up at the stars
My mother keeps saying that
died of illness
easily
There's nothing in general
Not only will it be stolen
What a star
Do you have it?
Is that sky blue?
Nacho Star
Ugly, terrible father, loser, always a loser
Under this murky sky, I continued to struggle and die
Let's receive our inheritance now, it's all from our parents, let's go on a journey
I still have nothing in my hands, so let's start from here
Joestar, you have the sun in the sky
That's right, Joestar
Your family is a doctor, but they're making money
Your father is a good doctor
What do you think?
But it's an expensive hat
Stop it, your mother gave it to you for your birthday.
Stop
What are you doing?
Just because you're in front of a girl, you're trying to act cool
Hey, do you know who this is?
If it was Jona from the Joestar family, he would be more ruthless.
After all, this guy is Jona of the Joestar family.
The rich aristocrats shouldn't just stand there and act all high and mighty.
what?
Hey, let's go
Um, are you okay?
Leave me alone
but
I did it because I wanted to, not to be thanked by you.
I'm aiming for true sincerity. You were a girl and I was having trouble with you, so I just stood up to you.
Someday I'll be able to win
Okay, let's go
Jonathan Joestar
Jonathan Joestar...
Let’s go, Danny!
you
You're Dio Brando!
So you're Jonathan Joestar?
Everyone calls me Chocho!
Looking forward to working with you.
Let me introduce you to my friend Danny.
It's a very useful shape.
It won't bite so it's okay.
friend?
Danny!
What are you doing? I won't forgive you!
I've been waiting for you, Diobrando.
Jonathan Joestar?
Come in. This is the mansion where you will be living from today onwards.
What's up, JoJo?
You must be tired from traveling all the way from London, Dio.
From today onwards, you are part of our family. Please live your life just like our son, Jojo.
Yes, I am grateful for Lord Joestar's actions.
Hehehehe.
Brand, this is Inspector Archer.
Police? Did something happen?
Yes, no, I've known Lord Joestar for a long time.
I heard Danny crying earlier.
It came over suddenly, so the teacher was surprised and it ended up hitting my leg.
Danny is an excellent watchdog for the Joestar family.
He’s a friendly creature, but
I’m sorry he surprised you.
JoJo, enough about Danny.
yes.
JoJo has lost his mother too—
and you both are the same age!
Please get along well with each other.
Now, let me show you to your room.
Mr. Brand.
Hehehehe.
nice to meet you!
Hehehehehehehehehe.
See you, JoJo.
Yeah.
So this is me.
Gearsk!
Don't touch my bag.
I'll try to carry it
結構
Your hands are sticky with dog drool
Sorry
I don't want you to touch me.
Ta-ta, JoJo!
Let me start by saying
I like number one the most
I won't let anyone act intimidating in front of me.
I was just trying to carry it for—
What are you both doing?
And one more thing—
I hate dogs.
The attitude of those who fawn over humans
The insects are running
Don't let that stupid dog get close to me
Sir Josser
i am coming
thus
The two boys meet
The two of them begin their youth
Also
Here comes JoJo
Dioc
Is that okay?
We are
As a highly respected aristocrat
real
Gentlemen
Make your goal your mission
for that
I have to learn
Take care of yourself
You have to be smart
Logic
Terrified
To not lose
Under the guidance of
the goddess of familial love
Whatever happens
To reign
Those born together
JoJo
Same again
I was wrong.
How many times has this happened?
This is the sixth time.
All uses are correct
I liked reading books
This much
Still looking good
Even though I haven't learned it yet
Is that okay?
We are
As a proud aristocrat
real
Gentlemen
And maybe
Be quiet
Stretch your vagina
beautifully
Supple
It's always
beautifully
Don't forget
Under the guidance of
the goddess of familial love
Whatever happens
To be loved
As a proud aristocrat
Harmful information
JoJo
nevertheless
Is it sincere?
Use of oneself
graceful
ironware
The perfect supporter
Put away the girl's dishes
It's okay to eat
No meals
Use
Follow their example
I
Embarrassing
You
I was spoiled
Such
My mother prepared it for me.
I always tried to correct my preaching.
You see, we are nobles of high birth.
Always question philosophy and truth in your mind
There are two knights in English folklore.
One day, their master was
taken prisoner by the enemy.
The enemy was afraid of the
two knights, who had great power.
“If you two will be executed in her place,
I will guarantee the life of your master.”
{\ Original: If you are executed in his place, the Lord's life will be guaranteed.}
Here's the problem for both of you
yes
Those two knights who gave themselves
up as prisoners to save their master;
{\ Original: Two knights sacrificed themselves to save their master and were taken prisoner.}
Is what you see beyond the prison bars the mud in front of you?
Or was it the stars shining above them?
What do you think?
Or the mud?
I think I saw mud
Why do you think so?
In the end, they had no choice
but to die for their master.
If you're dead, you can't accomplish anything.
So no matter how many plans I had, I felt I had to live and do something.
They were looking at the stars!
You lived your life to the fullest, and your two noble names will be engraved in history.
So
How you lived, how things happened, cherish that
I think they should have stayed
alive and done something!
That soul-dissolving powerlessness
What they saw was the mud!
They teach us lessons about what we can do with our lives.
They were proud to the end, they were looking at the stars
I think it teaches us how to live our lives.
You are an aristocrat, you have what you have, you live by taking it.
So isn’t it your responsibility to think
about what you’ll achieve with your life?
{\ Original: So, in order to fulfill that responsibility, shouldn't we think about what we can accomplish with our lives?}
I
There’s no right answer to this question.
Is that okay?
People live in the silence of fate, so they reach out their hands
Are you seeing stars or mud? Call both justice.
I stepped in next to him, the winner is Choma-san, Choma-san, the new champion!
Ta-da! I trained with Danny!
Now, who will be the next to
challenge our champion, JoJo?
A new face has just asked to join our game.
His name is Dio Brando!
How about getting to know your new friends by getting them involved in our games?
Alright, let’s do it!
The rule is if you get
hit in the face once, you—
{\ Original: The rule is that if you get hit by the cross section even once, you lose!}
If this is the rule, I'll throw it away if I do it in London!
Gong down!
Go, Jar Jarz!
Yay!
What a movement!
I've never seen that before!
Wow, Charger!
Can't get through!
perfection!
I got in!
Charger!
Can't get through!
What a wonderful opportunity!
Dio! Dio! Dio! Dio!
Everyone, Mina
I think my finger went in his eye.
I lost because of a foul.
I'm sorry I'm late today
Dio was amazing!
How do you do that move?
everyone
It hurts
Danny...
For some reason, Dio is trying to trap me.
It feels like he’s invading my life.
Hey, Danny, my heart aches
I'm full of anxiety
What if I were to die today?
Will everyone cry?
You're always warm
Thank you for staying by my side!
If mum were still here,
would it feel this way?
Is this how you loved me?
You're a little
My handkerchief
Oi! Thanks for bringing
my handkerchief back!
Hey, I’ll be back here tomorrow too,
If you'd like, come too.
Danny!
Are you curious?
Please excuse me for
grabbing it without permission.
It doesn't matter, the stone mask was apparently excavated from an archaeological site in Mexico.
Mexico...
We bought it from a London art dealer,
around the time JoJo was born.
On the way back,
we had a carriage accident.
That was the time your dear
father saved us, you know.
Are you interested in it?
In particular
JoJo is always out playing
with Danny, isn’t he?
Danny has a friendship and trust for Jojo.
Do you have a friend dog?
I had bought Danny when JoJo was young.
At first, he was afraid
of unfamiliar people,
And he didn’t get on well with JoJo yet.
But one time, JoJo was drowning in a river.
My voice is all alone and no one can hear it
Just as she was about to die, a shadow heard her scream and jumped into the river. It was Danny.
He dove in and saved JoJo’s life.
Danny's courageous actions, knowing what life is
Young JoJo was moved by Danny’s bravery.
They are best friends.
Is that so?
Husband
Eh? Ah, that’s right.
親友
Erina!
JoJo!
The two were reunited
love
Love! That wonderful curiosity
that guided JoJo’s actions.
Immediately the two
I fell in love
Danny!
Come boy!
You're so smart
You have to separate the core properly before eating it.
Hey JoJo, what are you carving over there?
Huh? It’s nothing.
What are you hiding?
It's so boring
When you say it like that, it makes
me want to see it even more!
People will laugh
I won’t laugh.
You’ll tell people!
I won’t tell, so show me!
No.
JoJo!
Elna
Just call
Feelings
Rest in peace
What kind of music
To that sound
I'm falling in love
What's going well
To be laughing like this
Vivid River Pool
The sky gets higher
Elna
Joe John
The joy of being there
The clouds are proud
The clouds are proud, and
the wind’s a little sweet
Joe John
Elna
I'm short of words
For these ever overflowing feelings
forever
One word: I'm happy
I want to hear
With your voice
This is ticklish
you
Bad person
I don't know
I'm being asked by you
So give me a reason
The reason for the two of us
Hands and
My hand,
Unable to connect, we are lost
Continues into tomorrow
This little courage
Trembling Heart
People who get excited
attract
Pale
question
It’s already this late!
Because a customer is coming today
I need to hurry back.
Erina!
I’ll see you tomorrow!
Joe John
Strongly attracted
That name of yours
Jonathan Joestar
You’re Erina Pendleton, right?
or
It's Erina Pendleton
Today is
Apparently he and Jojo were playing together
that
something
ray
He did it!
As expected of Dion
What we can't do
Do it calmly
I'm numb there
Admire
Have you kissed JoJo yet?
Not yet
The first person you kissed wasn’t JoJo...
This is Dio
What does it mean if you're a lady?
You understand, right?
This guy
This woman
What are you doing washing
my kiss away with mud?!
Are you stupid?
What’re you sleeping for?
Why did they give me alcohol?
Who do you think puts
food on the table? Stupid bitch!
This idiot
Hey, now go buy some booze!
Mom and Dad are a little unwell
What are you pretending to be sick for?
Oi, you hear me?
Dad, stop it.
Mom
I’m sorry! Please forgive me!
It's food, I can't take it anymore
I was abandoned by the moon
I'm a useless guy
If push comes to shove, I'll need you to work too.
Wake up
I'm counting on you
-Stop it, Father!
Can’t you hear my voice?
My voice
The voice calling for you?
You buy the alcohol
I already have money
what
Will you rebel?
You can make this much money too
Please, leave some money
for medicine at least!
There's a lot of flesh and blood
How proud do you think I am to work?
This stupid
This guy is making fun of everyone, really.
With the money I had taken from that nobleman
Yes, he's good at it.
Why don’t I send him a letter...
different
I am
With you
Dio
Dio!!
Why?
Why is this happening?
Hurt her
Who am I?
What did you do?
Why?
Dio
You are amazing
Much more than me
I respect that.
But in my heart
One thing is for sure
There is something burning
Dio!
People's names are very passionate
I won't forgive you
I heard that
My love
About me etc.
I don't care
Stand up to it
Even if we can't beat each other
I can't lose
Emotions
Dominate
Not like him
Trembling Heart
Her Honor
Get it back
Dio
fair and square
smash
I'll make you understand
New power
It comes up
It feels so good!
This heart
You gave me
Dio!
You
Until I cry
Hit
Throwing money
How dare you
Towards me
Dirty
This idiot
Like this
To someone who seems to win
This me
This Dio
Like this
To a scumbag
This me
This Dio
What on earth is going on?!
Both of you, go back to the punishment room!
Dio...
Your stupid kiss worked better than expected!
…
How miserable and painful,
This is the first time I've ever felt this way!
Erina!
Elina,
Erina! Did you say goodbye
to all your friends?
Yes, Father.
I'm sorry, but it's due to my work schedule.
With all due respect...
Let’s go.
I’ll make friends over there too.
I gradually began to look down on them.
His explosive power...
That mental strength.
If we don't grow more,
So that we can be proud of our sincerity,
If you don't control your mind more calmly,
To get it all.
But...
What’s that noise?
Is there someone in the depolarizing furnace?
Are they trying to get out?!
No!
Oh my god...
Someone! Someone please help!
Then Perseverance, times changed,
Riding behind Bistorias,
Population increasing to
the point of overflowing
The praise showered on the arts and entertainment,
In a flow that no one can stop,
Turbulent and dissolving development,
The pinnacle of British culture
After the summit, it's downhill,
Top runner,
human history,
After that it's downhill,
Top runner,
The judge will be counted,
Rondo piece with index finger,
The port's days are filled with new and old,
A map of London with great ideas,
Just like the current state of the country
Focusing on the darkness,
The swaying curtains of Galta,
Portobello,
A new market.
Is that correct?
The one excavated from Mexico?
I think it was Mexico
It was quite a while ago...
Until you clarify!
Yay!
But you're right, sir.
Some gentleman’s wife
fell in love with it,
And bought it from me at a high price—
Okay, done.
We did it.
Now, where could I find this gentleman—
That seems a little suspicious.
Who the hell are you anyway?
That's rude.
My name is Sephiri.
It's a danshaku.
I came from Italy to
find the Stone Mask.
All the way from Italy?!
I think they said he was a northern aristocrat.
I'm just going to check the ledger,
Please wait.
Gratz.
Let me give you a bit of advice,
The sun will be setting soon.
It’s better if you don’t
go beyond that street.
It mists.
Thank you for watching.
I don't want to reach for my suit and fall towards the red
Beautiful and dirty mix together and the night drinks pile up
Abandoned by resignation, I lean close to you and shake your hand
This darkness is different from other countries
Something is wrong. People are swaying in the river and being carried away.
Give me a warmth Kisaki Jack
(Hate the poor, hate the
rich, and raise your voice)
Let's all gather here now, Jack.
In 1887, the Trafalda pair raised their voices in equality.
From afar, the rich look on and laugh at your profession and life
Accelerate steadily
Let's all gather here now, Jack.
In 1887, the Trafalda pair raised their voices, saying, "Your profession, your life,
Accelerate steadily
Let's all gather here now, Jack.
I got it! The one who snatched the fangs away was my most noble hero, Jonathan Joe Turner!
Full moon, spaceship, if public opinion falls, move forward into the future
Is it today? Where is it here? On top of which castle?
Will I really be able to live here? New memories exist here now
Look again someday, you'll see, you won't find
Now here, a full moon, a spaceship, if public opinion falls, move forward into the future
Is it today? Where is it here? On top of which castle? Move forward into the future
JoJo! Your pass won’t go to waste!
Try! We won the last game!
That was magnificent!
Thanks to your pass! Let's first tell Dad about this victory!
JoJo!
Can we write about your friendship
with JoJo for the school newspaper?
Thank you. Please go ahead and change and wait for me. Let's go home together.
Time passed like the
endless flow of water
Ever since you started
calling him “Father”
I think of that word
which is so familiar to me
Seven Years of Prefectural Production
You were beautiful and sincere
I straighten my collar, thinking of my friend
You regretted your mistake of not wearing your collar.
In place of Tani, you supported me
Ahead of me was your back
We walked this path
together for seven years
So why is it that I don’t
feel any friendship for you?
How are you feeling?
Just the wind has come this far
If this is taking so long, I'm getting old.
It's still today
Oh yeah, that's a big deal.
JoJo and Dio Brando, they...
Ah, Dio is a proper member
of the Joestar family now!
And JoJo has become
a splendid gentleman.
He submitted a brilliant thesis in the field of high school studies.
Dio graduated with the highest grades in law.
I respect you
Back then...
Husband
I just got home
Dio, welcome home
And Jojo too
Are you alright?
The seats don't stop
Today, the doctor recommended
I be admitted to hospital.
I'm against it.
Hospitals these days are all about making money.
They say it’s a problem in London too.
I feel safer at home.
I refused.
The trembling in your hands and the pain in your chest will go away.
Congratulations to both of you on your wins
You already know?
Inspector Archer here told me.
That's terrible, Inspector.
We wanted to see Father’s face light up...
Even though he came flying
Damn
Really big nose
I have such wonderful sons.
Especially you, Dio.
When you graduate, you can be whatever you want to be.
He gave me a chance even though I was born poor.
Thank you.
So, I'll leave it at that.
Inspector, thank you for always visiting.
With the appearance of Jack the Ripper, the world has become a dangerous place.
But this is Liverpool!
There are people everywhere who lack the sense of right and wrong like him.
Well then, excuse me.
…
It responds only to blood and operates with a precise mechanism.
Who on earth made this...
If we can solve this mystery, it might spark something new in the Japanese Language Society.
If that happens, then there must be some destiny for this stone that my mother bought.
Dario Brando?
I'm always sorry, Dio.
It's easy to give medicine
thank you
I don't want to get older
I am currently ill
“I’ll probably die.”
My heart hurts, my hands shake, and the stones won't stop.
Can’t you hear my voice?
The voice calling for you?
My mother died, and my father and I
Yes, whatever happens with that scum
I have endured
Yes, until the day finally came
He's dead, and the moon has abandoned us. Damn it.
Yeah, I'm gonna beat this guy up and drink now.
The only one
I threw that thing at you and trampled on you
I don’t bloody need it anymore!
My mother was killed by him, and everything was taken from her.
Can you endure it, Tia?
How hellish that your blood
is flowing through my veins
Punish this curse, take it all into your hands
Keep winning until the very end of humanity
Be prepared and take action
Wear a mask and become a brand, father
Sleep with the past in a perfect world
Get it
Tia
What happened to the medicine now?
What’s the matter, JoJo?
A letter from your father seven years ago.
The detailed document from your father's deathbed is here.
Wow
Let me see it.
My father and the girl are the same
You always brought medicine to my father.
What on earth are
you trying to say?!
Answer me
What on earth are you trying to say?
Give me the medicine back!
JoJo
To examine this drug
to doubt our friendship
Tia
I swear to you in all sincerity and on the honor of your father, Mr. Brand.
My own innocence
I’ll never speak of this again.
I swear to him
Tia
A vow
I swear
oath
I swear to you, Tia
Is there any honor in that lottery?
Give me back that medicine
Tia
I won't let you near my father anymore.
Changed to the core
We never had a friendship from the start
I will protect JoJo
It's a misunderstanding, JoJo
It's a misunderstanding
And
There's no evidence.
It's just a guess
yes
I hated my father
Above all, I was suspicious
I've become selfish
JoJo
What did you do, Tia?
no
It's okay
I can't pull anymore
A perfect world
Get it
Tia
father
What's going on, JoJo?
Speaking out loud like that
father
I'm going to London for a couple of days.
Meanwhile, the doctors I hired
I decided to provide perfect care.
Except from them
Please do not take this as medicine or tia.
but
Let me do what I want
I don't know why
I
I believe in my son
father
thank you
7 years ago
This guy
It reacted to my blood and activated
Use this guy
It was disguised as a research accident.
Hey, your research will kill you
The time limit is tight, so prepare yourself and take off
Looking up at the stars in search of a laxative
Aiming for the end of the world, East End of London
This place I followed is in the mud
Augustus Golito, where the plague comes
This place in front of me is the other side of the world
There's a reason we need to move forward
Even if you lose this right hand, look at the stars
It's finally time to choose
This is me and the smell
Who will come wading through the sea?
The me of that time
August Golito Devours Everything
Augustus Golito, the end of everything
I don't know what's come
There must have been something called "Shosan"
Kokosuku even devours it
We are the Augurs
It's no problem if you don't know the world
Just tell me a simple truth
Hey hey hey
My cousin's son
This knife is sharp
I'm not going to get into the costume.
If you tend to do that, you'll end up showing your innocence
I am Augustus Golito
It goes without saying that we are cheats
The have-nots take the haves
Life is an Auger
Even my heart was stolen
It seems like it would be safe if we ran away first
High Cattongaren
Augustus Gorrit
It can even take your life
I don't mind losing this finger
Augustus Gorrit
Our Imcrony
I have
You'll lose your fingers too
Yeah, maybe just one person
Augustus Gorrit
Proud of that resolve and deceive
I've been looking for Quornini
Don't bluff
Give the rich boy a try
Wilder Meow
I even blew my belly out
The mood is also aligned
I ended up in the wrong town
Handling my end
Countdown
3 2 1
This Speed ​​Burgon was allowed, why didn't he kick with all his might?
I came here for the sake of my father.
I thought you must have a father,
or mother, or siblings too.
{\ Original: That's why Kelsion thought you must have a father, mother, and siblings.}
I didn’t want to do anything
to cause your father grief.
I came here for your father.
That's why Kelsion thought you must have a father, mother, and siblings.
That's why Kelsion doesn't want to do anything that would cause your father grief.
Tell me your name.
Jora, Joestar.
Joestar-san, please name the person playing the German role.
Be careful. They're tricky. Hey, treat your wounds.
This Speed ​​Burgon will guide you to Minsei.
Why?
I like you.
Foca Street
O man of resolve,
Continue taking a look
You who see the stars in your heart
O courageous one,
With a courageous heart
Light up the darkness
A complete cheers to Tsugatsugashin Sunland!
Cheers to this beloved destiny, this encounter!
Once the water is boiling, pour the water into the pot.
The water boiled.
Pour water into the water.
I can't help but drink alcohol
Can’t you hear my voice?
A voice calling you
Shut up and don't come out
You are the only one who can see the sun
Become the richest
The case is different between you and me
Where am I looking, Tanchiki?
Nyahaha are you listening to this?
A blue-blooded kid
What’re you mumbling about?!
Can't you hear my voice?
This idiot
There is no trace of the Heisei era
Just Flosier from GG
This idiot
Your help is
Human voice
I'll kill you
A voice calling someone
It's an interesting machine
Hey you idiot
It's in my arms
Human experimentation
JoeJoe
I'll solve your research
What
What is this light?
Hallucination?
Dead
If you get stabbed in the head with this much force, it's only natural that you'll die instantly.
It's an ancient instrument of torture and murder.
Not dead
Hiba, what is this guy?
Too angry
Murder Chronicles Kazakhstan
I'm tired of thinking
not good
We can fight
I hate that the sun I see is the last one I see!
Thank you.
Did the sunlight turn it to ash?
ah…
Ugh...
Ah...
Hahaha...
Damn...
This is...
The power of the Stone Mask...
So Dio...
He hasn't returned from the liquor store yet.
Quickly chase after them...
Please use the room
thank you
Hey!
Ah...
Take that Oriental, Wyche!
yes!
Hahahaha...
long…
Sorry...
This is my fault...
picture?
I…
If only he'd stayed at Lutow's house...
Dio's father, Dario Brando...
That is what I mean.
I'll tell you
It's a story from when you were a baby
Yes, this is my ring
But no theft report was filed.
A man was arrested for trying to put a ring into the seventh
The ring was given to Sir Joster when he was betrothed to his wife.
It was clear that this was a special pairing.
Yes, this is the ring I made with my wife.
Did you remember your wife today?
He had tears in his eyes.
I have caught the culprit
Would you like to see me?
Stealing something from a nobleman is a serious crime
The punishment for fighting is certain.
Got it
Hey, hey
Don't complain, Brand.
Mr. Brando,
Oh no, then
Dario Brando is no lifesaver or anything.
He's just a thief
Sir Joster knew that.
He adopted Dio.
Why?
I am moved to tears by the words and actions that followed today.
Didn't he say this to you?
This ring was given to me
Yes, I said
Uh, yeah
It's not a lie
This is what I gave to him
He is innocent
It's one half of your wife.
Brand-san
yes
This is yours
Please give this ring to me and buy something for your family.
Lord Joster, why did you do that?
If I were suffering in poverty
I would have done the same
Yes, for the ones I love
For the ones I love
The stars in the sky are attracted to each other
Soon, like a myth
This light will clear the darkness
Let us pray
thank you
You are too kind
This villain is laughing inside
Maybe so
But think the other way around.
From the music of destiny, people reach out to the stars
Let's embrace that courage, that loneliness
Pain is all connected
Everything has meaning
I am prepared to believe in humanity.
If it falls, you can't see it, you see.
it is
Someday it will shine
Inherited and turned into gold
I'm ready to keep believing
Curse your fate
I'm waiting for D.
It can still be stopped
- Lyrics, composition, arrangement, lyrics, arrangement, composition, arrangement
- Lyrics, composition, arrangement, music composition, arrangement, arrangement
- I heard a strange rumor.
- Floscia's man,
- He reportedly broke the wall with his bare hands.
- And then the man, in the morning sun,
- It won't fit.
- It disappeared.
- It's the same as 30 years ago.
- Just like back then.
- In the wilderness of memory,
- A smashed grass fire.
- That sunrise over the Atlantic Ocean
- It was blood red.
- Full of passion,
- I'm fascinated by the world of roads.
- My respected father,
- Crossed the seven seas.
- Dear Father and Mother,
- To my youth.
The Stone Mask...
- They took it all away.
- Vowed vengeance,
- To get it back,
- Tomorrow for sure, tomorrow for sure.
- I think about it day in and day out,
-There's a saying that goes, "That's who he is."
- Stone Mask, if you let me find it,
- It will be irreversible.
- This hand,
- believe.
- Young girl.
- Did you come back from London?
- I got the deciphering material.
- Too bad, Dio.
- Really.
- You may not understand, but this is the truth.
- I understand, girl.
- That's the kind of guy you are.
- I know this is selfish, but I have a favor to ask.
- This is the last one.
- Can you give me some time?
- To the police,
- Time for independence.
- I,
- I regret my life.
- Born into a poor family,
- I got ambitious.
- I did something stupid.
- Sin,
- I was making amends.
- Don't believe it.
- His words.
- picture?
- Everyone has a dirty look on their face.
- Let me introduce myself.
- I'm Speed ​​Oagon, the busybody.
- I've been in the dark sea since I was born,
I've seen a lot of bad guys.
- So you can tell by the smell.
- This one's a habit.
- It smells like vore.
- This guy is born evil.
- Mr. Joestar, just hand it over roughly.
- We already have the evidence.
Dad, I heard the whole story.
I decide to rest in the bedroom
My son
I don't want to see him get caught. That guy won't get caught.
I was born with that fate
I get it, Jojo. You'll get arrested, but at least...
I want you to put handcuffs on me. We've been together for seven years.
Be careful why
Got it
I'll put the handcuffs on
Humans have limitations
I've figured it out
The more Oro blooms, the more
The limits of life
Hey JoJo, I'm so frustrated
There's nothing in these hands
The prison where I was imprisoned
Covered in mud
No matter how much I struggle, I can't see the stars
My eyes are closed
Do you understand that murky sky?
These hands are crushing me, they can't reach me
This beautiful blood that has been JoJo
Even after vomiting, this blood won't go away
So now is the time to break this cage
Catch the Stars
And I
Mother
Humans
I'm quitting
JoJo
throat
Okay.
Shoot
JoJo...
Hey, doctor, call a doctor
Dad, Dad
Gradually, this is my dead mother's ring. I'll be happy if I come.
Don't begrudge me the reason
Maybe being strict with you made you feel unfair.
Anyway
Not bad
Gradually, the end came in my son's arms.
Oh my god
It was definitely a mistake back then
When you die, everything
Damn it, Mr. Joestar
I was always told to be sincere.
Always proudly
I said I'd save you
I was told I believed
I'm powerless to have been unable to protect you
What is sincerity?
Dad, open your chest
What are you proud of?
What's the purpose
This Joestar blood
flowing through my body!
Always remained sincere
Be proud and understand yourself
Ready to cut through the dark wilderness
Look up at the stars and accept it all
Engrave this will in your mind
Be proud of your heart and shine golden
Let's become the future and send it to the stars
The Joestar blood that flows through my body
Everything is connected and everything has meaning
Resisting this fate and sadness
A single drop of courage
Police work is tough
what up
That's the corpse
Dio's body is missing
What?
Police Officer, get away from the window.
What's up with this guy?
I'm back to life
Even though I was shot so many times
Be careful
Someone has a weapon
No way
Dio!
stop
Shoot me
Don't help me
quickly
I don't know
Just what's happening now
Jaja
Can you hear me?
you
JoeJoe
I am
I have gained such great power
From Stone Mask
Your father's power
Do monsters create monsters?
Mr. Joestar!
That's how it works.
There's nothing we can do about that monster
How about it?
It's no wonder that God has lost some unknown ability from his brain.
So then
If you completely destroy the head
Stop it
Look!
more
It's stronger
Turon...
above ーーー!
Poor, poor!
Mr. Joestar!
Just a little longer, just a little longer, I'll enjoy this wonderful power.
I still don't know how far I can go!
JoeJoe
Oh, JoJo
Stop your pointless struggle
I told you!
The more you try to come up with a plan, the more you realize there are limitations to what humans can do.
Don't hide in the shadows of the curtains, come out
You too will become my life!
Dion! It's not strategy that will stop you, it's courage!
You can't defeat him this day, Speedwagon, you run from the mansion!
Joestar-san! Don't run away to the top!
The running flames illuminate the darkness
Come on up, Dion! I'm here.
Are you inviting me, JoJo? Okay, you go first.
Shining light on the running flames
I will end you, your power, here
It's no use, it's no use! Let's suck the life out of it
Flickering flames, don't let them fall!
Let's offer light to the other side!
After you gave me your power
Your back was always ahead of me
You were always on my back
My youth is with you
Settlement in this era
Jojo, the Joestar mansion burns down
Under the map, everything is lost
Burn everything except this life
I'll finish you
This is what Joestar must be thinking
The stronger the firepower, the more the monster's recovery power can't keep up.
More, more firepower
But the flames have reached the roof
Damn it, Mr. Joestar
Woolly
This body is immortal, you are the only one who will die.
How the goddess of Jillary shines
Give me loving judgment in your heart
I won't let go of this knife
You're closed off, it's a knife.
It's no use, I'm immortal
Jillary
The power of hell
The Goddess of Giving Love Sways in Flames
Apply equal force and justice
This isn't how it should be, the sacred goddess
The power of hell
Goddess of Giving Love
Can you hear me?
I can hear you
in front
I told you about the Astika people.
That is
It was a 13th-century mistake, not a 16th-century one.
Even though we are in a position where we must accurately tell the story,
I'm very sorry.
Someone also said
I don't want to get old
by the way
Did you take a proper break?
good
I am a storyteller
I have been a witness to many different human situations.
And I kept saying
I want all the acrylic stands
I completed it
Now
Shall we talk a little more?
The story so far seems a bit like a fairy tale
It's definitely a reality
And from here too
So strange.
At that time, the mansion was engulfed in flames and collapsed.
But Joestar was alive.
I beat Dion.
But I lost everything
after that
3 days
1 day
2 days
3 days
4th
5 days
6th
7th
8th
9th
10th
11th
12th
13th
14th
15th
16th
17th
18th
19th
20th
21st
22nd
23rd
24th
25th
27th
28th
29th
30th
31st
32nd
33rd
34th
35th
36th
37th
38 days
39 days
40 days
41 days
42 days
43 days
That's why I came!
Nursing is done well.
Please come back at a later date.
Are you okay?
Oh, wait a minute.
Sigh...
I am...
Huh...
…
I slept for three whole days straight.
Everyone in the mansion
Please stay calm now
We've passed the peak, but it's still a tough time.
I'm glad you're alive
You've been nursing me
you
No way
But they look similar
Who said we look alike?
To Elina Pendleton
picture?
It's been a while
Jonathan Joestar
Why?
This is my father's hospital
I moved to India seven years ago.
I recently returned to Japan.
It's really been a while
I was weak
I couldn't run to you
I was a young child.
I couldn't face you
That voice remains unchanged
These unchanging feelings
Vivid rebab
The sky gets higher
Elina Jojos
The joy of being there
The clouds are proud
The wind is a little sweet
Erina!
sorry
I relaxed and lost consciousness
With my broken arm
I'll always support you
Eye to eye
If you touch it, it's there
A little courage
Continues into tomorrow
Hand in hand
Touch and there
Fate comes into contact
forever
My heart is trembling now
overlap
Faintly attracted to each other
A continuation of that day
The two
destiny
yes
Meeting people is
Maybe it's decided by fate
Speedwagon is cool
Misunderstanding! Misunderstanding! Misunderstanding!
It's a misunderstanding!
Wait, it's the murderer
The method was the same woman's throat.
Slash
That belly is a face
Ammo is the worst
The identity of the synchronized person is completely unknown
I can't grasp the truth
I like you.
Don't walk outside at night
Like you
Performance
Ah, it's already this late, I have to go home quickly.
It's still this late
But Jack the Ripper might show up.
Scary
It's scary.
Now you're talking to him
picture?
I played late into the night and got depraved
Who is it?
I like you
Because I was seen
I feel no pain, I have nothing to fear
Now that I've been reborn, I'll start my life
If we don't heal the wounds, we need lives.
And the fulfilling game is weak
Don't you want power?
I will bestow power and pleasure.
Humans are bound by Zennartaga and fear great evil.
However, in rare cases, there are evil elites who have no Zennartagha.
Me, you, how about you come with me, Dio?
What do you know about me?
Bokarsachak, you must be angry.
A woman drowning in fun, a woman covered in happiness
Defeat more, fear no more
I will bestow power and pleasure.
Jack, no more worries, more pleasure in your hands
I have no fear
Bad Earth, how many times have I been zeroed out?
You come with me, Jack, Zalipa.
Take my hand, who are you?
Whether to look at the time or what to look at, there are enough words to
Welcome me, I can't reach you
I'm living my life, the sun is already gone
Cut out death Cut out death Cut out death Cut out death
This world
That stone gana
I want to believe that, like the others, I have become a powder keg.
I think so, yes
It's okay, it's okay
let's go
That
what happened?
Who is it?
I've been here for a while now
Jonathan Joestar
and Miss Elida Pendleton
BGM
I'm surprised I survived
Is that Ishikamen's power?
Ishikamen!
BGM
chance!
departure!
BGM
Ash
All Air
BGM
Not bad at all
Death
Are you getting worse?
BGM
What?
A compound fractured arm
BGM
No pain
I am Zeppeli bullet scale
Courage alone is not enough to win
Ishikamen's Power
I'm on your side
Breathing?
Breathing created that power?!
I'm on your side
It's Jola San Jose.
BGM
there is nothing
What did you do?
Why did you say my name?
Please ask your questions one at a time.
I'll show you the answer
Follow me
Then
Fate changes
Whether to accept
It's up to you
What happens next?
If this breathing occurs
Let me show you now
With a special breath
Special endorsement
The blood carries
The body burns the bifnech
Energy is generated
The name is
Hamon Energy
The power of Hamon is transmitted
This miracle happened
This is the power of Hamon
Breathing brings
The power of blood
Everyone has a blood flow
It gives you just a little bit of energy
Transporting nutrients
Regulating body temperature
Hamon's power is that small energy
Collected from the whole body
What makes this possible is
It's a rhythm of breathing.
Breathing is the power of now
Yes, the power of breathing
Yes I know
This breath, both inside and out
About the Stone Mask
And about you and Dio
Dio
The mask can only be worn by those who haven't changed.
Rio the Stone Masked Man
I still walk in the darkness
I travel the world
I followed the mask
To destroy
Dio is alive
If we don't fight
If you don't destroy it
Jamon in your hand
Otherwise
You and the world
Fate is in motion
I finally found it
What do you mean, Dio?
This fate
Everything is lifted up
That's it
supermarket
destiny
fight
That's my destiny
Me and Dio
The individual body of the Stone Mask
Unlocking the unknown power of your brain
Turning humans into vampires
it is
You must take blood energy from others.
On the other hand, Hamon's power
From your own bloodstream
To draw out energy
Front and back
Same energy
Yeah
In other words
To remove this jamon
What do you think I should do?
I'm starting to understand
Hamon. Hit them with another kind of hamon and they'll shatter.
And these energy waves have the same shape as sunlight.
The power to defeat Dio.
Yes. Time is running out. Learn how to turn courage into strength.
Jojo, Dio.
Eina, I can't get you involved.
I just want you to nod now.
I'll definitely come back to this place.
Is this the Hamon from JoJo?
…
The clouds flow, the wind leaves thoughts behind
go around
I nodded.
To your resolve
In sadness
Stars are drawn together
Guided by the destiny I love
Caught in the mud
I'm floating here
Left behind
Living the dream, waiting by the window
For whom is loneliness
Even if it doesn't reach
Even if you're not attracted to me now
I want to scream
To be me
You are attracted to each other
Always guided by fate
I weave the days together
Let's live
Looking up at the stars
To this place
You'll tell me someday
Stay proud
Accepting all of you
Destiny and Love
So that we can call it that
The stars are attracted to each other
Guided by the destiny I love
Wherever you are
I am me
Live on
Wang Chen, you're still alive?
yes
Ugh ugh ugh!
Ah!
Hahaha!
Haha!
Ha!
What is that power?
Haha!
No way, that Dio guy
SPEEEEEEEE!
Wagum!
You are,
I know too much about the Stone Mask's secrets.
It's Agarmaru!
Mr. Joestar!
You were looking too!
Because, because! Dio-sama said so!
I can lick your blood!
Lick? Lick? Lick? Lick! Lick! Lick!
Bello-san Joestar?
Be careful JoJo, he's got some serious power.
What's with this weird hat?
Grace
Let's eat!
Huh?
My arms... flames
My arm...
me
It was
I got a new life
Creating something that surpasses humanity
If it's important, it's not here
Or your body!
It's hot! What's this?
It's hot! It's hot!
Oh! Wait a minute!
Amazing, JoJo
You've mastered Hamon in such a short time.
what up?
JoJo
I lost my treasury
So I wanted power
But that
Not the same as Dio
To hurt someone
It is fundamentally different from the power that is obtained by stealing.
But it's the same power!
There is a proverb in the northern country of Norway:
The North Wind created the brave Viking
A harsh north wind blows
Because I know the pain
A Viking with timber frame was born
Not like them
You
I know the pain
pain
The pain of losing a friend
The pain of inheriting pride
The pain of the person you want to protect
Proof of Life
Listen to the pain
I was always told to be sincere.
Always following my father's lead
I still don't know if it's true sincerity
The Joestar's blood is hot and trembling
The daily routine surface is dyed in a glowing red darkness
That tragedy repeats itself
Holding this pain
Is it a matter of daily routine?
It was something I discovered by chance.
What?
A wedge driven into the wilderness of memory
Once upon a time, I crossed the seven seas with my father
Quiet Shore Night
That mask emits light
58 of his comrades were killed.
Severi
A masked man comes
It's the same as back then
At this time, the morning sun of salvation shone
It was my father
Illuminated by the red morning sun, my father disappeared
My watch stopped then
Holding this pain
I've been chasing
Don't repeat
Vow revenge
Don't make me sad
Tomorrow will shine
With pain
What you need
The courage to own the pain
and
Ready to shoulder the burden
JoJo
The thought
I haven't forgotten
yes
I believe in the power of this question.
let's go
【applause】
JoJo
Joestar
Aha
Dio
One
Where are you?
Ah, here it comes.
Otsuchi
Red Asahi
He won't splash blood on me.
a
Pacara
this
T-The horse!!
yes
crackle crackle
Seriously?
You're a horse too
crackle crackle
That guy
That guy should be Yama-chan, the researcher finally got a grip on him.
Yeah yo yo, I'm off to pay off the accumulated debts
Represent the underworld AK Speed ​​is a detailed investigation by agreement
I'll be your guide, I'll show you the 16-bar showtime
From London to the south, on the round land, we drove without rest in a carriage
I can see that I can go to the Imishie Toner
Nara, a city on the shore
Wind Knight's Road Natural Fortress Maru
Wind Knight's Road The true nature of the fate is Dio's hideout
The joy of taking action while the Sun King is still around
While the Sun King is still there, clean up every month
Dio, you're so good at playing with your life.
Dio, come tomorrow to you, we'll defeat the end now
Thank you Speed ​​Ago I appreciate it
The inside information was accurate. It seems that Tranchen has escaped further ahead.
Dio will build his empire here.
If we can find him while the sun is still out
Enter the tunnel. This is the entrance to the city.
Arrived on schedule
Hey, giant carriage, why are you stopping the carriage?
Be careful, the sun doesn't reach here
Escape from Tranchen
Look, horse, horse
What is this thing?
The horses also slipped in easily.
Your blood
I'll give it a taste.
Jota, you two stay back.
I will fight
JoJo, fighting spirit.
It's growing
This insect is a giant human being.
I'm challenging you to a fight
Can you call that courage?
What are you talking about?
What exactly is courage?
Disturbing breathing is scary
If you overcome fear, your breathing will not become irregular
Ripple Cannon Attack
Goku is a product of courage
Human production is the production of courage
The greatness of humanity is the greatness of courage
No matter how strong
These zombies don't know courage
Drinks and dollars
Dollars!
Hot! Hot!
desire!
I can definitely kill you
surely!
Pieces out!
I'll eat it
Hidden passage in the tunnel
Window Light Lot
This is the knights' training ground
I hear there are a variety of tricks
And there's a huge underground cemetery.
He's inviting
Chasing makes you lazy
I'm sure Dio is up there
Dollars!
Can you hear me?
Sleeping Knights
Dollars!
Answer me
Tell the King Again
Let go of that grudge now
It's erased history
Subverting justice
Win it all
That's the world
Unwavering
This Dio World
Dio's World
The long silence
It has corrupted this country
Now is the time to speak up
My throat has been blown
Scream from the mud
Drop that star
Let's allow that
Mytion!
Easy jewel!
Raise this voice
Rot in 300 years
Let it go behind you
Return in 300 years
This one second
Wait, Dio
Come quickly, JoJo
I am
I got my world
Dollars!
Kill them all
Destroy it all
Even life is controlled
Breaking God's Word
Controlling history
I'll learn everything anew
Controlling Time
Beyond Eternity
Heavenly Command
Rule them all
It's been a while
Live to the fullest
Acknowledge all
Justice is justice
A country of justice and ulterior motives
Beyond Eternity
Rule them all
Song weaving
Seeking kindness
My World
This world
Dio's World
Laughter
Ah, it melts
The dead melt so fast
My cheeks melted and holes appeared
The tongue pops out of the hole
There's a hole in my cheek
A tongue is sticking out of the hole
Jack!
Oh, that's true.
Dio!
Protruding
The fire went out
Your lives too
It's time to sink
I've been preparing for that moment
But it makes me feel good
You are a man who cannot be forgiven, JoJo. You have a fighting spirit.
Jojo Lessender The North Wind Created the Vikings
I have a fighting spirit. I broke a drop from the glass the other day. I can defeat them.
The North Wind created the Vikings.
Disturbed the universe
A similar wind is blowing
Wine Harmony
I feel it
Sing the Darkness
The Serpent Gate Wave
Resonate throughout your body
Solar Universe
Sing the Darkness
My hands are shaking, Harmony
Hautau fans will surely burn out
Sunlight
Yellow
Over
Don't do it
Dollar Hive
Wave Gate of the Sun
Dio
This is the power that will defeat you
Dio Frando
I don't know you personally
But
Against the stone wall that awakened your brain
I dare say
for now
You
I dare to say to the stone wall
We finally met
Don't get on my head
If I can heal this wound in my stomach
JoeJoe
It was attached to you
What?
Fire injuries are detected
With your lives
I'll disinfect this wound with ultramarine
you
How many lives did that wound suck out of you?
You
Do you remember how many slices of bread you have eaten?
I'll make you take root
The blade of the sun
bread
Poor poor
this is
My arms are frozen
The energy you radiate
I thought it was blood related.
I am
You can control your body freely
If you freeze your veins
I can't use that power
Don't disrupt your breathing
Breathe
Attack
Waste, waste, waste, waste
breathe?
波紋?
If you blow
It would be fitting if they were playing a fanfare for me
A poor friend that suits you
What?
fellow
Yes.
Do you remember?
Someday
Your father
The story of the knight that my parents told
what?
16世紀
Plot to assassinate Elizabeth I
The tragic queen sentenced to death
Mary Seward
I told there
Two people
It's the story of a proud knight.
My dad too
yes
We listened to it together, didn't we?
JoeJoe
Dio
Today, this tradition is passed down in England.
Let's talk about two knights
The spirit that descends downwards is alive
A tale of knightly pride
It was three hundred years ago
Two countries competing for support
Queen Elizabeth Suffers
Beautiful Mary Seward
He gave the sword to Mary.
Two legendary heroes
Power with You
It will happen again in the afterlife
Plaford Solo
Deliberate Heart
Shoot the shapeshifting enemy
Two people with no luck
I trained that strength
Looking for a stop
Finding comfort in Mary's self-love
Pledge your life
But one day
Their mistress, Mary,
By Elizabeth
accused of murdering her husband
I'll be captured
The two heroes are unstoppable
To save Mary
To stop the two heroes
Elizabeth calls out
Let your skin and blood live on
I will spare my master's life.
There's no way we could refuse
We have no regrets
For this dear queen
But he was about to be executed
I'll tell you about the maid's souvenir.
Your master is not imprisoned.
You and I lost our heads
That's her lying here like trash
Let's keep him alive
Because there is a risk of rebellion
You betrayed me, Elizabeth.
I will curse you with this grudge
Curse forever
The anger of the Eighth End makes human flesh like iron
I can't get through that neck
Her hair got tangled around Plaford's chest.
Like a living thing
I lived with this in mind
Knight's Tale
A strong smell that gives you goosebumps
What a loyalty
But they should have done better.
In the end, I couldn't do anything in the mud
It could be said that it was a pointless death
You may be right.
But nothing is meaningless
The same goes for when you came to this house.
It's all connected
I want to believe they continued to see the stars.
People live in a prison called fate
Reach out your hand there
Are you seeing stars?
Or somewhere
Both
Joe John
Dio
Call it justice
Hahahahaha... those two...
I made it into a weapon of revenge that can blow away even demons.
Damn it...
Even history can be your servant!
No way...
Hahahahahaha...
Hahahaha...
Oh no...
Hahahaha
What is this appearance?
To avenge a grudge
What an embarrassing sight
Don't you think so?
Kill them all.
A continuation of that day
Tarkus
Braford
Let's scream "Fansfare"
Above us
Our
Pride, the great wrestler Bruford
and Tarkus
Your thoughts and pride
I can't imagine the resentment
But to me too
There's something I'm carrying
We're the ones who'll eat this guy.
Cartilage
It's delicious
The man's pride
I take it as a kiss
My master
I'm in Braford
The end of this brave man's life
I want to draw
Okay, that's good.
Come on, it's a kiss duel
Run away, both of you.
Joe Stan
Tarkus
I won't let you get in my way
a
In the wilderness of memory
Hit
smoking
Atlantic
That morning sun
It was red as blood
Osa
You're not coming
ah
Fuck
I can't do anything
I'm already grateful
I don't have anything
I'm powerless
Wait a minute
Don't mess with me, even at a time like this
Even if you give up, it still hurts
Continue to deceive
Tomorrow for sure
you
Like I'm alive
I kept chasing
Let's make a tragedy
Is revenge your identity?
Is that your pride?
What if
Fight for your pride
and
If we win
I hope you win
What is your heart now?
Let me shake it off
It's not the pain that's scary
What you should know
regain
Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow
Tomorrow and now
Osa
Melt
I came along to die
Speed ​​moves
Now my heart
Let me shake it off
Look at you
Someday tomorrow
Don't wait
I start walking
Should believe
Should be reclaimed
Tomorrow
now
I'll carve it
Blood Beat
you
Please bring back that proud heart
I am
Black Knight
Branboard
I like this
pain
Why doesn't it work?
You just said pain
You are feeling pain now
pain
So I stopped fighting with you
So you stopped the sword
You are a proud knight
Human
The pain
Proof of Life
Is this a human?
Because there is pain
I can feel the joy of being here now
A strange sense of peace
I feel now
Bravo
Let me make you follow the words engraved on my sword
Good luck
And courage
To save souls
That I have to kill
you
Queen Queen
No way
Defeating the Black Knight
also
You are this Dio
Hey Baby
The plant's jamon attack will tempt you.
what
More vulgar than a frog's argument
Hamon
It's dangerous
A knight's disgrace
What's the point of not repaying your grudge?
What is joy?
Queen
Victory!
Victory is our pride
Damn it
I'll do it
Let's do it
Queen
my
The last jamon
Follow me
My will
Queen
Collapse
I'll destroy that evil spirit.
Sink into the darkness of history
Tarkus
Old man
Mr. Jepel
When you're gone
If you are sad
Stone Mask
Destroying
Old man
When you're gone
If you are sad
Stone Mask
Destroying
Old man
I
I'm satisfied with my life
lastly
My everything
I entrusted it to you
Chocho
You
It's my hope
Old man
this
Life spills out of my arms again
You taught me my meaning and my destiny
He taught me that the greatness of human beings is courage
The light I receive will permeate my heart
It was like having a best friend and a son at the same time.
From now on I will live inside you
thank you
Everything is connected, everything has meaning
This pain that I believed
This pain
What your father entrusted to you, what you entrusted to him
The golden light inside me
There is one certain thing that I want to release in my heart right now
Embrace it and escape from this prison
Seeing the stars, the golden heartbeat, the brilliance of humanity
I'll light up the darkness and come to you
My hands to you
girl
Okay, okay.
Can't you hear my voice, my voice calling out to you?
I can't hear it, I've already killed the past
Don't call me by my name, I'm not like you
Death has broken it, my son.
It has been reborn, it remains the same, in order to live
I'll use it all and entrust justice to you.
Win all, rule all
I want something next, something I want
What I want is that is that is that is
Lyrics, composition, arrangement, and arrangement
Here it comes...JoeJoe...
Is this the world you wanted?
what?
Is the world you lost long ago a pitiful one, surrounded by dead people like this?
It's a wonderful world where I control everything. Even death and history...
And to do so, do we rob innocent people?
It's a noble sacrifice for the future I envision.
You're just scared. Humans... that's why I stopped being human.
To obtain it, he went beyond humanity.
I just ran away.
All that matters is the results.
The only outcome is that I win and dominate...
It's all destined to be like that!
different!
It's about how you lived.
What have you left behind by resisting fate?
This symbol is...
He gave me strength and then died.
It's your father!
That's right...
It's something I can't do in all seriousness, but...
The current Jonathan Joos...
To get revenge!
I will kill you!
You're the same too!
That's how you get rid of your grudge!
No! You've been in denial!
I will take over!
Speed ​​out!
It's crap in my mouth...
Now you don't have it...
Dear Joes!
Squeeze it, that life is also at my disposal...
I've lost so much...
But the light shone.
A purified, tainted arrow...
That's what I lived for...
Waste, waste, waste!
The blur breaks!
Waste, waste, waste
To take everything
Set this heart on fire
Gained power
This pain will ease
If you think about it, you are me
You've been both sides of the story
Child's Ice
Burning my body
Kill me
Zettel told me
Using the sword as a medium, I will pour feathers into you.
Yay!
Defeated Diou
That's not right.
Stupid Tomoka
This is a sword
緊弱緊弱
Don don don
It's a little tense, but I can feel your pulse
Now you too can be part of my night
thief
What a monkey! You ran away from humans after all.
Why aren't you freezing me right now? Diou!
Just by being hit by this death, I have surpassed humanity
You can't keep up
You're a monkey, girl
No! If there are people who die
I'll search for that heart
Even humans grow
As long as we are human
If you wish for that, you can stop it
Like earth and ice
I will sacrifice my life to prove my worth
Even the people I've connected with
Like earth and ice
I will sacrifice my life to prove my worth
Diow! Diow! Diow!
How many times have I come?
I like Number One
My eyes!
It seems the original dream has entered his eyes.
Until I lose you
I'm gonna hit you now
I won't stop
That's stupid
My body is hot
Melting
be destroyed
This Dio
still
There was more
He broke his eye and released his own bodily fluids.
Dear Dio,
Mr.
Part
新聞!
How about a newspaper?
In 1888
December 4th
London Crest
The article
That little incident
That small town
Missing Persons Case
Very strange incident
73 people
disappeared
It suddenly disappeared overnight
The groaning I heard from the deer
No one has been found yet
In 1888
December 15th
Wind Nights Sound Article
Eyewitnesses speak out
The day after the incident was gone
Men burning clothes
And smashed it with a hammer
Yes, the mask of will
In 1888
December 18th
Seven Rider Second Shacola
From drinking
Iwaburu is
Heir to the John Star family
Jonathan?
John Starr got married
The other person is
The Pendleton family
Spirit woman
Erina Pendleton
Honeymoon begins the next day
A long-term battle in America
A little news
John Starr
I wish you both happiness
I will always support you
When you stop, wherever you are
I'm going to rush over.
Harnemoon
I'm looking forward to the look up story
America is great
Someday I will too
I want to dig up some bills in America.
Shikusho
And after this
The fateful moment arrives
This story will be shared by the world.
Continue speaking until uniformity is achieved
That's this busybody
It's a job introducing Speedwagon.
But now
Speaking
It's not me
Boo
Eternal
Today
Offer a prayer
Among the circling stars
my
this
My hands are always touching yours
What's wrong?
I'm happy you're here
It's the same for me, I wanted you to meet your father.
Let's go eat
Jonathan!
That's...
Erina, I'm back in the guest room.
Don't forget to lock the door
I brought him with me.
My Body
Are you here?
Dio
JoJo
I dare to expose this pathetic state of myself to you
I used to underestimate you, but now I respect you
Because I realized that
If God controls destiny
There's no relationship as calculated as ours
I got this power because of you
Because you were there
I don't have it all
How far have you...
That's why this is destiny
I'm the only person in this world I respect, and I've got a human body.
Living a glorious eternity
JoJo
We are in this world
Two people are one
Lord Dio! Look! Look! Look! Please look!
JoJo!
From light to darkness, this is where my myth begins
Let's end it all and start it all
Don't destroy Dio's world, JoJo
Dio!
There are keys that don't make any sound.
Only you can take a deep breath
The myth begins
The ship is in danger of slowing down.
Only this one!
help me!
Beat them to death?
Or do you enjoy being a knight?
completely!
Don't give yourself, cut off your head
My friend Yamagami-san will not tolerate insults.
I'll steal you
That blood will become my servant
Connecting to the future
The last feather left
Just die.
Run!
Something inside me broke
Something decisive
JoJo!
This is it!
Run away
No, JoJo
With you
Until it burns
Everything is everything
Until it disappears
Flames run
Everything is connected
Live for me
It's okay if you cry
You will inherit this fate
The flag of loneliness also grew
Be happy
I'll live
Who will win in the end?
Dead Flower
Be happy
I'll live
JoJo!
It's about you
Before my consciousness melts
I thought you were coming.
Let go
Let go, JoJo!
This guy
Dead
It's about you
Before my consciousness melts
I thought you were coming.
Let go, JoJo!
His proud life
Vanished beyond the customer
The destiny and adventure
It's undecided
Will continue to be spoken of forever
Heart of Gold
When I sing
Two in One
A strange friendship
feel
I agree
Yo
Without you
Because you were there
Hey
JoeJoe
Now I
Keep watching the stars
Guided by the destiny I love
Reaching for the stars
The two of us, our destiny
Becoming One
music
Quietly
From the world
One saw the stars
During the tour
The stars shine
The mud pulsates
One saw the mud
Go away
With you
Light
Lighting
Let the wind blow tonight
Everyone is shaking
In the darkness
Ride the Shadows
Transcend time
The world
expensive
Getting tired
Calling the Name of Time
With you
The stars
shine
mud
teeth
Speedwagon is
Cool!
With you
The stars shine
I saw mud
Lyrics, composition, arrangement, and arrangement
【whale】
I'm really happy that I've been able to gradually get involved in this way.
So please take this opportunity to say a little thank you to your teacher.
Thank you so much, Dr. Araps, for gradually disrupting things.
And thank you to my childhood friend Imamura.
thank you.
Now, please, Mr. Koo.
I had the opportunity to play Inspector Archer. My name is Yabatsu Kou.
This is my first time performing in such a big musical, and musicals are the best.
Is it possible to be this happy?
This time in particular, I was able to do something that I personally will never be able to experience again.
Well, I got to see everything that the staff were doing behind the scenes,
Even today, when I watched it, all sorts of things kept going round and round in my head, and I was constantly moved.
This musical is really moving, isn't it?
Really.
I'm so glad.
To everyone here in the theater, to all the performers, to all the staff,
I'm really grateful to all the staff.
Thank you so much for supporting this reset, this moving fortress.
And, especially for us, this time we were reminded once again that the greatest source of nourishment is the smiles of our customers, as seen here.
It was a lecture that really made me feel that very strongly.
I am truly happy that I was able to give such a miraculous lecture all the way to the end.
Thank you very much.
【applause】
Now, Mr. Kong, please. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Great staff, great cast.
And thanks to everyone who came to the theater and everyone who watched the film,
We have now made it through the viewing process and are now able to reach the final performance today.
I am truly happy.
And, best of all, he was very supportive.
thank you.
And, above all, my son was doing his best as a single man.
【applause】
That's amazing.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Dad.
The person who raised him wasn't wrong.
I'm really happy.
And then, thank you for your greeting earlier, Kouchi-san.
They really supported this play.
Thank you very much. Thank you so very much.
Everyone, please check out Kouchi's Proud Funding page.
thank you.
For more details, please click here.
【applause】
Now, we're all connected.
We're connected.
See you at the next theater.
Thank you very much.
【applause】
Get rich.
[Laughter]
Thank you! Thank you!
Now, Miisa-chan, please.
yes.
The hurdle has become even higher.
[Laughter]
I'm not sure if I can speak it well though.
This is Shimizu Miisa, who plays Erina Pendle Ton.
【applause】
Thank you so much for joining us today.
And thank you to everyone who watched the stream.
What should I say?
It was really thanks to the strength of each cast member and the staff that we were able to get to this great war settlement.
And this work.
I think it's all thanks to everyone who supported me.
Please come everyone
Please look at the stars
That's it
So, Dice, please
yes
Speed ​​Mode Role Dice
Um
It was my first experience
It was really hard for me
But really
Yeah
It was really hard though
Already
To get support
Like supporting them.
Words like "support each other"
It really feels like it's going straight into your body.
It's a really nice spot
Thanks to that
I was able to get through it.
in
I can only say the best
With everyone here on stage
This person also said,
I'm not standing on this stage
Although he's not here today
And all the staff who helped create it
and
For the past 5 months
I really appreciate that we were able to be together.
I want to make it a treasure in my life.
Um
Please love JoJo
Thank you for taking an interest in Speedwagon again.
Including everyone who loves me
Thank you very much
Huh
Ladies please
I'm Toyama, and I supported the role of Cheppeli.
Today
Ceppeli
Cheplisen
Nice to meet you again
To everyone attending the Great Athletes' Music Performance and those watching the live stream,
Thank you very much
If you really think back
that
There were a lot of different things that happened.
Two people from JoJo
Shotaro-kun and now Yuya-kun, who finished here yesterday
And another Cheppeli
Hiro-kun
And alone
I've done this much
Led by Mamo-kun, this company is united as one.
With the determination to make it a success
This great player came here with the aim of becoming Rakugo.
Yes, without calling anyone
I've been able to come this far
Of course, the dedicated support of all the staff
It is the result of your efforts.
I only do half of each stage,
Every single performance was met with thunderous applause.
5000 yen
Um, us
The cast now is
It's really the energy of your ripples.
How much courage it gave us
I think we all really feel that way.
That's really true now.
I was there for almost six months, almost five months.
It really is like a family
It's already today and tomorrow will be a valley
Hey hey
valley?
It's a sweet story
Well, let's just leave it as a casual acquaintance.
Just a little bit
I feel a little lonely though
The world of JoJo that I really love
And with my favorite members
I found a group of people who breathed the same air as me at the theater.
Your hearts
Bang, that was it.
It has become my treasure
I am proud to have been able to do this with you all.
Thank you very much everyone
thank you
I want to finish again
Blacks
Teacher, please
good job
I'm Tetsuya Bessho, who co-starred with Joestar.
Thank you for today
I am overwhelmed with emotion
I have been involved in a lot of different works.
This work is exactly as the title suggests.
It was a strange adventure.
hey
Really
As some of you may know,
Born at the Imperial Theatre at the opening of Haran
The current Imperial Theatre is closing.
It will be the last new work
I participated without tears.
My friends are cast members here.
It is staff
And the original author
The collectors and the people of the East
It took five years
Apparently the script was rewritten 17 times. This work was born out of this process, and has now been well received by everyone, and is now coming to an end.
There are many musicals, including works from overseas, and such works, such as Coordinate Zero, are on Broadway or in the West End, and we are here in Japan,
We will be screening the film for a thousand days and ten thousand days, amplifying it greatly and in a very Japanese style, but I believe that what you have seen this time is a work that has become a coordinate axis, going from zero to one.
This work may be taken over and performed again someday, but I hope that my colleagues here at Zero One on this coordinate axis will
I really love them all and feel like they are all my sons and daughters.
There was only one difference. We both have the same father, and as a father, I would like to continue to tenaciously survive in the musical world as a friend who drinks mud and stars together, both pure and murky.
I am so grateful to have two wonderful sons like this, and today, you may be watching me somewhere, but my son is also Yuyaku.
I was able to take part in a truly wonderful production as a father.
If you have any worries, I hope you will just think that in the end, everything is connected within you, and that everything has meaning.
I hope this work will make you think that there is surely light and stars beyond. Thank you very much.
【applause】
Now, Mambo, please.
I don't know where to start, really.
But anyway, I'm glad I met you. Really.
【applause】
We try to provide entertainment, but sometimes it's tough.
Well, it's scary sometimes.
But, as Dice said earlier, it's not just about supporting each other in the literal sense,
This company made me realize that this is what it means to truly support one another.
Of course, there were a lot of things that happened.
Those are the only words I can express right now, but I want to express more than that.
I was able to hold it as a treasure, and more than anything, I was able to share it with so many people.
[Laughter]
【applause】
Having people enjoy themselves is what makes us happiest.
I am happy to have been able to experience this with these members.
Jojo's brother passed away last week, but as his father said just now,
I think we will continue to look forward and pursue various forms of expression in our own individual ways.
It's still going to be useful.
[Laughter]
【applause】
We'll definitely meet again.
And I think it would be great to see them again in this JoJo.
It's all connected
I too dream of such a day, and today I would like to express my sincere gratitude to all of you.
Thank you everyone
I'm going to say something really nice.
I think it will tighten up nicely.
thank you
I'm Seitaro Arisa, the person who investigated Jonah.
I don't know if you all really noticed,
Because this is the kind of person I am
Even if I stand in the middle, everyone
A lot of people really supported me.
He was like a warm older brother to me.
People who are like family
That's fine for you, so just be yourself
Those words alone have really brought me this far
However, when I look around me,
This time everyone
I've seen the faces that look like they're in pain
Really everyone
The curtain won't open
I think I may have caused a lot of anxiety.
That voice is reaching me directly, too.
However, I also received a lot of criticism from the people around me.
I received a lot of messages asking me what was going on.
But I
I really believe in everyone
I've already seen everyone working hard here.
I feel like I should just watch it.
Just please wait for me
That's really the only feeling I have.
We've all overcome so many big obstacles together
Even if we don't have any more conversations
It's an invisible bond
It's like we're becoming more and more connected through these things.
I've been feeling it ever since the rehearsal studio.
After all, open the curtain like this
The other Yuya who plays Jonathan Josser
We've really talked about a lot of things up until today.
Yesterday I was watching Yuya's War Village and Hiro's War Village.
After all,
It was there today
One more
I felt like I had really completed it.
I've seen some really amazing things
I'm glad I worked hard after all.
I really felt that way as of yesterday.
Today, everyone was so
Seeing your happy face
I am truly filled with joy from my heart
As I had originally thought,
I think I was able to witness a historic moment.
World Garden
We all really worked hard to create this
already
Well, starting with Koishi-san
Koishi-san raised the flag and we all felt like we should follow him.
I'm trying my best to climb the hill, climb, climb
I think I was able to really make everyone happy today.
Thank you so much
I also spoke without really thinking about it.
Maybe some of you think that's not the case.
This is definitely my feeling
The company's feelings
I may be overconfident today, but
I think I've made everyone happy already.
It's okay to think that
I can be proud of the fact that I also provided support here.
I can be proud of the fact that I also supported them.
Everyone did their best.
Yuya
Iro-san
thank you
【applause】
I used this to cut the river.
[Laughter]
Also, in front of everyone
So that we can meet as JoJo
And in the future, this work will not only be limited to Japan
I wish I could stay in the world
[Laughter]
Embracing big dreams
I would like to close today
[Laughter]
Thank you very much
【applause】
Well, I hope to see you again
Today is truly a day
thank you
【applause】
me
Thank you so very much
Everyone...I said everyone.
They're not friends.
Mina...Mina-chan.
Not everyone.
Thank you everyone!
We'll definitely see each other again!
thank you very much!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sorry sorry.
be careful!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching