This is already on the screen.
It's okay to talk
Yeah
Are you okay
It's okay
You, watching this.
Yeah, you there.
It's you guys
You have been chosen.
I’ve decided you’re worthy
of being confided in.
I’m leaving this record of my
will behind for the next generation.
After this, I am headed to an
archaeological site in Mexico.
Time has started to move again
after standing still for 49 years.
Time that had stopped has started to move again
It keeps moving forward.
It has started moving
That's why now
That is why I have to
create this record now.
This record must be kept.
If something should
happen to me, I—
Never mind.
Back to the story.
As you all know, this foundation
was created to support various fields,
Such as medicine, pharmacy, and archaeology—
All with the goal of contributing
to the welfare of humanity.
That’s how it looks on the outside.
On the surface
Right, that’s the cover.
{\ O (spread): It was established with the aim of providing support in a variety of fields.}
On the surface,
Now, listen carefully.
There is a secret to why I established
this foundation here in the USA,
{\ O (gap): I founded this foundation here in the United States and have branches all over the world.}
And created our branches around the world...
That secret is...
The Stone Mask.
[AZTEC CHANTING]
{\ O (spread): The true purpose of the foundation
is to solve the secret of the Stone Mask.}
That’s why I’m here today, to leave
behind a record of the tale of that mask.
And also to tell you the story
of the golden spirit I once knew.
So that you can inherit it.
It all began in the 13th century.
Deep in the Central Mexican Plateau,
a tribe was raising a battle cry.
They were members of the
people of the sun—the Aztecs!
(Chief! Chief! Chief!)
[AZTEC CHANTING]
(Eternal!)
(Life!)
Taken in this hand
(Chief! Ha!)
(Life!)}
Shalt thou become our life?
(Power!)}
(Chief!)
{\ O (spread): However, at some point, that
tribe abruptly disappeared.}
(With pleasure!)
{\ O (spread): The mystery of this disappearance
lies in the Stone Mask.}
Blood of the living
Became entwined in the
unfortunate fate of two young men.
(Chief!)}
With that, let’s pick up the narrative
on the outskirts of London in 1868.
Bloody hell! This rain is awful,
it came outta nowhere!
(We sacrifice!)}
Oi Cammie, you feelin’ cold?
I’ll warm you right up!
Why don’t we stay up all
night, you sweet little thing?
(Chief! Ha!)}
Your voice is sweeter
than birdsong, Debbie!
Wot have we here!
That carriage has gone and wrecked itself!
No one’s swarmed it yet! Alright!
First come, first served! Let’s go!
-Hang on...
-Hurry up! C’mon, c’mon, c’mon!
-Wait!
I said wait!
Yahoo!
Darling, wait! We really
shouldn’t be doing this!
Look at that fancy carriage,
they gotta be nobles!
It’s a treasure hunt! C’mere and look!
This bloke must’ve died instantly.
Look at that! What a
pretty necklace! All mine!
It's a beautiful necklace, I'll take it.
This box’ll have somethin’ good...
What the—
Just a creepy mask!
Don’t need that!
Darling!
Well, isn’t this a nice ring? I’ll take that!
In the carriage! A baby survived!
One man’s misfortune is
another man’s fortune!
Have a look!
A pocket watch too!
Nice teeth!
Aren’t these nice teeth?
They’ll fetch a pretty penny.
That’s enough!
Nobles can buy replacement
teeth! And he’s a noble!
Look, find it
No bad deed done here. Just calm down.
{\ O (spread): The one who bites the stab is a nobleman, this guy is also a nobleman}
Let's start with the top leaves
Let’s take some of those upper teeth.
You... Did you rescue us...?
Are my wife and son...?
She croa—
{\ O (spread): Your wife has already passed away
it seems, but your child is safe.}
Go get him!
baby
I helped
So this too is fate...
I want to express my gratitude
to you for saving my life...
My name is Joestar...
I will never forget your kindness!
I don’t have a fancy name, but
please call me Brando.
Dario Brando!
And so the years flow by until 1880.
It’s an era filled with frenzy.
(Like the ground before a storm,
we’re thirsty with desire)
They were caught up in a dream!
(The era is changing, and now is
the time to make ourselves rich)
Their hands were reaching out!
(In sunlight yellow day, with pride
in our queen, we pierce the horizon)
Grab the money in your hands
(We pierce!)
Time to leave
The base of the castle is also high
The times have changed them!
Open the horizon
(In midnight blue darkness)
(We grovel and squirm to
get our hands on what we want)
(We squirm!)
I hear those voices,
Those oh-so-familiar voices!
Well, your faces seem to be asking
“Who’s this?” so listen up!
Let me introduce myself:
Speedwagon’s in da house!
While I’m passing down this
story to the future generations,
Since it’ll all be yours, I might
as well tell you all what’s sweet
I'll teach you
This country now
It's exactly this era
Let me tell you what’s going
on in this era and this land
Let the sound tell you the speed
Time is accelerating
Becoming stronger
Let Speedwagon tell you
all about this era and this land!
Don't get dropped
of social revolution
(The world is speeding up)
The lights come on
I have hope
Let the light burn, let the light burn today too
(Speeding up)
(So don’t let yourself be thrown off!)
(The lamplight of the Industrial
Revolution burns bright)
Everyone comes to pray in the dark night
(So we sleep with hope in our hearts)
I need to be aware of that weakness
Between the light and darkness!
(Should strife and inequality judge you)
(Reach out your hand to
the sunlight yellow beam)
And reach for the heavens!
(Set your soul aflame in
the beat of the steam)
The light!
(The midnight blue darkness is growing)
(Throw away your fears,
and cut ties with your weaknesses)
The dark!
(The light!)
Light and dark, illumination and shadow
Front and back, two diverging paths
Challenge your God, seize your fortune
It’s a new era, steam trains are the craze
(The dark!)
Midnight blue!
(The light!)}
(We rip through the wasteland,
carrying our resolve)
Rip through the wasteland!
(The light!)
Newborn babes crying out
in the midst of disparity
(The dark!)}
A lineage of destiny, Phantom Blood
{\ O (spread): Don’t let this era
slip from your hands}
Fate’s thread is woven without any end
{\ O (spread): (Sunlight yellow gleam,
the hymn of humanity)}
(The dark!)
Sunlight yellow!}
And just as with any adventure of men,
Always gorgeous but bizarre now and then
(The light!)
The hymn of humanity!}
See with your own eyes the whole venture
To the heavens!}
That’s right, this is
one Bizarre Adventure!
(The dark!)
Oi, brat! Whatcha gonna do?
Whatcha gonna do?
C’mon, let’s go!
hey hey!
Hey, there he is!
Kemeonela!
Nice!
Stupid brat!
Hey, look at ‘im. Bastard!
Do you understand?
This disgusting SEGA!
Don’t let this brat go!
Little puke stain!
Fuck!
What’re you looking at, smart-arse?
Oi!
Hey!
Disgusting!
How’s your old man doing, shitstain?
I haven’t seen him since
his pub went under!
He croak or somethin’?
Word’s going around that
yer mum died in the plague!
Shame, she was a real looker!
I wish I'd offered that woman for sale to you!
He should have sold her off
before she kicked the bucket!
Dio!
Dio! Can’t you hear me?! Dio!
What is it, Father?
Is it medicine?
Oh... Do you need your medicine?
Nah, I don’t need that.
C’mere, I gotta tell you something.
I haven’t got much longer. I know it.
I’m worried that after I die...
My only child will be all by
himself. In that case... Dio,
Oi!
This, this, accept
Take this.
“Joestar”?
He’s a noble.
And he owes me one.
He owes me a debt of gratitude.
Okay?
When I die, send him that letter.
Go to him.
He’ll take care of you, you can
go to school. Sounds good, don’t it?
Oh! Make sure you put a stamp on it!
Cut it properly and stick it on.
Father...
Dad
Now you start acting like a parent?!
Listen up...
You’re a smart boy.
I won't lose to anyone
Become the richest
Dio!
Don’t lose to anyone! Become
the richest man in the world!
How’s it going, I ask myself
They keep taking from me,
and it’s driving me mad
This place reeks of all these deadbeats
I might already be in hell,
the way it makes me sick
Nausea
Still, my mother
And yet, my mum told me to be noble
Be noble
Let go of your pride
She held me and taught me to be proud
He hugged me
Hey Dio
“Hey Dio, look up at the stars”
She kept on saying that,
until the illness took her
Just like that...
Why are my hands always empty?
Am I just here to be taken from?
What a star
Tell me, Joestar, the sky
that you have over you
Do you have it?
Is it blue?
This disgraceful father of
mine, the lowest of the low
A deadbeat will always be a deadbeat
Under this murky sky,
Now, I’ll go take this “inheritance”
{\ O (spread): He struggled and struggled,
and this is how he’s gonna die}
I’ll use any means, yes,
to set me on my path
Tell me, Joestar, in the sky over you,
Is the sun shining?
Oh yeah!
You’ve got something good today too, eh?
Give it back!
Over here!
{\ O (spread): Stop it! It was a birthday
present from my mother!}
Hey Erina, I heard that
your old man’s a quack!
Stop
What are you doing?! Take this!
Ow! That hurt!
{\ O (spread): I hate when guys try to
act cool in front of girls!}
-Hey, do you know who this guy is?
If it was Jona from the Joestar family, he would be more ruthless.
If he’s that Jonathan kid
from the Joestar family,
I’m gonna give him even
more of a walloping!
{\ O (spread): The rich aristocrats shouldn't just stand there and act all high and mighty.}
Ah-ha!
He is the Joestars’ Jonathan!
Snotty little rich boy! You think
you’re so high and mighty?
Danny!
Eh?!
Let’s go already! Shit!
You were a damsel in distress,
so I had to stand up for you.
I’ll beat them, someday.
Let’s go, Danny!
Oh, wait!
Jonathan Joestar
Hey Danny, Danny
You...
You must be Dio Brando!
Jonathan Joestar?
Everyone calls me JoJo. Nice to meet you!
Ah, Danny! I’ll introduce you.
This is my friend, Danny.
He’s a clever old hound!
Oh, and don’t worry about him biting!
It won't bite so it's okay.
Friend?
Yeah!
Danny! What was that for!
We’ve been waiting for you, Dio Brando.
Lord Joestar!
Something wrong, JoJo?
Ah, nothing.
{\ O (spread): From today on, you’ll be
living here in our mansion.}
You’ve travelled all the way from
London, Dio. You must be tired.
You’ll be given the same
kind of life as my son, JoJo.
I am grateful for your
kindness, Lord Joestar.
Mister Brando!
I’m Police Inspector Archer!
Police? Has something happened?
Oh, no!
I’m an old friend of the Joestars.
Although, I could hear Danny
whimper a moment ago...
{\ O (spread): It came over suddenly, so the teacher was surprised and it ended up hitting my leg.}
Ah, that was—
-He came at me so suddenly.
{\ O (spread): He’s a friendly creature, but
I’m sorry he surprised you.}
When I jumped in surprise,
I think my leg may have hit him!
Danny is the Joestar household’s
wonderful guard dog.
JoJo!
{\ O (spread): JoJo has lost his mother too—
and you both are the same age!}
You’ll let this Danny matter go, right?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Hehehehe.
Nice to have met you!
Yeah.
Now then, let me get—
Watch it!
So this is me.
Gearsk!
Don’t touch my bag!
I was just trying to carry it for—
That’s enough.
Your hand is covered in dog drool.
Sorry
I don't want you to touch me.
Ta-ta, JoJo!
Pardon me if I don’t want
it all over my things!
Alright JoJo, I’ll tell
you from the get-go.
I like being the best!
I’m always number one!
I don’t care who you are,
no one looks down on me!
What are you two doing?
And one more thing—
I hate dogs.
The way they grovel and suck
up to humans disgusts me.
i am coming
Keep your stupid dog away from me!
thus
The two boys meet
The two of them begin their youth
Also
Coming, Lord Joestar!
Thus, with this meeting, the
two boys’ youth had begun.
Are you coming, JoJo, Dio?
Bear in mind, as honourable nobles,
We take on the duty of
becoming true gentlemen
This is why we study, acquire knowledge,
(Without pause!)
(Without limit!)
for that
I have to learn
And arm ourselves with logic!
Take care of yourself
You have to be smart
Logic
(So you’ll never lose!)
Terrified
To not lose
Under the guidance of
the goddess of familial love
For the sake of heading
the house of Joestar
(The honourable Joestars!)
JoJo
What’s this, JoJo? JoJo!
Same again
I was wrong.
The same mistakes once again
How many times have
you made them! Six times!
This is the sixth time.
Dio has all of them correct!
It’s just because I love reading so much!
But they haven’t even
taught us this in school yet!
Bear in mind, as proud nobles,
We behave like true gentlemen
Sit up straight, use your knife with grace,
Gentlemen
(So elegantly!)
And maybe
Be quiet
So that your mouth always remains spotless
Stretch your vagina
beautifully
Supple
(Unfailingly!)
It's always
beautifully
Don't forget
Under the guidance of
the goddess of familial love
Whatever happens
To be loved
As a proud aristocrat
Harmful information
JoJo
nevertheless
Is it sincere?
Use of oneself
(So gracefully!)
For the sake of being loved as a Joestar!
(The proud Joestars!)
What’s this, JoJo? JoJo!
Do you call yourself a gentleman?
Look at Dio’s elegant touch
His manners are perfect!
Take away JoJo’s plates!
You will go without dinner tonight!
I am embarrassed by
how much I’ve spoiled you
But...
Such
My mother prepared it for me.
I always tried to correct my preaching.
My mother taught me well. She
always made sure I sat up straight.
You see, we are nobles of high birth.
Bear in mind, as honourable nobles,
In our hearts we must always consider
questions of philosophy and justice
In our great England, a tale of two knights
has been passed down for generations.
One day, their master was
taken prisoner by the enemy.
The enemy was afraid of the
two knights, who had great power.
And so she gave them this condition:
{\ O (spread): “If you two will be executed in her place,
I will guarantee the life of your master.”}
Here is my question for you:
-Yes, sir!
Those two knights who gave themselves
up as prisoners to save their master;
{\ O (rank): Two knights sacrificed themselves to save their master and were taken prisoner.}
Was it the mud that lay before their eyes?
{\ O (spread): What was the first thing they
saw through their prison bars?}
Or was it the stars shining above them?
What do you think?
The stars?
Or the mud?
I...
I think they were looking at the mud.
{\ O (spread): In the end, they had no choice
but to die for their master.}
What’s your reasoning?
So no matter what tricks
they would have had to pull,
{\ O (gap): So no matter how many plans I had, I felt I had to live and do something.}
They were looking at the stars!
So what?
The names of those two knights
will be etched into history!
So what!
The way one lives, and the things
one does, those are important!
I think they should have stayed
alive and done something!
But they—
They were left empty-handed
in the end!
Their lesson is to teach us what
we can achieve by staying alive!
They held onto their
pride until the very end!
They were looking at the stars! I think
they’re teaching us how we should live!
Listen!
{\ O (spread): You are an aristocrat, you have what you have, you live by taking it.}
You’re a noble! You have it all!
{\ O (spread): So isn’t it your responsibility to think
about what you’ll achieve with your life?}
You’ve lived by taking
from those beneath you!
That’s enough, you two.
Bear in mind—
All people live in a prison called fate
Reaching out through those bars,
Do they see the stars? Or the mud?
{\ O (spread): I stepped in next to him, the winner is Choma-san, Choma-san, the new champion!}
Either one could be said to be correct
A world without disparity, that’s sports
{\ O (spread): Now, who will be the next to
challenge our champion, JoJo?}
Where courage alone
has the chance to overturn
Get ready to rumble! Fanaticism
overcomes all differences
-Shall we tell our new friend
how we do things here?
{\ O (spread): This is straight up religion!
If you lose, instant fucking funeral!}
Yeah! Do it!
{\ O (spread): All eyes on are on this ritual
where triumph goes to the victor}
-Good!
The winner is a sweeping hero
{\ O (spread): Don’t worry, I played by the
same rules back in London.}
Who will be declared king?!
The opening bell rings
Here comes today’s challenger!
Oi!
Hey hey, JoJo JoJo!
Oi, JoJo!
That’s a hit to the face!
He lost!
Our king! Our king!
Charger!
Can't get through!
What a wonderful opportunity!
Dio! Dio! Dio! Dio!
Guys, guys, guys!
I think my finger went in his eye.
I must forfeit my win. I have
to leave now, excuse me!
-Hey, hey!
Dio, you were amazing!
How do you move like that?
It hurts
Teach me!
Guys! Ow...
Danny...
Why is Dio always trying to bring me down?
It feels like he’s invading my life.
Hey, Danny, my heart aches
And I’m filled with worry
What if I were to die today?
Would anyone cry for me?
You’re always so understanding
Thank you for staying by my side!
If mum were still here,
would it feel this way?
Would she love me this way?
You’re...
My hanky...
Oi! Thanks for bringing
my handkerchief back!
Hey, I’ll be back here tomorrow too,
So stop by again!
Danny!
Has it caught your fancy?
Please excuse me for
grabbing it without permission.
They say this Stone Mask was
unearthed in some Mexican ruins.
Mexico...
Mm-hmm.
{\ O (spread): We bought it from a London art dealer,
around the time JoJo was born.}
On the way back,
we had a carriage accident.
That was the time your dear
father saved us, you know.
Are you interested in it?
Uh...
JoJo is always out playing
with Danny, isn’t he?
It’s because of the trust and
friendship Danny has in JoJo.
Friendship? With a dog?
I had bought Danny when JoJo was young.
At first, he was afraid
of unfamiliar people,
And he didn’t get on well with JoJo yet.
But one time, JoJo was drowning in a river.
A figure, hearing his screams,
flew down to the river.
{\ O (spread): There wasn’t even one person
around who could hear his voice.}
It was Danny!
He dove in and saved JoJo’s life.
Danny was brave to have risked
his own life to save another.
Young JoJo was moved by Danny’s bravery.
That’s when JoJo truly
became friends with him.
Is that so?
M’lord.
Eh? Ah, that’s right.
Friends...
Erina!
JoJo!
The two met once more!
love
Love! That wonderful curiosity
that guided JoJo’s actions.
JoJo was instantly
head over heels for her.
I fell in love
Danny!
Come boy!
Oh, you’re so clever to eat
the fruit but not the core.
You have to separate the core properly before eating it.
Hey JoJo, what are you carving over there?
Huh? It’s nothing.
What are you hiding?
It’s nothing interesting.
When you say it like that, it makes
me want to see it even more!
You’ll just laugh!
I won’t laugh.
You’ll tell people!
I won’t tell, so show me!
I told you, no!
JoJo!
Oh, my!
Erina, just saying your
name makes me feel at ease
Any musician would fall
in love with its melody
It puts me in such a good mood
To that sound
I'm falling in love
Oh!
What's going well
To be laughing like this
There’s nothing but blue skies
here in vibrant Liverpool
Erina
Elna
JoJo
Our happiness is right here
The clouds are proud
The clouds are proud, and
the wind’s a little sweet
JoJo
Erina
There aren’t enough words
For these ever overflowing feelings
I want to hear your voice
say, “it makes me happy”
That would be so
embarrassing, you—
Scoundrel!
Bad person
I don't know
I don’t know why, but I’m drawn to you
I'm being asked by you
Then find a reason,
let’s make it our reason!
So give me a reason
The reason for the two of us
Your hand,
Hands and
My hand,
When they’re apart I feel so lost
It gives me a little courage
to move forward to tomorrow
People who get excited
attract
Our hearts are resonating,
beating in time
Pale
question
Drawing us together, these
fleeting feelings surround us
It’s already this late!
We have a guest coming
tonight, I have to hurry home.
I need to hurry back.
Erina!
I’ll see you tomorrow!
Yes, JoJo!
Danny!
The one I’m so strongly
drawn to, his name is...
Hey!
I heard you were hanging
out with JoJo today.
It's Erina Pendleton
Today is
Apparently he and Jojo were playing together
that
He...
something
ray
He did it!
Do it calmly
He does the things we’re too chicken
to, and with such confidence too!
I'm numb there
Admire
I’ve got goosebumps!
I want to be just like him!
Have you kissed JoJo yet?
You haven’t, have you?
The first person you kissed wasn’t JoJo...
That’s our Dio!
It was me, Dio!
You know what this sort of thing
means for a lady’s reputation, right?
Hey!
She’s—!
You bitch!
{\ O (spread): What are you doing washing
my kiss away with mud?!}
Dio...
Get up, bitch!
Oi, why’s the booze gone?!
Who do you think puts
food on the table? Stupid bitch!
This idiot
Hey, now go buy some booze!
Father, mother’s clearly not well!
She’s just fakin’ it!
Mum! Mum!
Of course you shouldn’t go to the shops!
I’ve hurt you. I’m a good-for-nothin’.
Please forgive me!
In tough times like these, I’ve
gotta work for your sake too.
Please, you’ve got to get well!
Dio...
-Mum! Mum!
Dio boy, go and buy me booze!
But our money’s already—
I'm counting on you
-Stop it, Father!
Oi, you hear me?
My voice
The voice calling for you?
I already have money
You got money from that
factory job, don’t ya?
what
Will you rebel?
You can make this much money too
Please, leave some money
for medicine at least!
You’re really gonna
disobey me, you bastard?
Father!
You really expect me to
work my arse off for you? Idiot!
You’re all trying to make a fool of me!
After all the trouble I went
through to nick that noble’s shit!
That’s it. That noble, Joestar.
Why don’t I send him a letter...
No...
Dio...
Dio!!
Dio, how could you do such a thing?
How could you hurt her like that!
What in the world have I ever done
to you?! Can you tell me, Dio?
I admired you!
But now there is a single
flame that burns in my heart
What did you do?
Why?
Dio...
You are amazing
You’re so amazing, so
much more than I am
Aren’t you using my name
DIO: A little too lightly?
JOJO: I’ll never forgive you!
So you’ve heard? What I
did to your beloved Erina?
-You’ve disgraced her!
DIO: I bet you’re mad with jealousy!
JOJO: This is for her sake, not mine!
About me etc.
I don't care
I have to stand up to him, even
if I can’t beat him. I cannot lose!
Control your emotions, you’re
different from that drunken lout
On the blood resonating in my heart,
I swear to restore her honour, Dio!
Stand up to it
Even if we can't beat each other
I’ll put you back in your place,
I’ll teach you a lesson you won’t forget
I can't lose
Emotions
Come at me!
This new power arising within me
Trembling Heart
You’re the one who lit this fire in me
Get it back
Dio!
fair and square
smash
I'll make you understand
New power
It comes up
It feels so good!
I won’t stop beating you until you cry!
You miserable insect!
You scum of the earth!
How dare such scum like
you come at me, Dio!
Me, the great Dio!
You two! You’ll be punished for this!
Now go back to your rooms!
Hit
Throwing money
How dare you do this to me?
Towards me
Dirty
This idiot
Like this
To someone who seems to win
This me
This Dio
Like this
To a scumbag
This me
This Dio
What on earth is going on?!
That stupid kiss of yours hurt
me more than you intended!
Ah... Eri—
I feel so miserable!
I’ve never felt pain like this before...
How miserable and painful,
This is the first time I've ever felt this way!
Erina!
Erina...
Erina! Did you say goodbye
to all your friends?
Yes, Father.
I’m sorry for imposing my career
on you. Even though I know you—
With all due respect...
Let’s go.
I’ll make friends over there too.
I underestimated JoJo.
His explosive power...
His resilience...
I have to become stronger...
So that I can become
a gentleman at heart!
I have to control my anger and stay calm...
So that I can take everything from him!
However...
What’s that noise?
Could someone be
inside the incinerator?
Are they trying to get out?!
Danny!!
Oh my god...
Someone! Someone please help!
Seven years passed from that day
Times are changing,
the Victorian era’s flying by us
Population increasing to
the point of overflowing
Art and entertainment
are showered in praise
In the middle of this
unstoppable flow, agitation rages
The height of development,
the growth of British culture
But what goes up, must come
down. It’s only natural
human history,
That the top runners are being singled out
London’s peace has one
of its fingers broken
After that it's downhill,
Top runner,
The judge will be counted,
Chaotic days mix the old and the new
Rondo piece with index finger,
The port's days are filled with new and old,
The map of London
paints a stark contrast
A map of London with great ideas,
Just like the current state of the country
Put the focus on the
dark parts and you’ll see
The curtain of swaying inequality
In this market still
learning from its past!
Is that correct?
You’re... You’re certain,
that it was the Stone Mask?
The one excavated from Mexico?
From Mexico, you say?
It was quite a while ago...
A while?! Could you please clarify?
Yes, I’m certain, sir.
But you're right, sir.
Some gentleman’s wife
fell in love with it,
And bought it from me at a high price—
Yes!! Finally! I found it!
We did it.
Now, where could I find this gentleman—
I don’t trust you...
Who the hell are you anyway?
I apologise. My name
is Zeppeli, and I’m a baron.
My name is Sephiri.
It's a danshaku.
I came from Italy to
find the Stone Mask.
All the way from Italy?!
Wait, he said he was
a nobleman from up north...
I’ll go check in the books!
Please wait.
Just a little word of warning...
Let me give you a bit of advice,
The sun will be setting soon.
It’s better if you don’t
go beyond that street.
Wait a minute!
Yes.
A fog has rolled in...
(A palpable shadow stretches over the city)
(And soon it’ll swallow the sun whole)
(Don’t let it get you,
fight as hard as you can!)
(Fog and smog cover the city,
hiding the smell of crime)
{\ O (spread): (Something’s wrong, people
are thirsty, distorted, broken!)}
(Stretch out your hands towards the light)
(We won’t sink down to hell!)
{\ O (spread): (Hate the poor, hate the
rich, and raise your voice)}
The filth rubs off on the clean
and gathers like grime
Thrown away with the rubbish
He’s got it!
{\ O (spread): Pressed together, our
lot gives off a stench}
The star of Hugh Hudson, our very
own Jonathan Joestar, grabs the pass!
(He’s like a heavy locomotive!)
(One’s on his back!)
{\ O (spread): In 1887, the Trafalda pair raised their voices, saying, "Your profession, your life,}
(He can’t be toppled)
(And a second!)
(Keep pushing forward, JoJo!)
{\ O (spread): I got it! The one who snatched the fangs away was my most noble hero, Jonathan Joe Turner!}
(Bloody hell!)
{\ O (spread): Full moon, spaceship, if public opinion falls, move forward into the future}
(The pride of our school!)
(Incredible!)
(Hugh Hudson’s acclaimed JoJo!)
(And a fourth!)
{\ O (spread): Now here, a full moon, a spaceship, if public opinion falls, move forward into the future}
(Is he finally wavering?)
{\ O (spread): Is it today? Where is it here? On top of which castle? Move forward into the future}
Someone caught the pass!
The final match of the
season ends in victory!
Dio!
(Dio Brando)}
(Leaving them all behind)
(Once again, Dio catches the pass)
(Nobody can catch up to him)
{\ O (spread): Can we write about your friendship
with JoJo for the school newspaper?}
Let me get changed first.
{\ O (spread): (They move like clockwork! You’d
almost feel bad for their rivals!)}
Shall we go home together?
Yeah.
(Truly!)}
(JoJo and Dio!)
{\ O (spread): I think of that word
which is so familiar to me}
(In perfect harmony, they
make the best partners!)
You’re... beautiful,
and a true gentleman
My friend, who’s always
pushing me to be better
You’ve repented for the
wrong you did to Erina
You’ve offered me a shoulder
to lean on, now that Danny’s gone
Ahead of me was your back
We walked this path
together for seven years
So why is it that I don’t
feel any friendship for you?
How are you feeling?
Well, I’m old enough now that
a mere cold can last a long time.
Sir, you’re not that old yet!
Ah, well! I’ve got some big news for you!
Oh yeah, that's a big deal.
JoJo and Dio Brando, they...
Seem to have won!
{\ O (spread): Ah, Dio is a proper member
of the Joestar family now!}
And JoJo has become
a splendid gentleman.
His recent archaeology thesis is superb!
And Dio is projected to graduate
top of his class in law school.
I...
I admire you! Back then—
My lord!
Yes?
I’m home!
Father!
{\ O (spread): Dio! Welcome back!
Ah, and JoJo as well!}
Are you alright?
I can’t get rid of this cough...
Today, the doctor recommended
I be admitted to hospital.
I object!
These days, hospitals
only care about profits!
They say it’s a problem in London too.
I feel safer at home.
I give in.
The shaky hands and chest pain,
they’ll likely get better before long.
{\ O (spread): The trembling in your hands and the pain in your chest will go away.}
Enough of that. You two...
Congratulations on your victory!
What?!
How rude of you, inspector!
Huh?
We...
Oh no, silly me!
I truly am proud.
I have such wonderful sons.
Especially you, Dio.
I was born poor...
But you gave me a chance.
{\ O (spread): Feel free to do whatever
you like after graduation.}
Thank you.
So, I'll leave it at that.
Inspector, thank you for always visiting.
I have a busy night ahead of me, with
the likes of Jack the Ripper out there.
{\ O (gap): With the appearance of Jack the Ripper, the world has become a dangerous place.}
But this is Liverpool!
There are people everywhere who lack the sense of right and wrong like him.
Well then, I’ll be off.
There are men like him without
any humanity everywhere.
Now, if you’ll pardon me.
The spring mechanism only reacts to blood...
If I solved this riddle, it might cause a
sensation in the archaeology department.
If that happened, this mask that my
mother bought would have a fate of its own.
{\ O (rank): If that happens, then there must be some destiny for this stone that my mother bought.}
This is...
Thank you again, Master Dio—
Oh, it’s the least I could do.
Thank you. I’m getting too old for this.
“Right now... I’m sick.”
I am currently ill
“I’ll probably die.”
“My heart hurts,”
“My hands shake,”
“And I can’t stop coughing.”
Dio...
I endured no matter what
Yes, until the day finally came
Bloody hell! Ever since that wench
died I’ve been crumbling in debt!
I know!
You pawn this crap and bring
me back some booze instead!
My one and only memento of mum
You threw it away!
You wiped your feet with it!
Are you bloody deaf, Dio?!
Everything’s been
taken away from me
How hellish that your blood
is flowing through my veins
I’ll bury you and this damn curse
I will take everything
into my own two hands!
I’ll stay on top, even to
the limits of my humanity
I will find the resolve, plan ahead,
And then, hiding behind a mask—
Dario Brando, my wretched father
May you rot in hell,
together with the past
A world where everything is perfect,
In the palm of your hand, Dio!
Dio!
What’s that in your hand? Medicine?
I found this letter from your
father, from seven years ago.
It details your father’s symptoms
at the time of his death.
Huh?
Show me that.
They’re the same symptoms as my father’s.
Are you always the one who
brings Father his medicine?
What is this non—
Answer me!
What on earth are
you trying to say?!
I’m going to have this
medicine investigated.
JoJo...
If you doubt the validity
of that medicine,
Then you doubt our very friendship.
As a gentleman,
{\ O (gap): I swear to you in all sincerity and on the honor of your father, Mr. Brand.}
If you can swear on your father’s honour,
I ask you to swear your innocence on
your father’s honour and the Brando name.
I’ll never speak of this again.
Swear on it.
Tia
A vow
I swear
oath
Swear on that guy?
Dio,
DIO: Swear on it?
JOJO: Come on, swear on it!
DIO: Swear...
JOJO: Swear on it now!
JOJO: Can you swear on it, Dio?!
{\ O (spread): I won’t ever let you go
near my father again!}
That scum has never had any
honour for me to swear on!
That there was never any
friendship between us to begin with!
I’ll protect the Joestar family.
This is all a
misunderstanding, JoJo!
Just a misunderstanding...
Besides...
It’s not like you have
any proof, do you?
Nothing more than a flimsy theory.
Yes,
I despised my father, hated
him more than anything.
I just lost my temper when
you started suspecting me...
I've become selfish
JoJo...
JoJo! JoJo!!
JoJo
Is something the matter, Master Dio?
No...
I’m alright...
Dio Dio Dio Dio Dio!
It’s too late to turn back now.
A world where everything is perfect,
In the palm of your hand, Dio!
Father!
What’s going on, Young Master JoJo?!
Speaking out loud like that
-Father!
I’m going to London
for two or three days.
While I’m gone, take only what the
doctors and nurses I’ve hired give you.
I decided to provide perfect care.
Excuse me, but—
Please don’t accept any care
or medicine from anyone else.
but
We’ll do as he says.
I don’t know what’s going on...
I
I believe in my son
Father...
Thank you, Father.
Seven years ago, this thing...
This guy
It moved in reaction to my blood.
With this...
I’ll make it appear as if he had
an accident during his research.
JoJo...
Your own research...
Will be the death of you!
Time’s nearly out, so I gathered
my resolve and took off!
{\ O (spread): I headed for the fringe of
society, the East End of London}
Turning my eyes to the stars
and praying for an antidote
{\ O (spread): Now I’ve arrived here
in this town steeped in mud}
Ogre Street, the place
where plagues are born
Before my eyes lies
the underbelly of society
But I have a reason why I must move forward
Even if I were to lose
this right hand of mine
I’ll look to the stars!
At long last our meeting takes place
{\ O (spread): This is Ogre Street and
we’re the ogres, duh!}
Got no problem with you bein’ naïve,
I’m just showin’ you the simple reality
{\ O (spread): There’s a scent in the air
and it smells like prey}
Hey hey hey,
how about it, rich boy?
{\ O (spread): Sniffing you out through the
storm someone’s making his way}
Want a taste of the
edge of this knife?
{\ O (spread): It’s time for your
leader to take the stage}
We’re gonna strip you of all that you got
Put up a fight and your life will be lost
This is Ogre Street!
Ain’t it obvious that we’d cheat?
Us have-nots are gonna
steal your riches away!
{\ O (spread): Dunno what the hell
you came here for}
Hey hey hey
My cousin's son
This knife is sharp
From your life to that foolish
heart—we’ll steal ‘em away!
{\ O (spread): Bet you thought you
stood a good chance, huh?}
I'm not going to get into the costume.
If you tend to do that, you'll end up showing your innocence
I am Augustus Golito
Tail between your legs, you can
save your own skin by runnin’ away!
{\ O (spread): In a moment we’ll
devour all that hope}
It goes without saying that we are cheats
The have-nots take the haves
Life is an Auger
Is this guy insane?!
Even my heart was stolen
It seems like it would be safe if we ran away first
High Cattongaren
Augustus Gorrit
(Ogre Street, go on and leave it all behind)
It can even take your life
I don’t care if I lose four fingers!
(Ogre Street, we’ll even fill
our stomachs with your life)
I came here for a reason!
You said you’re fine with
losing four fingers, hah?
(Ogre Street, why don’t we
put that resolve to the test?)
Hold on! I only came here
looking for a poison seller!
Quit bluffin’! Let me have a
go at this soft little rich boy!
That’s the sound of blade hitting bone!
Made the mistake of my life, pickin’
a fight with this fearless tough guy
Countdown to my final breath—
Three, two, one!
I ended up in the wrong town
Stop, everyone!
Handling my end
Countdown
3 2 1
I, Speedwagon, won’t allow you
to lay a hand on that gentleman!
This Speed ​​Burgon was allowed, why didn't he kick with all his might?
Why didn’t you kick me
with your full strength?
I came here for the sake of my father.
So in the moment I kicked,
{\ O (spread): I thought you must have a father,
or mother, or siblings too.}
I don't want to do anything that would disappoint your father.
I came here for your father.
That's why Kelsion thought you must have a father, mother, and siblings.
I didn’t want to do anything
to cause your father grief.
{\ O (rank): That's why Kelsion doesn't want to do anything that would cause your father grief.}
Tell me your name!
Jonathan Joestar.
Someone bandage his wound.
{\ O (spread): Mr. Joestar, if you’re looking
for poison, that’d be Wang Chan.}
Be careful, he’s a crafty one!
I, Speedwagon, will lead you to his shop!
Why?!
‘Cause I’ve taken a liking to ya!
(Ogre Street)
With your determination to fight
(Ogre Street, you’ve lit in
us a glowing guiding light)
(You, who have the courage)
(To see the stars down here in the mud)
O courageous one,
With a courageous heart
(Light up the darkness with
your unwavering heart!)
Your refreshing sunlight
Brought me completely to my knees
This must be some
strange twist of fate!
Let’s toast—to our meeting!
JoJo...
JoJo...!
Dio...
JoJo has gone off to London...
Could he have died a dog’s death already?
Dio...
Or could he have found
evidence of the medicine?
Which is it?!
Dio...
The water boiled.
Booze! I can’t help but drink!
Can’t you hear my voice?
The voice calling for you?
-Shut up, get out of my head!
You’re the only one I care about
Become the richest man!
-You piece of shit, we’re not the same!
Watch where you’re going, twat!
Oi, are you listening, you stupid brat?
You should ask yer mum to hold
you by the hand next time!
Didn’t you hear me?
Oi! You piece of shit—
Can’t you hear my voice?}
Are you stupid? Oi, Dio!
You filthy old tramps with
no sense of personal hygiene...
Are you stupid? Oi, Dio!
How dare you! You bastard!
What did you do to my mate?!
One man’s misfortune...
Human voice
I’ll kill you!
Is another man’s fortune!
Interesting, this is a good
opportunity to try it out!
You’re my clever boy!
It's in my arms
It’s a live human experiment!
Dio Dio Dio Dio Dio!
{\ O (spread): I’ll find the answer to your
research myself right now!}
What...
What—
What is this light?
Was I hallucinating?
He’s dead...
The spikes pierced so deep into his skull,
it must have killed him instantly.
{\ O (gap): If you get stabbed in the head with this much force, it's only natural that you'll die instantly.}
This mask is just some ancient
sacrificial torture device.
He’s not dead!
Fangs?! What is he?!
I’m thirsty, thirsty, so thirsty!
He’s sucking my blood!
His face is...
Becoming younger?!
We can fight
I don’t want the morning sun
to be the last thing I ever see!
By the sunlight...
He turned into ash...
Ugh...
Ah...
Hahaha...
Damn...
Ow!
This is...
Is the power of the Stone Mask.
So this...
It seems he hasn’t come
home since last night.
I’ll call for reinforcements right away.
Please use the foyer.
Thank you.
-You there!
-Sir!
This Asian fellow,
Wang Chan—take him away.
Take that Oriental, Wyche!
Yes sir!
Oi, come on!
JoJo...
I apologise.
Sorry...
This is my cross to bear.
What?
If only I had made sure
that man was exiled...
Dio’s father...
I’ll tell you about it.
What do you mean?
I arrested the criminal!
Then that means—
I...
But I never reported a theft.
I arrested the man who
was caught pawning it.
Lord Joestar had that ring specially made
as a pair for his and his wife’s engagement.
It was obvious that it was stolen!
Yes, it’s the ring I had made with my wife.
When Lord Joestar thought about his wife,
Tears welled up in his eyes.
I have caught the culprit
Would you like to see for yourself?
Stealing from a noble is a heavy offence.
He’s certain to be exiled!
I see.
Here he is! Oi! Wake up! Brando!
Don't complain, Brand.
Brando?!
Oh, bollocks.
Dario Brando isn’t some saviour,
But a thief!
Even knowing this,
Lord Joestar adopted Dio.
He adopted Dio.
Why?
I was moved to tears by
what Lord Joestar said next.
Didn't he say this to you?
That I gave him this ring?
Yes, he said that. A lie!
Uh, yeah
It’s not a lie.
This is what I gave him.
He is innocent.
But it’s a memento of your wife!
Mr. Brando,
yes
This is yours.
With this ring, please buy
what you need for your family.
Lord Joestar! Are you taking the piss?!
If I were suffering from poverty
I would have done the same
thing, yes, for the ones I love
Yes, for the ones I love
For the ones I love
When the stars in the sky
shine, they start to tell a story
Soon, like a myth
Let’s pray that this light
will illuminate the darkness
Let us pray
Thank you, sir!
You are too good-natured!
This scumbag will laugh at
you tomorrow morning!
That may be true,
But think about it the other way around.
From the prison called fate,
people reach for the stars
Let’s embrace that courage,
that loneliness,
That pain
There’s a meaning to it all
I believe in humanity
and all of its resolve
I can’t see stars or nothin’!
That’s bollocks!
Someday it will shine
That’s why...
Inherited and turned into gold
I’ll keep on believing
That this gold I’ve passed on
Will shine one day
With all of my resolve...
I will defy fate!
{\ O (spread): - Lyrics, composition, arrangement, lyrics, arrangement, composition, arrangement}
Inspector.
{\ O (spread): - Lyrics, composition, arrangement, music composition, arrangement, arrangement}
I heard a bizarre rumour on the streets.
- Floscia's man,
It’s said that a vagabond shattered
a wall with his bare hands.
And then...
When the morning sun hit the man,
he turned to ashes and vanished.
- It disappeared.
It’s the same as what
happened 30 years ago...
It’s a wedge driven into
the wasteland of my memory
- In the wilderness of memory,
Full of passion and yearning
for the unknown world
At dawn, a blood-red sun
rose over the Atlantic Ocean
- It was blood red.
- Full of passion,
My beloved father, the voices
of my friends, my youth
The Stone Mask took
everything away from me
I crossed the seven seas
with my respected father
I swore I’d get revenge,
that I’d take it all back
Maybe not today, but
there’s always tomorrow
Yes, tomorrow...
“A man is what he thinks
about all day long.”
If I don’t find it, I can’t
recover what I’ve lost.
I, Dio, was...
Shit...
JoJo...
There’s a saying that goes like that.
- Stone Mask, if you let me find it,
- It will be irreversible.
- This hand,
- believe.
- Young girl.
I see you’ve returned from London—
It’s a shame it had
to come to this, Dio.
It truly hurts me.
Although you might not believe me,
Those are my true feelings.
I understand, JoJo.
You’re honest like that.
Although it’s selfish,
I have a favour to ask—
The final one
I will ask of you.
Can you give me more time?
Time—
Eh?
I...
R-Regret the choices I’ve
made throughout my life.
Because I was born into squalor...
My ambition was relentless.
What I did was terrible!
I want to repent for my sins!
- I was making amends.
Don’t believe a word he says!
I can see from your face that
you’re wondering who I am.
- picture?
- Everyone has a dirty look on their face.
Allow me to introduce myself!
I’m Speedwagon, the meddler!
Growing up in the darkest slums,
I’ve met all sorts of horrible
people throughout my life.
So I can tell all I need to know
about a person just from their smell.
This guy reeks!
Worse than vomit!
He was born evil!
Mr. Joestar, you should call
for the police right away.
This man has confessed already.
Father...
I’ve heard everything I need to.
I will return to my bed to rest.
I don’t want to see my son
being taken away in handcuffs.
You won’t succeed in arresting that man...
JoJo, I understand!
Arrest me.
{\ O (spread): I want you to put handcuffs on me. We've been together for seven years.}
But, if it’s not too much to ask;
I want you to be the
one who handcuffs me.
For the sake of those seven
years we spent together.
To be human is to have limits
That’s what I’ve come to realise
And still the more I try to plan,
The more I see the limitations of this life
What’re you talking about?
You know, JoJo...
This frustration, it’s unbearable
I’m always coming up empty-handed
This prison I’m trapped in,
it’s slathered in mud
I can’t see the stars, and no
matter how hard I struggle,
That murky sky up there,
It’s crushing me!
I can’t reach up this way
That’s why, now is the time
{\ O (spread): Yes, Joestar, even
your purest pedigree,}
Can’t wash the filth out of mine
To break free, from this cage
The stars!
And seize...
The Stone Mask?
I...
Reject...
JoJo!
Stop!
-JoJo!
-Father!
Dio!
Lord Joestar!
Father! Father!
This is...
Your late mother’s ring.
A doctor’s coming, he’ll save you! Hold on!
Please... don’t blame Dio for this.
Maybe... the fact that
I was so hard on you...
Made him feel like I was
treating him differently.
To die...
How could this be...
I knew I made a mistake, back then.
Now he’s dead and there’s
no bringing him back.
Mr. Joestar...
You always told me to be a gentleman
To always live with pride
Even though I said I’d save you,
Even though you said you believed me!
I couldn’t protect you—
How could I be so powerless?
What does it mean
to be a gentleman?
Father, open your eyes!
What’s pride worth now?
What’s the purpose of
This Joestar blood
flowing through my body?
You always remained a
gentleman, until the very end
Carrying yourself with
discipline and pride
Your resolve to shine a beacon
through the dark wastelands
I’ll accept it all, and
look up at the stars
I’ll engrave your will into my soul
Take pride in this heart
that shines like gold!
It will become the future,
sent up to the stars
This Joestar blood
flowing through my body!
Everything is connected,
there’s a meaning to it all
I’ll fight against this fate,
keep sorrow at bay
With just one drop of courage!
Inspector! It’s an emergency!
What’s wrong?
If that’s the case...
The body... Dio’s body is gone!
What?!
What did you say?!
Inspector!
What the hell?! He came back to life!
Even though we shot him into Swiss cheese!
Be careful! He’s got some kind of weapon!
Someone has a weapon
No way
Dio!
Stop!
Shoot him! Don’t just
stand there! Quickly!
I don’t get it! I can’t make heads
or tails of what’s happening!
JoJo!
H-He’s sucking his blood!
Dio!
These monsters are
making more monsters?!
Run away, Mr. Joestar!
You’ll only get killed!
That monster is too bloody strong!
The brain!
Speedwagon!
I must make my will stronger!
JoJo!
Weak! So weak!
Let me enjoy this amazing power
for just a little longer!
Humans have limits!
This isn’t a “trick” I’m using to stop you!
This fire won’t kill him.
How about it?
That mask must have drawn out
an unknown power from his brain!
{\ O (rank): It's no wonder that God has lost some unknown ability from his brain.}
So then
I’ll have to completely destroy his head!
Stop!
Look!
more
It’s courage!
Turon...
above ーーー!
Poor, poor!
Mr. Joestar!
Just a little longer, just a little longer, I'll enjoy this wonderful power.
After all, I still don’t know
what I’m capable of yet!
JoJo...
Don’t run upstairs!
Come, Dio.
I’m up here.
Is that an invitation, JoJo?
{\ O (spread): No matter how many
tricks you come up with,}
Very well, I’ll take care of you first
{\ O (spread): Quit hiding behind that
curtain! Come out here!}
(The flash of flames,
scattering the light)
{\ O (spread): You and your friend
can become my lifeforce!}
I’ll suck you dry!
(The flames are pulsing)
JOJO: Father! I’ll mourn you
DIO: I offer you my thanks
(The flash of flames,
illuminating the dark)
Come on up, Dion! I'm here.
Are you inviting me, JoJo? Okay, you go first.
Shining light on the running flames
I’ll put an end to you and
your cursed powers here!
It’s useless! Useless! Useless!
(Flickering from light to dark)
JOJO: Please give me strength
DIO: For giving me strength
I always walked in your shadow
Your back was always ahead of me
You were always right behind me
My youth was with you
It’s time for us to say goodbye to it
The Joestar manor is burning
And Father is dead!
I’ve lost everything, save for my life
I’ll let that burn to ash too.
I’ll stop you, Dio!
Mr. Joestar was surely thinking,
That a stronger fire could overpower
that demon’s healing ability.
{\ O (gap): The stronger the firepower, the more the monster's recovery power can't keep up.}
“If only the flames were
even hotter!” But by then...
The fire had already engulfed the
mansion, even overtaking the roof.
Damn it! Mr. Joestar!
Woolly
This body is immortal.
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
(Equally doling out love and judgement)
-JoJo!
It’s useless! I’m immortal!
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
(Equally doling out love and judgement)
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
(Equally doling out love and judgement)
Goddess of Giving Love
This can’t be how my life ends—
The power of hell
Goddess of Giving Love
JoJo!!
Can you hear me?
You can hear me.
Good.
I hope you had a nice intermission.
I’ve returned in order to
continue telling our story,
This room doesn’t allow visitors.
{\ O (spread): Of the world to which all of
you have become witnesses.}
But that’s why I’m here!
{\ O (spread): And so that we can continue our
show of love for these characters.}
I’m doing enough for him as his nurse.
Please come back some other day.
Is he alright?! Oi, hold it—
{\ O (spread): I hope you get the merch
you’re looking for too.}
JoJo...
{\ O (spread): The story up to this point
seems like a bit of a fairytale, but...}
Can you hear me?
My voice,
{\ O (spread): Things are going to get more
and more bizarre from here on out.}
You recognise it, right?
From that bright, fleeting moment
when we were drawn together
I want to hear your voice again too
{\ O (spread): Previously, the mansion was
shrouded in flames and burnt down...}
Where am I...?
You slept for three whole days!
The mansion! Everyone is—
Please, just relax for now!
You’ve made it through the worst
of it, but you’re still in bad shape!
I’m so glad you’re alive!
Have you been caring
for me this whole—
You’re—
No, it couldn’t be.
But you look like...
Look like who?
Like Erina Pendleton?
{\ O (spread): After carrying the unconscious Mr. Joestar
to the hospital, I came back to visit him!}
It’s been a while, Jonathan Joestar.
24th
25th
27th
How?
28th
29th
30th
31st
This is my father’s hospital.
{\ O (spread): To give him some small
hope to keep on living!}
32nd
33rd
34th
We moved to India seven years
ago, and just recently returned.
35th
36th
37th
It’s really been too long.
38 days
39 days
40 days
41 days
I was weak back then,
I couldn’t run to your side
42 days
43 days
That's why I came!
Nursing is done well.
I was childish back then,
I couldn’t face you
Please come back at a later date.
Are you okay?
Oh, wait a minute.
Your voice is still the same
Sigh...
My feelings are still the same
There’s nothing but blue skies
here in vibrant Liverpool
Erina
JoJo
I am...
Our happiness is right here
Huh...
…
The clouds are proud, and
the wind’s a little sweet
…
Erina!
Oh, I’m sorry! I must have
lost my focus and fainted.
…
I slept for three whole days straight.
My goodness, you caught
me with your broken arm!
Everyone in the mansion
Please stay calm now
We've passed the peak, but it's still a tough time.
I’ll always be there to catch you.
I'm glad you're alive
You've been nursing me
When our
you
No way
Eyes meet
But they look similar
Who said we look alike?
To Elina Pendleton
picture?
I can see it there
It's been a while
Jonathan Joestar
Why?
This is my father's hospital
That little bit of courage
to move towards tomorrow
I moved to India seven years ago.
I recently returned to Japan.
It's really been a while
Your hand
I was weak
I couldn't run to you
Meets mine
I was a young child.
I can feel you there
Our fates entwined forever
Now our hearts
resonate, beating as one
Drawn together on that fleeting day
We’ll continue from there
Just the two of us
Fate? That’s right.
Maybe some people are
just fated to meet one another.
Speedwagon coolly withdraws.
Extra, extra! Read all about it!
He’s struck again,
that bloodthirsty maniac
It was the same method, another woman—
Her throat was slit
(And she had her guts ripped out!)
The utmost cruelty!
No known motive at all!
The truth of the
matter is out of reach!
(Like it’s made of fog)
(Don’t go out walking at night!)
(You’ll be killed! He’ll find you!)
(Only killing prostitutes,
throwing their guts up on the wall)
(Only found in fog and
darkness, that’s Jack—)
Jack the Ripper!
You’re kidding!
Oh, it’s already so late!
I have to return home soon...
It’s not late at all!
But we might run
into Jack the Ripper!
It’s a terrifying thought!
Terrifying, is it?
It is!
Well, as a matter of fact...
You’re talking with him right now!
You’re out playing too late,
You dirty harlot!
You...
{\ O (spread): (The plague of London,
that bloodthirsty killer!)}
Slash
The method was the same woman's throat.
That belly is a face
Ammo is the worst
The identity of the synchronized person is completely unknown
I can't grasp the truth
I like you.
Now that you’ve seen me, I’ll—
I don’t feel any pain, I’ve
got nothing to fear anymore
Come to my side, Jack the Ripper!
{\ O (spread): I’ve been reborn, now’s the
time for my life to start!}
Take my hand!
{\ O (spread): Oh, I must heal these wounds,
and for that I’ll need lives!}
Seeing stars, or seeing mud?
{\ O (spread): Not to mention a
faithful servant—Jack!}
We’ll change the tune of
that tired old philosophy!
I’ll start to live from this moment on
A life that forsakes the sun!
(Blood, flesh, devour it all!)
(Wry! Wry!)}
I don’t need it anymore!
(Blood, flesh, devour it all!)
{\ O (spread): However, very rarely there are
those not constrained by goodness.}
(Blood! Flesh!)
{\ O (spread): Those are the evil elite.
Like myself, and you as well!}
This is Dio’s World!
{\ O (spread): How about it? Will you
become my, Dio’s, companion?}
The Stone Mask...
I want to believe it turned
to dust like everything else.
{\ O (spread): I understand you, Jack.
You’re angry at them, right? }
Yes.
{\ O (spread): Those women who
indulge in pleasure}
It has to have been.
{\ O (spread): Women who are
dripping with ecstasy}
It’s alright.
{\ O (spread): Go and spill more guts! There’s
no need to be afraid anymore}
I’m alright.
Has he been here
this whole time?
Jonathan Joestar!
And Miss Erina Pendleton.
You’ve done well to survive
the power of the Stone Mask!
{\ O (spread): I’ll give you pleasure greater
than you’ve known before}
JoJo!
(Pow!)
{\ O (spread): Break out from the narrow
confines of your prison}
Squeeze out
Every last ounce
Of air inside your lungs!
How could you, he’s injured!
What?! My broken arm—
It doesn’t hurt anymore!
I am Baron Zeppeli!
Courage alone won’t defeat
the power of the Stone Mask
I am on your side!
{\ O (spread): Whether to look at the time or what to look at, there are enough words to}
I manipulated your breath, your
breath made the pain go away
How do you know my name!
Hey JoJo, one question at a time!
This world
The Stone Mask?!
If you do, your fate will change
{\ O (spread): I want to believe that, like the others, I have become a powder keg.}
Whether you accept that or not
let's go
The choice is up to you!
That
What will happen now?
Let me demonstrate for you
The power that this breathing awakens!
(Breathe in, breathe out)
(In, out!)
(Pow!)
With this special breathing
(Pa-pa-pa-pow!)
You carry special oxygen
(In, out, in)
In the blood it sends racing
All throughout your body!
(Pow!)
And energy is born!
(Pa-pa-pa-pow!)
Its name is—
(In, out, in)
Ripple Energy!
(Memetaa!)
[TN: Sound of a frog being punched]
The ripple’s power
passes through the frog
Making this miracle happen—
The power this breathing
infuses into your blood!
(In, out)
Everyone has a little bit of energy
flowing through their bloodstream.
It does things like carry nutrients
and regulate your body temperature.
The power of the ripple gathers that small
amount of energy from all over the body.
This is made possible by the rhythm
of a particular breathing technique.
In, out!
(Pow!)
We must fight!
{\ O (spread): They’re two sides of the same coin,
this breathing and the Stone Mask}
(Pa-pa-pa-pow!)
We must destroy it!
(In, out, in)
And you must wield this
ripple energy, or you will die!
That’s right, your fate,
and the fate of the world
{\ O (spread): The man wearing the mask, Dio,
walks in the darkness even now!}
(Pa-pa-pa-pow!)
It has been set in motion!
(In, out, in)
I finally found it!
Will I get my hands on it? Our fates
Are all tied together. This is—
(In, out!)
Destiny!
To fight... That is my destiny!
Mine and Dio’s!
The Stone Mask’s bone needles
draw a strange power from the brain,
That turns humans into vampires.
Beings who must get energy
by taking the blood of others.
However, the ripple also derives its
power from the flow of the bloodstream.
Has the same shape as the light of the sun!
{\ O (spread): It’s the same energy, like
two sides of the same coin.}
You see?
We’re already out of time.
You must learn how to turn
your courage into power!
JoJo?
Erina...
{\ O (spread): If you hit them with another
ripple, they’ll break apart!}
I can’t get you involved in this!
For now, please just go along with it!
I swear I’ll come back here again.
How...?
Collected from the whole body
What makes this possible is
It's a rhythm of breathing.
Breathing is the power of now
The power to defeat Dio!
Yes I know
This breath, both inside and out
About the Stone Mask
And about you and Dio
Dio
The mask can only be worn by those who haven't changed.
Rio the Stone Masked Man
I still walk in the darkness
I travel the world
I followed the mask
To destroy
Dio is alive
If we don't fight
If you don't destroy it
Jamon in your hand
Otherwise
You and the world
(In, out!)
I finally found it
Do you accept it?
This fate
Everything is lifted up
That's it
supermarket
destiny
fight
That's my destiny
Me and Dio
The individual body of the Stone Mask
Unlocking the unknown power of your brain
Turning humans into vampires
it is
You must take blood energy from others.
On the other hand, Hamon's power
From your own bloodstream
To draw out energy
Front and back
Same energy
Yeah
In other words
To remove this jamon
What do you mean, Dio?
The clouds are drifting by
and the wind is swirling round
Leaving memories behind
I nodded along, to your resolve
To the sorrow you held
Stars are drawn together
Guided by this hapless fate
As I wander here, mired in mud
I am left behind
I live in a dream,
waiting by the window
Tell me, why am I left in solitude?
Even if it doesn’t reach you,
even if it won’t bring you back to me,
I want to scream!
Because you left for my sake
You are drawn to me
Forever guided by fate
I’ll live my days, spinning its thread
While looking up at the stars
So that one day you’ll tell me the story,
I’ll keep living with pride
I’ll accept every part of you
Our stars shine together
{\ O (spread): So that I can call this
destiny one of love}
No matter where you are, I will, I will,
I will live on!
Wang Chan, you’re alive?!
Yep!
C’mere!
Why are you so strong?!
Don’t tell me... It’s
because of that damn Dio!
Speeeedwagon!
You know too much about
the secret of the Stone Mask!
JOJO: Stop right there!
Mr. Joestar!
I wa-ha-ha-was looking for you too!
Because, because Lord Dio
said I could slurp up your blood!
Licky licky? Licky licky!
Licky licky! Licky licky!
Lickithan Joestar.
JoJo, be careful.
He’s strong enough to rival you.
What was that, you old fart?
Old fart?
Time for a taste!
His arm... got longer!
It’s useless.
I’ve been given new life!
And a body that transcends humanit—
That’s not what’s important here.
M-My body...
It’s hot!
What the—it’s hot! So hot!!
Ah! Wait!
In this short time, you’ve
learned the ripple so well.
What’s wrong, JoJo?
I lost so much...
That’s why I wanted power.
But not this...
Not the same as Dio’s!
Yours is fundamentally different
from those who gain power by stealing!
Ah!
Haha!
Ha!
But it’s the same power!
Haha!
No way, that Dio guy
SPEEEEEEEE!
Wagum!
You are,
I know too much about the Stone Mask's secrets.
It’s amazing!
There’s a saying in the
northern country of Norway:
“The north wind created the brave vikings!”
Because they knew the pain
of the harsh northern winds,
They became vikings with backbone!
You are different from Dio and his ilk!
Because you feel the pain.
Pain...
The pain of losing friends
It’s a wedge driven into the
wasteland of my memories
My father and I once
crossed the seven seas
One quiet and calm night
The mask burst with light
And all 58 men of my
crew were massacred
Mr. Zeppeli!
The man in the mask came forward
{\ O (spread): I still don’t understand what
it means to be a true gentleman}
ZEP: Clothed in blood and darkness
JOJO: The same as it was then!
{\ O (spread): But the Joestar blood
resonating in my heart burns hot}
My arm...
me
What I saw in that moment, illuminated
by the salvation of the morning sun, was—
It was my father!
It was
Under the red light of the
morning sun, my father disappeared
I got a new life
My soul’s clock has been
frozen in that moment ever since
Creating something that surpasses humanity
If it's important, it's not here
ZEP: I’ve been chasing after it
JOJO: So that it won’t repeat
{\ O (spread): I was the one who excavated
that cursed Stone Mask!}
ZEP: I swore to take revenge
JOJO: I won’t let you down!
Or your body!
It's hot! What's this?
ZEP: So that tomorrow will be
JOJO: Shining bright
It's hot! It's hot!
Oh! Wait a minute!
We embrace this pain!
Amazing, JoJo
What you need is the courage
to make that pain your own!
You've mastered Hamon in such a short time.
And the resolve to face the consequences.
what up?
JoJo!
I lost my treasury
So I wanted power
But that
Not the same as Dio
To hurt someone
It is fundamentally different from the power that is obtained by stealing.
But it's the same power!
There is a proverb in the northern country of Norway:
The North Wind created the brave Viking
A harsh north wind blows
Because I know the pain
A Viking with timber frame was born
Not like them
You
I know the pain
pain
The pain of losing a friend
The pain of inheriting pride
The pain of the person you want to protect
Proof of Life
We embrace this pain
I was always told to be sincere.
Always following my father's lead
I still don't know if it's true sincerity
The Joestar's blood is hot and trembling
The daily routine surface is dyed in a glowing red darkness
That tragedy repeats itself
We embrace this pain
Hey JoJo.
JoJo JoJo JoJo.
Ha-hey JoJo.
Hey-ha-hey-ha JoJo.
Don’t forget this goal.
Yes, sir.
I believe in the power of the ripple.
Yep.
I like your fringe.
Hey JoJo, JoJo!
Why, why?!
Jonathan Joestar!
Lord Dio! It hurts! Where are you?
Are you angry?
You’re good company, huh?
Oh! It burns! It burns!
My body, it—
Is that Mr. Horse?
Look Wang Chan!
Your, your ancestors—
Clippity clop, clippity clop!
The lovable sweetheart, Mr. Joestar,
has finally got a handle on the ripple
Hey yo yo! We’re coming
to collect payment
These bills been piling piling up
Your underworld rep, AKA
Speedwagon, is here to give a full report
Who else would be your guide
To this 16 bar showtime?
South of London, in total daylight,
That famous city of knights
He’s inside the horse’s body!
This is Windknight’s Lot
A natural fortress like an augite rock
Give me a little taste of your fresh blood!
{\ O (spread): When we pass through this
tunnel, you’ll see the sights}
Windknight’s Lot
Fate’ll have it—Dio’s hideout
While the sun’s out
We’ll knock it out
Clean this vampire nest out
Ay, Dio, dick, you make me sick
You play with life, that’s bullshit!
No more tomorrows Dio, that’s it
Now’s the end, ya gonna get hit!
Thanks for keeping watch, Speedwagon.
My underground sources say that
Wang Chan definitely fled here.
Without a doubt, this is where
Dio is building his own empire.
It’ll be better if we search for
them while the sun is still out.
The entrance to the town
is through this tunnel.
Stand down, you two.
I will fight!
JoJo, here’s a battle lesson!
You’ve heard of fleas, yes?
They come after us humans
even though we’re giants to them.
Could you call something
like that “courageous”?
What are you yammering on about!
{\ O (spread): That guy should be Yama-chan, the researcher finally got a grip on him.}
So then, what exactly is “courage”?
“Fear” sends your breathing awry!
{\ O (spread): Represent the underworld AK Speed ​​is a detailed investigation by agreement}
Surrendering to that fear
throws your breath out of sync.
The ripple breathing technique
is a product of courage!
{\ O (spread): From London to the south, on the round land, we drove without rest in a carriage}
The hymn of humanity
is a song of courage!
The greatness of humanity
is the greatness of courage!
These zombies, no matter how
strong, know nothing of courage!
They’re just like fleas!
Hot, so hot!
Yes... I’ll eat every
shred of you in one bite!
There’s a hidden passage in the tunnel!
Dio, come tomorrow to you, we'll defeat the end now
Thank you Speed ​​Ago I appreciate it
The inside information was accurate. It seems that Tranchen has escaped further ahead.
Dio will build his empire here.
If we can find him while the sun is still out
Enter the tunnel. This is the entrance to the city.
Arrived on schedule
Hey, giant carriage, why are you stopping the carriage?
Be careful, the sun doesn't reach here
Escape from Tranchen
Look, horse, horse
What is this thing?
The horses also slipped in easily.
Your blood
I'll give it a taste.
Jota, you two stay back.
I will fight
JoJo, fighting spirit.
It's growing
This insect is a giant human being.
I'm challenging you to a fight
Can you call that courage?
How dare you! I’ll kill you!
I’ve heard it has many tricks, because
it was once a training ground for knights.
There’s also a vast catacomb underground.
They’re inviting us. We must go farther.
Yes. Dio’s surely at the end of the trail.
Can you hear me?
Sleeping knights...
Follow me, serve royalty once again
Get your revenge on the past,
let’s rewrite history
Upend righteousness,
go for total victory
That’s this world, the
unwavering world of Dio
This is Dio’s World!
Your long silence has
left this world to rot
Now raise your voices,
from crushed throats
Crying out from the mud,
conquer the stars
I’ll allow you this and more!
(My sword, it’s yours!)
(Now is the time to raise our voices)
Wrrryyy!
(We’ve been sleeping for 300 years,
us rotten and forgotten corpses)
Wrrryyy!
Get your revenge!
300 years asleep, haunted
by painful thoughts
(Wry wry, we vow to kill!)
(Wry wry, we vow to destroy!)
(Wry wry!)
Wait, Dio!
Come quick, JoJo.
(Wry wry!)
My world is in the palm of my hand now!
So much that there’s a hole in my cheek...
My tongue is sticking out of the hole!
Your cheek is melting,
And your tongue is sticking
out of the hole? Really, Jack?
{\ O (spread): Tearing its natural
order from God’s grasp}
Dio!
Rewriting and upending it anew
I will dominate even time,
My body eternal and sublime
(Eternal life!)
I will dominate everything,
rise above all my cares
(We vow to steal them away!)
Win it all, negate righteousness
In this peacefully unaware country
(This country is ours!)
And demand peace of mind!
(Wry wry, we vow to kill!)
(Wry wry, we vow to destroy!)
Wry wry!
It’s melting...
Let it go behind you
Return in 300 years
This one second
Wait, Dio
Come quickly, JoJo
I am
I got my world
Dollars!
Kill them all
Destroy it all
Even life is controlled
Breaking God's Word
Controlling history
I will dominate everything,
I’ll face them now
The sun has set.
It’s time for your lives
to go down with it!
I’ve been building up my
courage for this moment!
Even so, I can’t help
this feeling of dread.
As a human, I can’t let
you get away with this!
JoJo!
Put your training to use.
(We’ll feast! On your blood and flesh!)
(Steal it away!)
(To heal all of our wounds!)
JoJo, here’s a lesson for you
The north wind made the vikings!
This battle will be an exercise—
You’ll defeat them without spilling
a single drop of wine from this glass!
SPW: We’re not here to play around, have you lost it?
ZEP: You shut your trap!
JACK: I’ll kill them!
DIO: Ah—wait, wait—
Tough vikings were born
from the harsh north wind
Will this wine make a viking out of you?
(Give us your blood!)
Make fear your own!
Here’s a battle lesson:
Muster up your courage! When the time
comes, don’t let your breathing go awry!
The hymn of humanity is a song of courage!
The greatness of humanity is
the greatness of courage!
Everything is connected!
There’s a meaning to it all!
Don’t let your breathing go awry!
(Wry!)
This wine will be my north wind!
(Give us your blood!)
The ripple of the wine!
(We’ll feast on your flesh!)
I can feel it flow, I’ll find my
way through the darkness!
(Give us your blood!)
Are resounding through my body!
{\ O (spread): You are a man who cannot be forgiven, JoJo. You have a fighting spirit.}
(We’ll feast on your flesh!)
With the power of the sun!
{\ O (spread): You are a man who cannot be forgiven, JoJo. You have a fighting spirit.}
Find your way through the darkness!
Pa-pow-pow-pow with unrelenting heat!
(Heat!)
{\ O (spread): I have a fighting spirit. I broke a drop from the glass the other day. I can defeat them.}
Sunlight...
(Sunlight...)
{\ O (spread): I have a fighting spirit. I broke a drop from the glass the other day. I can defeat them.}
Yellow...
(Yellow...)
Over...
(Over!)
Sunlight yellow, sunlight yellow
Overdrive!!
The ripple of the sun! Dio!
This is the power
that will defeat you!
Yeah?
Solar Universe
Sing the Darkness
My hands are shaking, Harmony
Hautau fans will surely burn out
Sunlight
Yellow
Over
I don’t know you, but...
Let me say this to the Stone
Mask that awakened your brain:
Finally, we meet.
Pow!
Utterly pathetic!
{\ O (spread): Perhaps you can heal this
wound in my stomach, JoJo.}
It’s freezing?!
I guessed that this energy of yours
is related to the flow of your blood!
{\ O (spread): Then I’ll be completely healed from
the damage you dealt me in that fire.}
I am able to control my own body at will.
If I freeze up all of your veins,
Then you won’t be able to use that power!
I can’t—I can’t catch my breath!
{\ O (spread): Just how many lives did you
extinguish to heal that wound?}
Mr. Zeppeli!
{\ O (spread): Do you remember how many slices of
bread you’ve eaten in your lifetime?}
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
Breathing techniques? Ripple?
If you’re going to be
blowing all this hot air,
You ought to use it to
play me a little fanfare!
Looks like your companions
are just as weak as you.
JOJO: What did you say?
DIO: Companions...
That’s right. Do you remember?
The story of the knights
your father told us that day?
The tragic queen who was sentenced
to beheading by Elizabeth the First,
After a failed assassination
plot in the 1600s...
Mary Stuart!
It was about the ones who served her!
Father told us...
We listened to it together, didn’t we?!
I'll make you take root
The blade of the sun
bread
Poor poor
this is
My arms are frozen
The energy you radiate
I thought it was blood related.
I am
You can control your body freely
If you freeze your veins
I can't use that power
Don't disrupt your breathing
Breathe
Attack
Waste, waste, waste, waste
breathe?
波紋?
If you blow
It would be fitting if they were playing a fanfare for me
A poor friend that suits you
What?
fellow
Yes!
Do you remember?
Someday
Your father
The story of those two proud knights...
I will regale you with
a tale of two knights,
The tragic queen sentenced to death
Which has been passed down for
generations in our great England.
Mary Seward
Those who lived with a gentleman’s spirit—
I told there
Two people
This is a story of knightly pride!
Long ago, 300 years before today
Two queens battled for the throne
One was Queen Elizabeth the First
And the other, the beautiful Mary Stuart
Two legendary heroes came forward,
Offering up their swords to serve Mary
Tarkus’s strength cleaved
through rocks like butter
Bruford, with his skill and spirit,
cut down foes like a phantom
Without any family, the
two honed their powers
While wishing for a nest to rest in
After finding peace in Mary’s affections,
They swore their loyalty to her
But one day, Elizabeth
accused their master, Mary,
Of murdering her husband,
and she was captured.
The two heroes would not rest
When it came to saving their Mary
In order to stop those two heroes,
Elizabeth made an appeal:
“You two, surrender at once!”
“And I will spare your master’s life!”
This, we cannot refuse
In this, we hold no regrets
Into vengeful revenants that
would send even the devil running!
Even history bends before me!
{\ O (spread): But in the moment they
were to be executed—}
It can’t be!
{\ O (spread): I’ll give you a little souvenir
before your trip to Hell!}
Such grotesque forms!
It’s the perfect form for
taking their revenge!
Don’t you think so?
{\ O (spread): Look at her lying over
there like a piece of rubbish!}
Kill them all!
{\ O (spread): After all, if she was left alive,
we’d risk a rebellion!}
Continue from where
you left off on that day!
Tarkus!
Bruford!
Play me a fanfare with their screams!
{\ O (spread): Stiff with rage, Tarkus’s
muscles were like iron}
Our pride!
Great Dark Knight Bruford!
{\ O (spread): Bruford, filled with regret,
ensnared them with his hair}
As though it were alive!
And that is the story,
Your pride, your resentment.
{\ O (spread): Of those knights who lived
according to their hearts}
I can’t even imagine it!
But I also bear my own burdens!
{\ O (spread): Such blind devotion—
it gives me goosebumps!}
I’m gonna be the one to eat ‘em!
I’ll savour every bit of his cartilage!
{\ O (spread): But those two should
have done a better job!}
Would like to be the one to bring
an end to this brave man’s life!
Alright, go ahead!
{\ O (spread): The only thing to call
their deaths is useless!}
We’ll duel as knights!
Run away, you two!
Mr. Joestar!
{\ O (spread): The same can be said about the
fact that you came here to this house.}
I won’t let you interfere!
A wedge driven into the
wasteland of my memory
{\ O (spread): I want to believe that they
kept on looking at the stars!}
At dawn, a blood-red sun
rose over the Atlantic Ocean
Old man!
Don’t come any closer!
Damn it...
There’s nothing I can do,
I’m a mere spectator
Come on, get real,
even at a time like this?
Even if I give up, the pain
will just be for another day
And tomorrow, yes tomorrow,
I’ll still be over here crying like a loser
In the end, I couldn't do anything in the mud
It could be said that it was a pointless death
Honourable knight,
I’ve got nothing, I’m powerless
The same goes for when you came to this house.
It's all connected
I want to believe they continued to see the stars.
People live in a prison called fate
Reach out your hand there
And you, Tarkus!
Or somewhere
Both
Joe John
Dio
Call it justice
Hahahahaha... those two...
I made it into a weapon of revenge that can blow away even demons.
I am...
Even history can be your servant!
No way...
Hahahahahaha...
Hahahaha...
Oh no...
Hahahaha
What is this appearance?
Our grudge!
What an embarrassing sight
Don't you think so?
Fucking hell!
A continuation of that day
Tarkus!
Is revenge your answer?
Is that what you take pride in?
If you want to preach, then fight
with your pride on the line!
You can lecture me after you win!
Now’s the time, to let
courage resonate in my heart
I’m not scared of pain
I must find the strength to stand up
Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow,
Old man!
Melt!
I didn’t follow you to
become a hindrance!
Speedwagon...
And look the enemy in the eyes
Won’t wait for a distant tomorrow
I’ll start walking,
Find the strength to
get back on my feet
JoJo!
Cut finely, beat of my blood!
Let it somehow be restored!
Okay, that's good.
Come on, it's a kiss duel
Run away, both of you.
Joe Stan
Tarkus
I’ll let courage resonate in my heart
Just now,
That means that now,
Atlantic
That morning sun
That’s why...
It was red as blood
Osa
So this is what it means to be human?
You're not coming
ah
Luck!
Pluck!
I can't do anything
I'm already grateful
I don't have anything
I'm powerless
Wait a minute
Don't mess with me, even at a time like this
Even if you give up, it still hurts
Continue to deceive
Tomorrow is right now!
And also...
To think, I had to kill him
in order to save his soul...
Damn you!
JoJo!
I can’t believe you actually
defeated the Dark Knight!
Just as I thought...
I, Dio, will—
What the...
Fight for your pride
and
If we win
I hope you win
What is your heart now?
Let me shake it off
It's not the pain that's scary
Why aren’t you moving?
regain
Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow
Tomorrow is now!
Osa
Melt
This pain means nothing to me!
Watch out, Mr. Joestar!
Someday tomorrow
What an embarrassment of a knight!
Don't wait
I start walking
He never got his revenge!
Should believe
Should be reclaimed
JoJo!
Tomorrow
No!
I'll carve it
Blood Beat
you
Please... This knight’s proud heart,
I am
Black Knight
Bruford...
I like this
Pain?
Why doesn't it work?
You said “pain”.
You can feel pain!
Pain...
I stopped fighting you.
That’s why you stopped your sword.
You are a great knight.
Human
The pain
Is proof of life!
You are human!
Because there is pain
Because of this pain, I can also feel
the joy of being alive in this moment.
I feel a bizarre sense of peace now.
I feel now
Bravo
I dedicate to you the word
engraved in my sword.
Good luck
And courage
To save souls
What did he have to be joyful about!
How could you!
I take pride in victory!
Fuck!
I’ll get you!
I’ll get you for this!
JoJo...
JoJo!
My final ripple...
{\ O (spread): I bet the blow from that
ripple-charged flower must hurt!}
My... dying wish is...
That you take my ripple
and continue on, JoJo!
If we lose you—
There’s no time to be sad.
The Stone Mask must be destroyed!
I...
I lived my own life to the fullest.
In the end,
I leave everything I have to you.
JoJo,
For victory!
Victory is our pride
Damn it
I'll do it
Let's do it
Queen
my
The last jamon
Follow me
My will
Queen
He collapsed.
I’ll vanquish your wicked soul!
Drown in the murk of history, Tarkus!
Tarkus
Old man!
Mr. Zeppeli!
Mr. Jepel
When you're gone
If you are sad
Stone Mask
Destroying
Old man!
When you're gone
If you are sad
Stone Mask
Destroying
Old man
I
I'm satisfied with my life
lastly
My everything
I entrusted it to you
Chocho
You
It's my hope
Old man
this
Once again, life is
spilling out of my arms
Who I am meant to be
You taught me that humanity’s
greatest gift is courage
Into my spirit
{\ O (spread): The light you’ve given
to me will shine through}
It felt like...
{\ O (spread): I had a friend and a son
in you at the same time.}
From here on...
I live within you.
JoJo.
That’s what I’ve come to believe
Even this pain...
I embrace it tightly
{\ O (spread): My father left to me
what you leave to me now}
I see the stars
{\ O (spread): The golden light that
shines from within me}
A golden spirit
{\ O (spread): It’s the one thing in my heart
that I can hold on to now}
Humanity’s glow in the darkness
Dio!
Light up the way to you...
JoJo...!
Dio...
Can’t you hear my voice?
The voice calling for you?
I can’t hear you
You and I are different
Dio...}
We’re not so different, you’re my son
I have changed into something new
You’re not so changed,
you did it to survive
I’ll use any means
DIO: I’ll steal it all
DARIO: You’ll steal it all
DIO: Upend righteousness
DARIO: You’re my clever boy!
DIO: I will conquer it all
DARIO: What will you want next?
DIO: I will dominate everything
{\ O (spread): Is the world you lost long ago a pitiful one, surrounded by dead people like this?}
Go ahead and dominate,
what will you want after that?
{\ O (spread): It’s a splendid world where
I’ve dominated everything.}
For that reason, you stole
from uninvolved innocents?
DARIO: What do you want?
{\ O (spread): They were a noble sacrifice for
the sake of the future that I designed.}
You’re just afraid.
Of being human...
That’s why you rejected your humanity.
The ends justify the means.
I will win,
And that means conquering
everything, of course.
All of this is fate!
No!
This is just how you
chose to live your life!
Opposing fate...
What will your legacy be?
Such righteousness!
{\ O (spread): That you’ve been trying
to obtain for so long...}
Just like the one who gave me this power...
It’s a pitiful world, isn’t it?
{\ O (spread): As a gentleman, it pains
me to say this, but...}
Now I, Jonathan Joestar...
For the sake of revenge...
Dio...
We’re one and the same; you want
to exact your revenge! I admire that!
No! I’ve come to right your wrongs!
I’ve accepted this as my legacy!
I will take over!
Speedwagon!
Right!
Ironic, isn’t it? Now
you’re the have-not, JoJo!
I’ll suck you dry
Become my next meal!
I’ve lost so many loved ones but
their light lives on in me, Dio!
I’ve come to cleanse
your corrupted ambitions
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
So I could steal everything from you
I’ll dull this pain
You were just like me,
two sides of the same coin
Like fire and ice, my body is burning
JOJO: I’ll kill you
DIO: You’ll kill me
JOJO: You’ll kill me
DIO: I’ll kill you
Just like Mr. Zeppeli taught me!
I’ll channel my ripple through this sword!
Not a chance!
You fools!
What! The sword is freezing—
Utterly pathetic!
Kill me
Zettel told me
Using the sword as a medium, I will pour feathers into you.
Yay!
You did it! You defeated Dio!
JoJo!
Utterly pathetic! I’m grasping
your carotid artery, JoJo!
Don don don
With this, you’ll become
one of my undead servants
It's a little tense, but I can feel your pulse
Ironic, isn’t it, Dio?
Now you too can be part of my night
thief
Just as I thought, you were
running away from humanity
Why don’t you freeze me now, Dio!
My fist... Just from hitting him!
I transcended humanity!
None of you are on my level.
JOJO: That’s what he taught me
DIO: You can’t reach me!
He put his hand in the
fire! If he does that—
{\ O (spread): JOJO: No, for as long as I have faith,
DIO: Compared to me, Dio!}
My lost friends, my father’s spirit
{\ O (spread): DIO: Let’s test your willpower
JOJO: I will reach you!}
JOJO: Our connection, it’s here
DIO: Even when I’ve thrown away my humanity
Like fire and ice
With my life on the
line, I’ll prove it now!
{\ O (spread): JOJO: Us humans...
DIO: To be human is to have limits}
-Dio! Dio! Dio!
-JoJo! JoJo! JoJo!
“I was only trying to be friendly!”
{\ O (spread): DIO: I’ll chip away at this body to prove it
JOJO: I’ll burn up this body to prove it}
“I think my finger went in his eye.”
Dio!
I won’t stop beating you
until you’re finished!
This is impossible!
The heat is coursing through me!
Crumble to dust!
Diow! Diow! Diow!
How many times have I come?
“I like being number one!”
“My eye!”
It seems the original dream has entered his eyes.
Until I lose you
I'm gonna hit you now
I won't stop
That's stupid
My body is hot
I’m melting!
Not yet!!
Watch out! He’s shooting
hot liquid out of his eyes!
Dio...!
Extra, extra! Read all about it!
He broke his eye and released his own bodily fluids.
Lord Dio...!
Mr.
Part
新聞!
How about a newspaper?
In 1888
(In 1888 on December the 4th)
(The London Press reported)
(In Windknight’s Lot)
(That little village, there was
a missing persons incident)
Missing Persons Case
A very bizarre case
Very strange incident
73 people vanished
In just one night,
they abruptly disappeared
It suddenly disappeared overnight
Moaning could be heard from underground
But no one was found
In 1888
(In 1888 on December the 15th)
(In the Windknight’s Lot Paper)
An eye-witness reported
That the following day, below a cliff
Men were seen burning clothing
(And destroying something with a hammer)
It seemed to be a stone mask
Seven Rider Second Shacola
(In 1889 on February the 2nd)
From drinking
(In the announcements section)
Iwaburu is
(The Joestar heir)
Jonathan!
This is the start of my mythos
Right, Erina Joestar?
I can’t speak—can’t breathe—
My ripple!
Erina! Not you too!
Honeymoon begins the next day
A long-term battle in America
A little news
John Starr
I wish you both happiness
I’ll always be there for you!
When you stop, wherever you are
If you’re in trouble, I’ll rush anywhere!
Happy honeymoon!
I can’t wait to hear all about it!
America, how nice!
I wanna go there too,
And try to dig up some oil for myself!
Damn it...
But after this, a fateful
moment was soon to come...
The fateful moment arrives
This story will be passed down
until the world has come full circle.
That will be the life’s work
of Speedwagon the meddler...
But, the one to tell you what
happens right now won’t be me...
I pray that today will never end
In the midst of a carousel of stars
When you’re next to me...
I’m happy!
I feel the same.
I wish you could’ve met my father...
Erina,
Today
Offer a prayer
Among the circling stars
my
this
Let my hand always be in yours
What’s wrong?
Go back to our cabin.
It's the same for me, I wanted you to meet your father.
Well, let’s go and eat!
Jonathan?
That’s...
Erina, I'm back in the guest room.
Don’t forget to lock the door!
I brought him with me.
My body...
Have you come?
Dio...
JoJo...
I used to despise you so much,
{\ O (spread): I dare show myself in this pitiful
state in front of you for a reason...}
But now I respect you...
That’s because I’ve realised something!
If there is a God that controls fate,
Then there’s never been a relationship
orchestrated as perfectly as ours...
You’re the reason I got this power,
And you’re the reason why...
The world has slipped from my grasp!
When will it...
Be enough for you?
You and I...
{\ O (spread): I’ll obtain the body of the one and
only person I respect in this world.}
Please look!
JoJo...
Are one and the same in this world!
Two people are one
Lord Dio! Look, look, look!
This is the start of his mythos!
This ark is swarming with his followers!
Please, spare the child!
Run!
I’ll take you as my own
I’ll tie our futures together
With my final ripple!
JoJo!
I felt it tear. Something
important inside me just tore
Jonathan!
ERINA: How could this be?!
JOJO: Get out of here!
I will burn with you
Until everything turns to ash
(The flash of flames)
You can’t ask me to live!
{\ O (spread): Painlessly cut his head
from his shoulders!}
There’s a meaning to it all!
JOJO: It’s alright if you cry
ERINA: Your courage is too cruel!
JOJO: You will be
ERINA: I will be
Will become an inheritance
Passed down forever
(Flames are burning everything up)}
His golden spirit
{\ O (spread): Just like my mother
died for me, I’ll—}
(Phantom Blood)
(Light and darkness flicker and flash)}
Like two who make one,
(Flames are burning everything up)}
Isn’t that right, Dio?
If it weren’t for you...
(Light and darkness flicker and flash)
JoJo!
I figured...
You would strike...
Before I...
Everything is everything
I’ll disappear
Flames run
Everything is connected
Live for me
It's okay if you cry
You will inherit this fate
The flag of loneliness also grew
Be happy
I’ll live
Who will win in the end?
Dead Flower
Be happy
I’m still alive!
JoJo!
No, it’s because of you
Lost consciousness.
I know what you’re like...
Let go
Let me go, JoJo!
He’s...
Dead...
[AZTEC CHANTING]
Before my consciousness melts
I thought you were coming.
But this fateful adventure
That proud life of his
Vanished into the dusts of time
JOJO: With you!
DIO: I will live!
(The sunlight yellow gleam shines)
(And the shadow of midnight
blue darkness grows)
(Living in the shadow of history)
(Even when the world resets)
(The tale will keep on being told)
We feel a bizarre friendship
feel
I agree
Yo
Without you
Because you were there
Hey
JoeJoe
Now I’ll...
Keep looking at the stars
Guided by this hapless fate
We’ll reach out to the stars
Our two fates
Have become one
(That immortal poem echoes quietly)
Quietly
Until the world
(One saw stars)
Is born anew
(The stars are shimmering)
(Like blood through a vein,
mud is pulsating)
(One saw mud)
Go away
With you
Light
Lighting
(Let the golden wind blow)
Everyone is shaking
In the darkness
Ride the Shadows
Transcend time
The world
expensive
Getting tired
(We’ll stop the flow of time)
With you
The stars
(Our golden spirit will shine)
shine
mud
teeth
Speedwagon coolly withdraws.
Thank you for coming
to today’s performance.
This is a public [streamed] performance.
Since it’s my and Zeppeli’s actor,
Hirose Yusuke’s, final performance,
We each wanted to say a
few words if you don’t mind.
Take it away, Mr. Hirose.
I had the honour of performing the double
cast role of Zeppeli. I am Hirose Yusuke.
Thank you for today.
{\ O (spread): I'm really happy that I've been able to gradually get involved in this way.}
The musical will close tomorrow, though.
{\ O (spread): So please take this opportunity to say a little thank you to your teacher.}
This type of role has been
played by others before,
Although personally, I
found that to be relieving.
There have been many
things that led to this day.
So even now, I have a lot of
thoughts and a lot of emotions, but...
Aside from that, the fact that we
have come this far is really thanks to...
{\ O (spread): I had the opportunity to play Inspector Archer. My name is Yabatsu Kou.}
Each and every one of the cast members
on this stage, and the wonderful and skilled staff.
{\ O (spread): This is my first time performing in such a big musical, and musicals are the best.}
And foremost, the people
who came every day—
You’re not coming every day?
Well, every day—
{\ O (spread): This time in particular, I was able to do something that I personally will never be able to experience again.}
Truly a lot of fans came
and filled the whole theatre.
{\ O (spread): Well, I got to see everything that the staff were doing behind the scenes,}
I would like to think our performance’s
quality is thanks to your support.
{\ O (spread): Even today, when I watched it, all sorts of things kept going round and round in my head, and I was constantly moved.}
Truly, you’ve made each member of
this performance happy. Thank you.
From the bottom of my heart,
Pow.
MAMORU: From the bottom of the heart, pow!
{\ O (spread): To everyone here in the theater, to all the performers, to all the staff,}
Well, I played the role of Jonathan
Joestar, I’m Matsushita Yuya.
Thank you for today!
Did you have fun, everyone?!
{\ O (spread): And, especially for us, this time we were reminded once again that the greatest source of nourishment is the smiles of our customers, as seen here.}
The best, hearing this is the best, yeah.
Uh, right. Really, tomorrow’s
truly the final performance.
{\ O (spread): I am truly happy that I was able to give such a miraculous lecture all the way to the end.}
That curtain call will
be the grand finale, too.
I was already so relieved that
I could raise my voice today.
{\ O (spread): I think that Shotaro will
do perfectly tomorrow.}
Yes, and tomorrow Mr. Hirose and I will
be watching the final performance together!
Everyone, do your best!
I’ll be giving it my all along with you!
Everyone, make sure
to—what are you saying?
I’m doing it! I was
just getting to it, okay?!
I’m gonna watch it too!
{\ O (spread): I wanted to voice some
personal thoughts here.}
Yeah, I’ll watch too.
Pardon me.
{\ O (spread): It’s been a long road to
arrive at our final performance.}
And so, please support everyone
through tomorrow’s final performance!
Truly, thank you for today!
{\ O (spread): Truly, I’m truly happy to
be on this stage. Thank you!}
[TN: Everyone’s muted for about 2 min]
{\ O (spread): Back in February, right?
Opening night was delayed.}
[INAUDIBLE]
MAMORU: It’s already over.
{\ O (spread): At that curtain call, really, at that time,
the audience cheered and applauded a lot,}
[INAUDIBLE]
Definitely, please support
tomorrow’s performance too!
{\ O (spread): Truthfully, at that time, I was feeling, within
me, that we became something unforgettable.}
Shotaro, do your best tomorrow!
{\ O (spread): Yes, that’s right. Truly,
thank you for everything.}
MAMORU: Do your best!
And to Mamo, who supported
me like a partner in this.
Isn’t it seriously amazing that
he did this role without a double?
MAMORU: It’s alright.
YUYA: No, it was wonderful.
Before you even started,
I almost cried when I saw your face.
Yeah, me too a bit! I got emotional!
MAMORU: Yes.
YUYA: Sorry, I had to excuse myself.
Excuse yourself...
YUYA: It wasn’t because of you or something like that that I left.
MAMORU: I get it.
Nah, you were really incredible.
Really spectacularly incredible.
MAMORU: Not at all.
YUYA: No, no, I’m sorry.
It might be unusual for a performer to say this,
but I truly respect you. Really, you’re wonderful.
MAMORU: No, no really.
YUYA: I thought he really rejected his humanity.
You were just that wonderful.
[INAUDIBLE]
MAMORU: Thanks.
YUYA: Yes. So then...
We’re not on the same stage
tonight as we were then, but—
From the first day of rehearsals until now, he’s
supported me, helped me improve, and encouraged me.
Shotaro too. I truly believe that without those
two, I would never have achieved this JoJo.
So, this has been my first time
acting in a double cast performance.
It was wonderful. Thanks!
And above all, above all, truly,
thank you for being devoted like this!
Now to everyone at the theatre,
And everyone watching the stream,
I don’t know where the cameras are but—
Thank you from the bottom of my heart!
And thank you to everyone who watched the stream.
What should I say?
It was really thanks to the strength of each cast member and the staff that we were able to get to this great war settlement.
And this work.
I think it's all thanks to everyone who supported me.
Please come everyone
Please look at the stars
That's it
So, Dice, please
yes
Speed ​​Mode Role Dice
Um
It was my first experience
It was really hard for me
But really
Yeah
It was really hard though
Already
To get support
Like supporting them.
Words like "support each other"
It really feels like it's going straight into your body.
It's a really nice spot
Thanks to that
I was able to get through it.
in
I can only say the best
With everyone here on stage
This person also said,
I'm not standing on this stage
Although he's not here today
And all the staff who helped create it
and
For the past 5 months
I really appreciate that we were able to be together.
I want to make it a treasure in my life.
Um
Please love JoJo
Thank you for taking an interest in Speedwagon again.
Including everyone who loves me
Thank you very much
Huh
Ladies please
I'm Toyama, and I supported the role of Cheppeli.
Today
Ceppeli
Cheplisen
Nice to meet you again
To everyone attending the Great Athletes' Music Performance and those watching the live stream,
Thank you very much
If you really think back
that
There were a lot of different things that happened.
Two people from JoJo
Shotaro-kun and now Yuya-kun, who finished here yesterday
And another Cheppeli
Hiro-kun
And alone
I've done this much
Led by Mamo-kun, this company is united as one.
With the determination to make it a success
This great player came here with the aim of becoming Rakugo.
Yes, without calling anyone
I've been able to come this far
Of course, the dedicated support of all the staff
It is the result of your efforts.
I only do half of each stage,
Every single performance was met with thunderous applause.
5000 yen
Um, us
The cast now is
It's really the energy of your ripples.
How much courage it gave us
I think we all really feel that way.
That's really true now.
I was there for almost six months, almost five months.
It really is like a family
It's already today and tomorrow will be a valley
Hey hey
valley?
It's a sweet story
Well, let's just leave it as a casual acquaintance.
Just a little bit
I feel a little lonely though
The world of JoJo that I really love
And with my favorite members
I found a group of people who breathed the same air as me at the theater.
Your hearts
Bang, that was it.
It has become my treasure
I am proud to have been able to do this with you all.
Thank you very much everyone
thank you
I want to finish again
Blacks
Teacher, please
good job
I'm Tetsuya Bessho, who co-starred with Joestar.
Thank you for today
I am overwhelmed with emotion
I have been involved in a lot of different works.
This work is exactly as the title suggests.
It was a strange adventure.
hey
Really
As some of you may know,
Born at the Imperial Theatre at the opening of Haran
The current Imperial Theatre is closing.
It will be the last new work
I participated without tears.
My friends are cast members here.
It is staff
And the original author
The collectors and the people of the East
It took five years
Apparently the script was rewritten 17 times. This work was born out of this process, and has now been well received by everyone, and is now coming to an end.
There are many musicals, including works from overseas, and such works, such as Coordinate Zero, are on Broadway or in the West End, and we are here in Japan,
We will be screening the film for a thousand days and ten thousand days, amplifying it greatly and in a very Japanese style, but I believe that what you have seen this time is a work that has become a coordinate axis, going from zero to one.
This work may be taken over and performed again someday, but I hope that my colleagues here at Zero One on this coordinate axis will
I really love them all and feel like they are all my sons and daughters.
There was only one difference. We both have the same father, and as a father, I would like to continue to tenaciously survive in the musical world as a friend who drinks mud and stars together, both pure and murky.
I am so grateful to have two wonderful sons like this, and today, you may be watching me somewhere, but my son is also Yuyaku.
I was able to take part in a truly wonderful production as a father.
If you have any worries, I hope you will just think that in the end, everything is connected within you, and that everything has meaning.
I hope this work will make you think that there is surely light and stars beyond. Thank you very much.
【applause】
Now, Mambo, please.
I don't know where to start, really.
But anyway, I'm glad I met you. Really.
【applause】
We try to provide entertainment, but sometimes it's tough.
Well, it's scary sometimes.
But, as Dice said earlier, it's not just about supporting each other in the literal sense,
This company made me realize that this is what it means to truly support one another.
Of course, there were a lot of things that happened.
Those are the only words I can express right now, but I want to express more than that.
I was able to hold it as a treasure, and more than anything, I was able to share it with so many people.
[Laughter]
【applause】
Having people enjoy themselves is what makes us happiest.
I am happy to have been able to experience this with these members.
Jojo's brother passed away last week, but as his father said just now,
I think we will continue to look forward and pursue various forms of expression in our own individual ways.
It's still going to be useful.
[Laughter]
【applause】
We'll definitely meet again.
And I think it would be great to see them again in this JoJo.
It's all connected
I too dream of such a day, and today I would like to express my sincere gratitude to all of you.
Thank you everyone
I'm going to say something really nice.
I think it will tighten up nicely.
thank you
I'm Seitaro Arisa, the person who investigated Jonah.
I don't know if you all really noticed,
Because this is the kind of person I am
Even if I stand in the middle, everyone
A lot of people really supported me.
He was like a warm older brother to me.
People who are like family
That's fine for you, so just be yourself
Those words alone have really brought me this far
However, when I look around me,
This time everyone
I've seen the faces that look like they're in pain
Really everyone
The curtain won't open
I think I may have caused a lot of anxiety.
That voice is reaching me directly, too.
However, I also received a lot of criticism from the people around me.
I received a lot of messages asking me what was going on.
But I
I really believe in everyone
I've already seen everyone working hard here.
I feel like I should just watch it.
Just please wait for me
That's really the only feeling I have.
We've all overcome so many big obstacles together
Even if we don't have any more conversations
It's an invisible bond
It's like we're becoming more and more connected through these things.
I've been feeling it ever since the rehearsal studio.
After all, open the curtain like this
The other Yuya who plays Jonathan Josser
We've really talked about a lot of things up until today.
Yesterday I was watching Yuya's War Village and Hiro's War Village.
After all,
It was there today
One more
I felt like I had really completed it.
I've seen some really amazing things
I'm glad I worked hard after all.
I really felt that way as of yesterday.
Today, everyone was so
Seeing your happy face
I am truly filled with joy from my heart
As I had originally thought,
I think I was able to witness a historic moment.
World Garden
We all really worked hard to create this
already
Well, starting with Koishi-san
Koishi-san raised the flag and we all felt like we should follow him.
I'm trying my best to climb the hill, climb, climb
I think I was able to really make everyone happy today.
Thank you so much
I also spoke without really thinking about it.
Maybe some of you think that's not the case.
This is definitely my feeling
The company's feelings
I may be overconfident today, but
I think I've made everyone happy already.
It's okay to think that
I can be proud of the fact that I also provided support here.
I can be proud of the fact that I also supported them.
Everyone did their best.
Yuya
Iro-san
thank you
【applause】
I used this to cut the river.
[Laughter]
Also, in front of everyone
So that we can meet as JoJo
And in the future, this work will not only be limited to Japan
I wish I could stay in the world
[Laughter]
Embracing big dreams
I would like to close today
[Laughter]
Thank you very much
【applause】
Well, I hope to see you again
Today is truly a day
thank you
【applause】
me
Thank you so very much
Everyone...I said everyone.
They're not friends.
Mina...Mina-chan.
Not everyone.
Thank you everyone!
We'll definitely see each other again!
thank you very much!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sorry sorry.
be careful!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching