Is this thing on?
Can you hear me?
Okay, it’s good.
Everything’s working.
You, watching this.
Yeah, you there.
You have been chosen.
I’ve decided you’re worthy
of being confided in.
I’m leaving this record of my
will behind for the next generation.
After this, I am headed to an
archaeological site in Mexico.
Time has started to move again
after standing still for 49 years.
It keeps moving forward.
That is why I have to
create this record now.
If something should
happen to me, I—
Never mind.
Back to the story.
As you all know, this foundation
was created to support various fields,
Such as medicine, pharmacy, and archaeology—
All with the goal of contributing
to the welfare of humanity.
That’s how it looks on the outside.
Right, that’s the cover.
Now, listen carefully.
There is a secret to why I established
this foundation here in the USA,
{\ T: I founded this foundation here in the United States and have branches all over the world.}
And created our branches around the world...
That secret is...
The Stone Mask.
[AZTEC CHANTING]
The true purpose of the foundation
is to solve the secret of the Stone Mask.
That’s why I’m here today, to leave
behind a record of the tale of that mask.
And also to tell you the story
of the golden spirit I once knew.
It all began in the 13th century.
Deep in the Central Mexican Plateau,
a tribe was raising a battle cry.
They were members of the
people of the sun—the Aztecs!
(Chief! Chief! Chief!)
[AZTEC CHANTING]
Blood be life, life be power
(Life!)
(Power!)
Eternal! Power! Eternal! Life!
(Eternal!)
(Life!)
Taken in this hand
(Chief! Ha!)
Shalt thou become our life?
(Chief!)
(With pleasure!)
Blood of the living
(Chief!)
Life is power
(We sacrifice!)
The power in this hand
(Chief! Ha!)
(We are children of the sun!)
(For us Aztecs, life becomes power!)
(We, Aztecs, have drawn the sun’s wrath!)
However, at some point, that
tribe abruptly disappeared.
The mystery of this disappearance
lies in the Stone Mask.
This is the story of how the Stone Mask
Became entwined in the
unfortunate fate of two young men.
With that, let’s pick up the narrative
on the outskirts of London in 1868.
Bloody hell! This rain is awful,
it came outta nowhere!
Oi Cammie, you feelin’ cold?
I’ll warm you right up!
Why don’t we stay up all
night, you sweet little thing?
Your voice is sweeter
than birdsong, Debbie!
Wot have we here!
That carriage has gone and wrecked itself!
No one’s swarmed it yet! Alright!
First come, first served! Let’s go!
-Hang on...
-Hurry up! C’mon, c’mon, c’mon!
-Wait!
I said wait!
Yahoo!
Darling, wait! We really
shouldn’t be doing this!
Look at that fancy carriage,
they gotta be nobles!
It’s a treasure hunt! C’mere and look!
This bloke must’ve died instantly.
Look at that! What a
pretty necklace! All mine!
This box’ll have somethin’ good...
What the—
Just a creepy mask!
Don’t need that!
Darling!
What?!
In the carriage! A baby survived!
A baby?! Leave it there!
We want valuables! Val-u-ables!
Oh...
Well, isn’t this a nice ring? I’ll take that!
-What are you doing?
One man’s misfortune is
another man’s fortune!
Have a look!
A pocket watch too!
Nice teeth!
Aren’t these nice teeth?
They’ll fetch a pretty penny.
That’s enough!
Nobles can buy replacement
teeth! And he’s a noble!
No bad deed done here. Just calm down.
Let’s take some of those upper teeth.
You... Did you rescue us...?
Are my wife and son...?
She croa—
Your wife has already passed away
it seems, but your child is safe.
Go get him!
So this too is fate...
I want to express my gratitude
to you for saving my life...
My name is Joestar...
I will never forget your kindness!
I don’t have a fancy name, but
please call me Brando.
Dario Brando!
And so the years flow by until 1880.
It’s an era filled with frenzy.
(Like the ground before a storm,
we’re thirsty with desire)
They were caught up in a dream!
(The era is changing, and now is
the time to make ourselves rich)
Their hands were reaching out!
(In sunlight yellow day, with pride
in our queen, we pierce the horizon)
(We pierce!)
The times have changed them!
(In midnight blue darkness)
(We grovel and squirm to
get our hands on what we want)
(We squirm!)
I hear those voices,
Those oh-so-familiar voices!
Well, your faces seem to be asking
“Who’s this?” so listen up!
Let me introduce myself:
Speedwagon’s in da house!
While I’m passing down this
story to the future generations,
Since it’ll all be yours, I might
as well tell you all what’s sweet
Let me tell you what’s going
on in this era and this land
Let Speedwagon tell you
all about this era and this land!
(The world is speeding up)
(Speeding up)
(So don’t let yourself be thrown off!)
(The lamplight of the Industrial
Revolution burns bright)
(So we sleep with hope in our hearts)
Between the light and darkness!
(Should strife and inequality judge you)
(Reach out your hand to
the sunlight yellow beam)
And reach for the heavens!
(Set your soul aflame in
the beat of the steam)
The light!
(The midnight blue darkness is growing)
(Throw away your fears,
and cut ties with your weaknesses)
The dark!
(The light!)
Light and dark, illumination and shadow
Front and back, two diverging paths
Challenge your God, seize your fortune
It’s a new era, steam trains are the craze
(The dark!)
(The light!)
The factory of the world, Great Britain
The spark of desire ignites to no end
The social order got a great reset
(The dark!)
Don’t let this era
slip from your hands
(Sunlight yellow gleam,
the hymn of humanity)
Sunlight yellow!
(With voices ringing to the heavens)
The hymn of humanity!
To the heavens!
(Midnight blue darkness)
Midnight blue!
(We rip through the wasteland,
carrying our resolve)
Rip through the wasteland!
(The light!)
Newborn babes crying out
in the midst of disparity
A lineage of destiny, Phantom Blood
Fate’s thread is woven without any end
(The dark!)
And just as with any adventure of men,
Always gorgeous but bizarre now and then
(The light!)
See with your own eyes the whole venture
That’s right, this is
one Bizarre Adventure!
(The dark!)
Stop right there! I’ll kill you!
Oi!
Shit—
Oi, brat! Whatcha gonna do?
Whatcha gonna do?
C’mon, let’s go!
Nice!
Stupid brat!
Hey, look at ‘im. Bastard!
Stop!
Don’t let this brat go!
Little puke stain!
What’re you looking at, smart-arse?
Oi!
How’s your old man doing, shitstain?
I haven’t seen him since
his pub went under!
He croak or somethin’?
Word’s going around that
yer mum died in the plague!
Shame, she was a real looker!
He should have sold her off
before she kicked the bucket!
Dio! Can’t you hear me?! Dio!
What is it, Father?
Oh... Do you need your medicine?
Nah, I don’t need that.
C’mere, I gotta tell you something.
I haven’t got much longer. I know it.
I’m worried that after I die...
My only child will be all by
himself. In that case... Dio,
Oi!
Dio!
Take this.
“Joestar”?
He’s a noble.
And he owes me one.
When I die, send him that letter.
Go to him.
He’ll take care of you, you can
go to school. Sounds good, don’t it?
Oh! Make sure you put a stamp on it!
Father...
Now you start acting like a parent?!
You’re a smart boy.
Don’t lose to anyone! Become
the richest man in the world!
Dio!
Listen up...
How’s it going, I ask myself
They keep taking from me,
and it’s driving me mad
This place reeks of all these deadbeats
I might already be in hell,
the way it makes me sick
And yet, my mum told me to be noble
She held me and taught me to be proud
“Hey Dio, look up at the stars”
She kept on saying that,
until the illness took her
Just like that...
Why are my hands always empty?
Am I just here to be taken from?
Tell me, Joestar, the sky
that you have over you
Is it blue?
Tell me, Joestar
This disgraceful father of
mine, the lowest of the low
A deadbeat will always be a deadbeat
Under this murky sky,
He struggled and struggled,
and this is how he’s gonna die
Now, I’ll go take this “inheritance”
I’ll use any means, yes,
to set me on my path
I may have nothing in my hands yet,
That means I’ll start from here
Tell me, Joestar, in the sky over you,
Is the sun shining?
It is, isn’t it, Joestar?
Oh yeah!
You’ve got something good today too, eh?
Give it back!
Over here!
Hey Erina, I heard that
your old man’s a quack!
My father’s a real doctor!
Oh really? This hat looks expensive!
Stop it! It was a birthday
present from my mother!
Stop right there!
What are you doing?! Take this!
I hate when guys try to
act cool in front of girls!
Ow! That hurt!
-Hey, do you know who this guy is?
If he’s that Jonathan kid
from the Joestar family,
I’m gonna give him even
more of a walloping!
Ah-ha!
He is the Joestars’ Jonathan!
Snotty little rich boy! You think
you’re so high and mighty?
Danny!
Eh?!
Let’s go already! Shit!
Uh... Are you alright?
Leave me alone!
But...
I did this because I wanted to.
I didn’t do it to get you to thank me.
My goal is to become a true gentleman.
You were a damsel in distress,
so I had to stand up for you.
I’ll beat them, someday.
Let’s go, Danny!
Oh, wait!
Jonathan Joestar...
You...
You must be Dio Brando!
And you’re...
Jonathan Joestar?
Everyone calls me JoJo. Nice to meet you!
Ah, Danny! I’ll introduce you.
This is my friend, Danny.
He’s a clever old hound!
Oh, and don’t worry about him biting!
Friend?
Yeah!
Danny! What was that for!
Danny!
You won’t get away with this!
We’ve been waiting for you, Dio Brando.
Lord Joestar!
Come inside!
From today on, you’ll be
living here in our mansion.
Something wrong, JoJo?
Ah, nothing.
You’ve travelled all the way from
London, Dio. You must be tired.
Starting today, you are part of our family.
You’ll be given the same
kind of life as my son, JoJo.
Yes!
I am grateful for your
kindness, Lord Joestar.
Mister Brando!
I’m Police Inspector Archer!
Police? Has something happened?
Oh, no!
I’m an old friend of the Joestars.
Although, I could hear Danny
whimper a moment ago...
Ah, that was—
-He came at me so suddenly.
When I jumped in surprise,
I think my leg may have hit him!
Danny is the Joestar household’s
wonderful guard dog.
He’s a friendly creature, but
I’m sorry he surprised you.
JoJo!
You’ll let this Danny matter go, right?
Yes, sir.
Good.
JoJo has lost his mother too—
and you both are the same age!
Make sure to get along with each other.
Now, allow me to show you to your room.
Mister Brando!
Nice to have met you!
Watch it!
Don’t touch my bag!
I was just trying to carry it for—
That’s enough.
Your hand is covered in dog drool.
Pardon me if I don’t want
it all over my things!
Alright JoJo, I’ll tell
you from the get-go.
Ta-ta, JoJo!
Now then, let me get—
I like being the best!
I’m always number one!
I don’t care who you are,
no one looks down on me!
I was only trying to be friendly!
What are you two doing?
And one more thing—
I hate dogs.
The way they grovel and suck
up to humans disgusts me.
Keep your stupid dog away from me!
Coming, Lord Joestar!
Thus, with this meeting, the
two boys’ youth had begun.
Are you coming, JoJo, Dio?
Bear in mind, as honourable nobles,
We take on the duty of
becoming true gentlemen
This is why we study, acquire knowledge,
(Without pause!)
(Without limit!)
And arm ourselves with logic!
(So you’ll never lose!)
Under the guidance of
the goddess of familial love
For the sake of heading
the house of Joestar
(The honourable Joestars!)
What’s this, JoJo? JoJo!
The same mistakes once again
How many times have
you made them! Six times!
Dio has all of them correct!
It’s just because I love reading so much!
But they haven’t even
taught us this in school yet!
Bear in mind, as proud nobles,
We behave like true gentlemen
(Unfailingly!)
Under the guidance of
the goddess of familial love
For the sake of being loved as a Joestar!
(The proud Joestars!)
Sit up straight, use your knife with grace,
What’s this, JoJo? JoJo!
Do you call yourself a gentleman?
(So elegantly!)
Look at Dio’s elegant touch
(So gracefully!)
So that your mouth always remains spotless
His manners are perfect!
Take away JoJo’s plates!
You will go without dinner tonight!
Observe and follow Dio’s example
I am embarrassed by
how much I’ve spoiled you
But...
My mother taught me well. She
always made sure I sat up straight.
Bear in mind, as honourable nobles,
In our hearts we must always consider
questions of philosophy and justice
In our great England, a tale of two knights
has been passed down for generations.
One day, their master was
taken prisoner by the enemy.
The enemy was afraid of the
two knights, who had great power.
And so she gave them this condition:
“If you two will be executed in her place,
I will guarantee the life of your master.”
Here is my question for you:
-Yes, sir!
Those two knights who gave themselves
up as prisoners to save their master;
{\ T: Two knights sacrificed themselves to save their master and were taken prisoner.}
What was the first thing they
saw through their prison bars?
Was it the mud that lay before their eyes?
Or was it the stars shining above them?
What do you think?
The stars?
Or the mud?
I...
I think they were looking at the mud.
What’s your reasoning?
In the end, they had no choice
but to die for their master.
You can’t achieve anything if you’re dead.
They were looking at the stars!
They held onto their honour!
The names of those two knights
will be etched into history!
So no matter what tricks
they would have had to pull,
So what!
So what?
The way one lives, and the things
one does, those are important!
But they—
I think they should have stayed
alive and done something!
They were left empty-handed
in the end!
Such regret...
I think...
Such powerlessness...
What they saw was the mud!
Their lesson is to teach us what
we can achieve by staying alive!
They held onto their
pride until the very end!
They were looking at the stars! I think
they’re teaching us how we should live!
Listen!
You’re a noble! You have it all!
You’ve lived by taking
from those beneath you!
So isn’t it your responsibility to think
about what you’ll achieve with your life?
{\ T: So, in order to fulfill that responsibility, shouldn't we think about what we can accomplish with our lives?}
I—
That’s enough, you two.
There’s no right answer to this question.
Bear in mind—
All people live in a prison called fate
Reaching out through those bars,
Do they see the stars? Or the mud?
Either one could be said to be correct
A world without disparity, that’s sports
Where courage alone
has the chance to overturn
Get ready to rumble! Fanaticism
overcomes all differences
This is straight up religion!
If you lose, instant fucking funeral!
All eyes on are on this ritual
where triumph goes to the victor
Everyone, gather around!
The winner is a sweeping hero
Who will be declared king?!
The opening bell rings
Here comes today’s challenger!
Oi!
Hey hey, JoJo JoJo!
Right in the face! The winner is Joestar!
Our new champion!
You did it, JoJo!
Danny would be proud!
Now, who will be the next to
challenge our champion, JoJo?
Everyone listen up!
Is there anyone?
A new face has just asked to join our game.
His name is Dio Brando!
Dio Brando?
-Shall we tell our new friend
how we do things here?
Yeah! Do it!
Alright, let’s do it!
-Good!
The rule is if you get
hit in the face once, you—
Don’t worry, I played by the
same rules back in London.
That’s the bell!
-Go, JoJo!
Beat him up!
What is this move!
I’ve never seen it before!
Oi, JoJo!
That’s a hit to the face!
He lost!
Our king! Our king!
Dio! Dio! Dio! Dio!
My eye!
Guys, guys, guys!
I think my finger went in his eye.
I must forfeit my win. I have
to leave now, excuse me!
-Hey, hey!
Dio, you were amazing!
How do you move like that?
Teach me!
Guys! Ow...
Danny...
Why is Dio always trying to bring me down?
It feels like he’s invading my life.
Hey, Danny, my heart aches
And I’m filled with worry
What if I were to die today?
Would anyone cry for me?
You’re always so understanding
Thank you for staying by my side!
If mum were still here,
would it feel this way?
Would she love me this way?
You’re...
My hanky...
Oi! Thanks for bringing
my handkerchief back!
Hey, I’ll be back here tomorrow too,
So stop by again!
Danny!
Has it caught your fancy?
Please excuse me for
grabbing it without permission.
It’s alright.
They say this Stone Mask was
unearthed in some Mexican ruins.
Mexico...
Mm-hmm.
We bought it from a London art dealer,
around the time JoJo was born.
On the way back,
we had a carriage accident.
That was the time your dear
father saved us, you know.
Are you interested in it?
Oh, no. Not especially.
Uh...
JoJo is always out playing
with Danny, isn’t he?
It’s because of the trust and
friendship Danny has in JoJo.
Friendship? With a dog?
I had bought Danny when JoJo was young.
At first, he was afraid
of unfamiliar people,
And he didn’t get on well with JoJo yet.
But one time, JoJo was drowning in a river.
There wasn’t even one person
around who could hear his voice.
Just when JoJo was about to drown...
A figure, hearing his screams,
flew down to the river.
It was Danny!
He dove in and saved JoJo’s life.
Danny was brave to have risked
his own life to save another.
Young JoJo was moved by Danny’s bravery.
That’s when JoJo truly
became friends with him.
Is that so?
M’lord.
Eh? Ah, that’s right.
Friends...
Erina!
JoJo!
The two met once more!
Love! That wonderful curiosity
that guided JoJo’s actions.
JoJo was instantly
head over heels for her.
Danny!
Come boy!
Oh, you’re so clever to eat
the fruit but not the core.
Hey JoJo, what are you carving over there?
Huh? It’s nothing.
What are you hiding?
It’s nothing interesting.
When you say it like that, it makes
me want to see it even more!
You’ll just laugh!
I won’t laugh.
You’ll tell people!
I won’t tell, so show me!
I told you, no!
JoJo!
Oh, my!
Erina, just saying your
name makes me feel at ease
Any musician would fall
in love with its melody
It puts me in such a good mood
Oh!
To be laughing like this
There’s nothing but blue skies
here in vibrant Liverpool
Erina
JoJo
Our happiness is right here
The clouds are proud, and
the wind’s a little sweet
JoJo
Erina
There aren’t enough words
For these ever overflowing feelings
I want to hear your voice
say, “it makes me happy”
That would be so
embarrassing, you—
Scoundrel!
I don’t know why, but I’m drawn to you
Then find a reason,
let’s make it our reason!
Your hand,
My hand,
When they’re apart I feel so lost
It gives me a little courage
to move forward to tomorrow
Our hearts are resonating,
beating in time
Drawing us together, these
fleeting feelings surround us
It’s already this late!
We have a guest coming
tonight, I have to hurry home.
Erina!
I’ll see you tomorrow!
Yes, JoJo!
Danny!
The one I’m so strongly
drawn to, his name is...
Jonathan Joestar
Hey!
You’re Erina Pendleton, right?
I heard you were hanging
out with JoJo today.
Umm...
What do you...
He...
He did it!
I’ve got goosebumps!
I want to be just like him!
Have you kissed JoJo yet?
You haven’t, have you?
The first person you kissed wasn’t JoJo...
That’s our Dio!
It was me, Dio!
He does the things we’re too chicken
to, and with such confidence too!
You know what this sort of thing
means for a lady’s reputation, right?
Hey!
She’s—!
You bitch!
What are you doing washing
my kiss away with mud?!
Dio...
Get up, bitch!
What’re you sleeping for?
Oi, why’s the booze gone?!
Who do you think puts
food on the table? Stupid bitch!
Hey, now go buy some booze!
Father, mother’s clearly not well!
I’m sorry! Please forgive me!
Of course you shouldn’t go to the shops!
I’ve hurt you. I’m a good-for-nothin’.
Please forgive me!
She’s just fakin’ it!
In tough times like these, I’ve
gotta work for your sake too.
Please, you’ve got to get well!
-Stop it, Father!
Dio...
Mum! Mum!
Can’t you hear my voice?
Oi, you hear me?
-Mum! Mum!
The voice calling for you?
Dio boy, go and buy me booze!
But our money’s already—
Are you talking back?!
You got money from that
factory job, don’t ya?
Please, leave some money
for medicine at least!
You’re really gonna
disobey me, you bastard?
Father!
You really expect me to
work my arse off for you? Idiot!
You’re all trying to make a fool of me!
After all the trouble I went
through to nick that noble’s shit!
That’s it. That noble, Joestar.
Why don’t I send him a letter...
No...
You and I are different!
Dio...
Dio!!
Dio, how could you do such a thing?
How could you hurt her like that!
What in the world have I ever done
to you?! Can you tell me, Dio?
Dio...
You’re so amazing, so
much more than I am
I admired you!
But now there is a single
flame that burns in my heart
Dio!
Aren’t you using my name
DIO: A little too lightly?
JOJO: I’ll never forgive you!
So you’ve heard? What I
did to your beloved Erina?
-You’ve disgraced her!
DIO: I bet you’re mad with jealousy!
JOJO: This is for her sake, not mine!
I have to stand up to him, even
if I can’t beat him. I cannot lose!
Control your emotions, you’re
different from that drunken lout
On the blood resonating in my heart,
I swear to restore her honour, Dio!
I’ll put you back in your place,
I’ll teach you a lesson you won’t forget
Come at me!
This new power arising within me
It feels so good!
You’re the one who lit this fire in me
Dio!
I won’t stop beating you until you cry!
How dare you do this to me?
You miserable insect!
You scum of the earth!
How dare such scum like
you come at me, Dio!
Me, the great Dio!
What on earth is going on?!
You two! You’ll be punished for this!
Now go back to your rooms!
Dio...
That stupid kiss of yours hurt
me more than you intended!
Ah... Eri—
I feel so miserable!
I’ve never felt pain like this before...
Erina!
Erina! Did you say goodbye
to all your friends?
Yes, Father.
I’m sorry for imposing my career
on you. Even though I know you—
Let’s go.
I’ll make friends over there too.
Erina...
I underestimated JoJo.
His explosive power...
His resilience...
I have to become stronger...
So that I can become
a gentleman at heart!
I have to control my anger and stay calm...
So that I can take everything from him!
However...
What’s that noise?
Could someone be
inside the incinerator?
Are they trying to get out?!
Ah, it burns!
Danny!!
Oh my god...
Someone! Someone please help!
Seven years passed from that day
Times are changing,
the Victorian era’s flying by us
Population increasing to
the point of overflowing
Art and entertainment
are showered in praise
In the middle of this
unstoppable flow, agitation rages
The height of development,
the growth of British culture
But what goes up, must come
down. It’s only natural
That the top runners are being singled out
London’s peace has one
of its fingers broken
Chaotic days mix the old and the new
The map of London
paints a stark contrast
Just like the current state of the country
Put the focus on the
dark parts and you’ll see
The curtain of swaying inequality
In this market still
learning from its past!
You’re... You’re certain,
that it was the Stone Mask?
The one excavated from Mexico?
From Mexico, you say?
It was quite a while ago...
A while?! Could you please clarify?
Yes, I’m certain, sir.
Some gentleman’s wife
fell in love with it,
And bought it from me at a high price—
Yes!! Finally! I found it!
Now, where could I find this gentleman—
Wait a minute!
I don’t trust you...
Who the hell are you anyway?
I apologise. My name
is Zeppeli, and I’m a baron.
I came from Italy to
find the Stone Mask.
All the way from Italy?!
Yes.
Wait, he said he was
a nobleman from up north...
I’ll go check in the books!
The sun will be setting soon.
It’s better if you don’t
go beyond that street.
A fog has rolled in...
(A palpable shadow stretches over the city)
(And soon it’ll swallow the sun whole)
(Don’t let it get you,
fight as hard as you can!)
Thank you.
Just a little word of warning...
(Fog and smog cover the city,
hiding the smell of crime)
(Stretch out your hands towards the light)
(We won’t sink down to hell!)
The filth rubs off on the clean
and gathers like grime
Thrown away with the rubbish
Pressed together, our
lot gives off a stench
The sweet smell of darkness
Is comforting to us
(Something’s wrong, people
are thirsty, distorted, broken!)
(Jack the Ripper has drawn first blood!)
(Hate the poor, hate the
rich, and raise your voice)
(Gather here and now, Jacks of this town!)
(Rebellion is now!)
In 1887, in Trafalgar Square
(We raise our voices!)
(Give us equality! Work! And money!)
The rich in their ivory towers
(They look on at us and laugh!)
(Give us food! Every day! Let us live!)
(The world is ever accelerating)
Rebellion is stopped in its tracks,
blood floods the streets of London
Away from there now, in Liverpool,
seven years have flown by
Their graduation year
Their graduation? But who are “they”?
From inside the scrum
they head for victory
So dazzling, brightly
shining, a pair of stars
(Now is the time to raise our voices!)
He’s got it!
The star of Hugh Hudson, our very
own Jonathan Joestar, grabs the pass!
(He’s like a heavy locomotive!)
(One’s on his back!)
(He can’t be toppled)
(And a second!)
(Keep pushing forward, JoJo!)
(Bloody hell!)
(The pride of our school!)
(Incredible!)
(Hugh Hudson’s acclaimed JoJo!)
(And a fourth!)
(Is he finally wavering?)
Someone caught the pass!
(None other than the great star Dio)
(Dio Brando)
(Leaving them all behind)
(Once again, Dio catches the pass)
(Nobody can catch up to him)
(They move like clockwork! You’d
almost feel bad for their rivals!)
(Our school’s pride!)
(Truly!)
(JoJo and Dio!)
(In perfect harmony, they
make the best partners!)
JoJo! Your pass won’t go to waste!
Try!!
The final match of the
season ends in victory!
That was magnificent!
It was all thanks to your pass!
Dio!
Let’s go and tell Father
about it right away!
Right, JoJo?
JoJo!
Uh-huh.
Dio!
Can we write about your friendship
with JoJo for the school newspaper?
Thanks!
Let me get changed first.
Shall we go home together?
Yeah.
Time passed like the
endless flow of water
Ever since you started
calling him “Father”
I think of that word
which is so familiar to me
Seven years spent studying diligently
You’re... beautiful,
and a true gentleman
My friend, who’s always
pushing me to be better
You’ve repented for the
wrong you did to Erina
You’ve offered me a shoulder
to lean on, now that Danny’s gone
We walked this path
together for seven years
I always followed in your
footsteps, one step behind,
So why is it that I don’t
feel any friendship for you?
How are you feeling?
Well, I’m old enough now that
a mere cold can last a long time.
Sir, you’re not that old yet!
Ah, well! I’ve got some big news for you!
JoJo and Dio Brando, they...
Seem to have won!
Ah, Dio is a proper member
of the Joestar family now!
And JoJo has become
a splendid gentleman.
His recent archaeology thesis is superb!
And Dio is projected to graduate
top of his class in law school.
I...
I admire you! Back then—
My lord!
Yes?
I’m home!
Dio! Welcome back!
Ah, and JoJo as well!
Father!
Are you alright?
I can’t get rid of this cough...
Today, the doctor recommended
I be admitted to hospital.
I object!
These days, hospitals
only care about profits!
They say it’s a problem in London too.
It’s true...
I feel safer at home.
I give in.
The shaky hands and chest pain,
they’ll likely get better before long.
Enough of that. You two...
Congratulations on your victory!
What?!
You already know?
How?
Inspector Archer here told me.
How rude of you, inspector!
Huh?
We...
We wanted to see Father’s face light up...
So we rushed home!
Oh no, silly me!
I truly am proud.
I have such wonderful sons.
Especially you, Dio.
You’ve worked so very hard.
Feel free to do whatever
you like after graduation.
I was born poor...
But you gave me a chance.
Thank you.
Inspector, thank you for always visiting.
I have a busy night ahead of me, with
the likes of Jack the Ripper out there.
{\ T: With the appearance of Jack the Ripper, the world has become a dangerous place.}
But this is Liverpool!
There are men like him without
any humanity everywhere.
Now, if you’ll pardon me.
Well then, I’ll be off.
The spring mechanism only reacts to blood...
Who on earth made this...
And for what reason?
If I solved this riddle, it might cause a
sensation in the archaeology department.
If that happened, this mask that my
mother bought would have a fate of its own.
{\ T: If that happens, then there must be some destiny for this stone that my mother bought.}
This is...
Dario Brando?
Thank you again, Master Dio—
Oh, it’s the least I could do.
Thank you. I’m getting too old for this.
“Right now... I’m sick.”
“I’ll probably die.”
“My heart hurts,”
“My hands shake,”
“And I can’t stop coughing.”
Dio...
Can’t you hear my voice?
The voice calling for you?
Mum died and left me alone
Yes, alone with that piece of shit!
I endured no matter what
Yes, until the day finally came
Bloody hell! Ever since that wench
died I’ve been crumbling in debt!
I know!
You pawn this crap and bring
me back some booze instead!
My one and only memento of mum
You threw it away!
You wiped your feet with it!
I don’t bloody need it anymore!
He’s the one who killed mum
Everything’s been
taken away from me
Are you bloody deaf, Dio?!
How hellish that your blood
is flowing through my veins
I’ll bury you and this damn curse
I will take everything
into my own two hands!
I’ll stay on top, even to
the limits of my humanity
I will find the resolve, plan ahead,
And then, hiding behind a mask—
Dario Brando, my wretched father
May you rot in hell,
together with the past
A world where everything is perfect,
In the palm of your hand, Dio!
Dio!
What’s that in your hand? Medicine?
What’s the matter, JoJo?
I found this letter from your
father, from seven years ago.
It details your father’s symptoms
at the time of his death.
Huh?
Show me that.
They’re the same symptoms as my father’s.
Are you always the one who
brings Father his medicine?
What is this non—
Answer me!
What on earth are
you trying to say?!
I’m going to have this
medicine investigated.
JoJo...
If you doubt the validity
of that medicine,
Then you doubt our very friendship.
Dio,
As a gentleman,
I ask you to swear your innocence on
your father’s honour and the Brando name.
If you can swear on your father’s honour,
I’ll never speak of this again.
Swear on it.
DIO: Swear on it?
JOJO: Come on, swear on it!
DIO: Swear...
JOJO: Swear on it now!
JOJO: Can you swear on it, Dio?!
Swear on that guy?
That scum has never had any
honour for me to swear on!
Dio,
Give me the medicine back!
I won’t ever let you go
near my father again!
I’m convinced now...
That there was never any
friendship between us to begin with!
I’ll protect the Joestar family.
This is all a
misunderstanding, JoJo!
Just a misunderstanding...
Besides...
It’s not like you have
any proof, do you?
Nothing more than a flimsy theory.
Yes,
I despised my father, hated
him more than anything.
I just lost my temper when
you started suspecting me...
JoJo...
JoJo! JoJo!!
Is something the matter, Master Dio?
No...
I’m alright...
Dio Dio Dio Dio Dio!
It’s too late to turn back now.
A world where everything is perfect,
In the palm of your hand, Dio!
Father!
What’s going on, Young Master JoJo?!
-Father!
Father...
What’s all this ruckus for?
I’m going to London
for two or three days.
While I’m gone, take only what the
doctors and nurses I’ve hired give you.
Please don’t accept any care
or medicine from anyone else.
Excuse me, but—
We’ll do as he says.
I don’t know what’s going on...
But I trust my son!
Thank you, Father.
Seven years ago, this thing...
It moved in reaction to my blood.
With this...
I’ll make it appear as if he had
an accident during his research.
JoJo...
Your own research...
Will be the death of you!
Time’s nearly out, so I gathered
my resolve and took off!
Turning my eyes to the stars
and praying for an antidote
I headed for the fringe of
society, the East End of London
Now I’ve arrived here
in this town steeped in mud
Ogre Street, the place
where plagues are born
Before my eyes lies
the underbelly of society
But I have a reason why I must move forward
Even if I were to lose
this right hand of mine
I’ll look to the stars!
At long last our meeting takes place
There’s a scent in the air
and it smells like prey
Sniffing you out through the
storm someone’s making his way
It’s time for your
leader to take the stage
(Ogre Street, we devour anything we can)
(Ogre Street, here everything meets its end)
Dunno what the hell
you came here for
Bet you thought you
stood a good chance, huh?
In a moment we’ll
devour all that hope
This is Ogre Street and
we’re the ogres, duh!
Got no problem with you bein’ naïve,
I’m just showin’ you the simple reality
Hey hey hey,
how about it, rich boy?
Want a taste of the
edge of this knife?
We’re gonna strip you of all that you got
Put up a fight and your life will be lost
This is Ogre Street!
Ain’t it obvious that we’d cheat?
Us have-nots are gonna
steal your riches away!
From your life to that foolish
heart—we’ll steal ‘em away!
Tail between your legs, you can
save your own skin by runnin’ away!
Is this guy insane?!
(Ogre Street, go on and leave it all behind)
I don’t care if I lose four fingers!
(Ogre Street, we’ll even fill
our stomachs with your life)
I came here for a reason!
You said you’re fine with
losing four fingers, hah?
(Ogre Street, why don’t we
put that resolve to the test?)
Hold on! I only came here
looking for a poison seller!
Quit bluffin’! Let me have a
go at this soft little rich boy!
That’s the sound of blade hitting bone!
Made the mistake of my life, pickin’
a fight with this fearless tough guy
Countdown to my final breath—
Three, two, one!
Stop, everyone!
I, Speedwagon, won’t allow you
to lay a hand on that gentleman!
Why didn’t you kick me
with your full strength?
I came here for the sake of my father.
So in the moment I kicked,
I thought you must have a father,
or mother, or siblings too.
I didn’t want to do anything
to cause your father grief.
{\ T: That's why Kelsion doesn't want to do anything that would cause your father grief.}
Tell me your name!
Jonathan Joestar.
Mr. Joestar, if you’re looking
for poison, that’d be Wang Chan.
Be careful, he’s a crafty one!
Someone bandage his wound.
I, Speedwagon, will lead you to his shop!
Why?!
‘Cause I’ve taken a liking to ya!
(Ogre Street)
With your determination to fight
(Ogre Street, you’ve lit in
us a glowing guiding light)
(You, who have the courage)
(To see the stars down here in the mud)
(Light up the darkness with
your unwavering heart!)
Your refreshing sunlight
Brought me completely to my knees
This must be some
strange twist of fate!
Let’s toast—to our meeting!
JoJo...
JoJo...!
Dio...
JoJo has gone off to London...
Could he have died a dog’s death already?
Dio...
Or could he have found
evidence of the medicine?
Which is it?!
Dio...
Booze! I can’t help but drink!
Can’t you hear my voice?
The voice calling for you?
-Shut up, get out of my head!
You’re the only one I care about
Become the richest man!
-You piece of shit, we’re not the same!
Oi, are you listening, you stupid brat?
You should ask yer mum to hold
you by the hand next time!
Watch where you’re going, twat!
Can’t you hear my voice?
Are you stupid? Oi, Dio!
Oi! You piece of shit—
Didn’t you hear me?
Can’t you hear my voice?
You filthy old tramps with
no sense of personal hygiene...
Are you stupid? Oi, Dio!
How dare you! You bastard!
What did you do to my mate?!
One man’s misfortune...
I’ll kill you!
Is another man’s fortune!
Interesting, this is a good
opportunity to try it out!
You’re my clever boy!
What’re you mumbling about?!
It’s a live human experiment!
Dio Dio Dio Dio Dio!
JoJo!
I’ll find the answer to your
research myself right now!
Dio Dio Dio Dio Dio!
What...
What—
[AZTEC CHANTING]
What is this light?
Was I hallucinating?
He’s dead...
The spikes pierced so deep into his skull,
it must have killed him instantly.
{\ T: If you get stabbed in the head with this much force, it's only natural that you'll die instantly.}
This mask is just some ancient
sacrificial torture device.
He’s not dead!
Fangs?! What is he?!
I’m thirsty, thirsty, so thirsty!
He’s sucking my blood!
His face is...
Becoming younger?!
I don’t want the morning sun
to be the last thing I ever see!
I was saved...
By the sunlight...
He turned into ash...
Ow!
So this...
Is the power of the Stone Mask.
So, where is Dio?
It seems he hasn’t come
home since last night.
I’ll call for reinforcements right away.
Please use the foyer.
Thank you.
-You there!
-Sir!
This Asian fellow,
Wang Chan—take him away.
Yes sir!
Oi, come on!
JoJo...
I apologise.
This is my cross to bear.
What?
If only I had made sure
that man was exiled...
Dio’s father...
Dario Brando.
What do you mean?
I’ll tell you about it.
This happened when you were a baby.
This is certainly my ring,
But I never reported a theft.
I arrested the man who
was caught pawning it.
Lord Joestar had that ring specially made
as a pair for his and his wife’s engagement.
It was obvious that it was stolen!
Yes, it’s the ring I had made with my wife.
When Lord Joestar thought about his wife,
Tears welled up in his eyes.
I...
I arrested the criminal!
Would you like to see for yourself?
Stealing from a noble is a heavy offence.
He’s certain to be exiled!
I see.
Here he is! Oi! Wake up! Brando!
Brando?!
Oh, bollocks.
Then that means—
Dario Brando isn’t some saviour,
But a thief!
Even knowing this,
Lord Joestar adopted Dio.
Why?
I...
I was moved to tears by
what Lord Joestar said next.
Did he tell you...
That I gave him this ring?
Yes, he said that. A lie!
It’s not a lie.
This is what I gave him.
He is innocent.
But it’s a memento of your wife!
Mr. Brando,
This is yours.
With this ring, please buy
what you need for your family.
Lord Joestar! Are you taking the piss?!
If I were suffering from poverty
I would have done the same
thing, yes, for the ones I love
When the stars in the sky
shine, they start to tell a story
Let’s pray that this light
will illuminate the darkness
Thank you, sir!
You are too good-natured!
This scumbag will laugh at
you tomorrow morning!
That may be true,
But think about it the other way around.
From the prison called fate,
people reach for the stars
Let’s embrace that courage,
that loneliness,
That pain
Everything is connected
There’s a meaning to it all
I believe in humanity
and all of its resolve
I can’t see stars or nothin’!
That’s bollocks!
That’s why...
I’ll keep on believing
That this gold I’ve passed on
Will shine one day
With all of my resolve...
I will defy fate!
Inspector.
I’ll wait for Dio.
He can still be stopped.
I heard a bizarre rumour on the streets.
It’s said that a vagabond shattered
a wall with his bare hands.
And then...
When the morning sun hit the man,
he turned to ashes and vanished.
It’s the same as what
happened 30 years ago...
It’s a wedge driven into
the wasteland of my memory
At dawn, a blood-red sun
rose over the Atlantic Ocean
Full of passion and yearning
for the unknown world
I crossed the seven seas
with my respected father
My beloved father, the voices
of my friends, my youth
The Stone Mask took
everything away from me
I swore I’d get revenge,
that I’d take it all back
Maybe not today, but
there’s always tomorrow
Yes, tomorrow...
“A man is what he thinks
about all day long.”
There’s a saying that goes like that.
The Stone Mask...
If I don’t find it, I can’t
recover what I’ve lost.
I, Dio, was...
Shit...
JoJo...
I see you’ve returned from London—
I have the antidote now.
It’s a shame it had
to come to this, Dio.
It truly hurts me.
Although you might not believe me,
Those are my true feelings.
I understand, JoJo.
You’re honest like that.
Although it’s selfish,
I have a favour to ask—
The final one
I will ask of you.
Can you give me more time?
Time—
To turn myself in to the police.
Eh?
I...
R-Regret the choices I’ve
made throughout my life.
Because I was born into squalor...
My ambition was relentless.
What I did was terrible!
I want to repent for my sins!
Don’t believe a word he says!
I can see from your face that
you’re wondering who I am.
Allow me to introduce myself!
I’m Speedwagon, the meddler!
Growing up in the darkest slums,
I’ve met all sorts of horrible
people throughout my life.
So I can tell all I need to know
about a person just from their smell.
This guy reeks!
Worse than vomit!
He was born evil!
Mr. Joestar, you should call
for the police right away.
This man has confessed already.
Father...
I’ve heard everything I need to.
I will return to my bed to rest.
I don’t want to see my son
being taken away in handcuffs.
Come on—
JoJo, I understand!
You won’t succeed in arresting that man...
Arrest me.
He was born with an innate destiny.
Silence!
But, if it’s not too much to ask;
I want you to be the
one who handcuffs me.
For the sake of those seven
years we spent together.
Be careful!
Agreed.
I will handcuff you.
To be human is to have limits
That’s what I’ve come to realise
And still the more I try to plan,
The more I see the limitations of this life
What’re you talking about?
You know, JoJo...
This frustration, it’s unbearable
I’m always coming up empty-handed
This prison I’m trapped in,
it’s slathered in mud
I can’t see the stars, and no
matter how hard I struggle,
My eyes are still blinded
Don’t you get it?
That murky sky up there,
It’s crushing me!
I can’t reach up this way
Yes, Joestar, even
your purest pedigree,
Can’t wash the filth out of mine
That’s why, now is the time
To break free, from this cage
The stars!
The Stone Mask?
And seize...
I...
Stop!
-JoJo!
-Father!
I...
Dio!
Reject...
My humanity!
JoJo!
JoJo...
Dio!
This is...
Shoot him!
Your late mother’s ring.
A doctor’s coming, he’ll save you! Hold on!
Lord Joestar!
Please... don’t blame Dio for this.
Hey—a doctor! Call a doctor!
Father! Father!
Maybe... the fact that
I was so hard on you...
Made him feel like I was
treating him differently.
Father...
It’s not so bad...
JoJo...
To die...
In my son’s arms.
Father?
How could this be...
I knew I made a mistake, back then.
Now he’s dead and there’s
no bringing him back.
Mr. Joestar...
You always told me to be a gentleman
To always live with pride
Even though I said I’d save you,
Even though you said you believed me!
I couldn’t protect you—
How could I be so powerless?
What does it mean
to be a gentleman?
Father, open your eyes!
What’s pride worth now?
What’s the purpose of
This Joestar blood
flowing through my body?
You always remained a
gentleman, until the very end
Carrying yourself with
discipline and pride
Your resolve to shine a beacon
through the dark wastelands
I’ll accept it all, and
look up at the stars
I’ll engrave your will into my soul
Take pride in this heart
that shines like gold!
It will become the future,
sent up to the stars
This Joestar blood
flowing through my body!
Everything is connected,
there’s a meaning to it all
I’ll fight against this fate,
keep sorrow at bay
With just one drop of courage!
Inspector! It’s an emergency!
What’s wrong?
The body... Dio’s body is gone!
What?!
What did you say?!
Oi copper, get away from the window!
Inspector!
What the hell?! He came back to life!
Even though we shot him into Swiss cheese!
Be careful! He’s got some kind of weapon!
Dio!
Stop!
Shoot him! Don’t just
stand there! Quickly!
I don’t get it! I can’t make heads
or tails of what’s happening!
JoJo!
Can you hear my voice?
H-He’s sucking his blood!
You’re—
JoJo...
I’ve gained such incredible power!
From the Stone Mask...
From your father’s blood!
Dio!
These monsters are
making more monsters?!
Run away, Mr. Joestar!
You’ll only get killed!
That monster is too bloody strong!
The brain!
That mask must have drawn out
an unknown power from his brain!
If that’s the case...
I’ll have to completely destroy his head!
Stop!
Speedwagon!
I must...
I must make my will stronger!
JoJo!
Weak! So weak!
Mr. Joestar!
Let me...
Let me enjoy this amazing power
for just a little longer!
After all, I still don’t know
what I’m capable of yet!
JoJo...
Stop this useless struggle of yours.
I told you, didn’t I?
No matter how many
tricks you come up with,
Humans have limits!
Quit hiding behind that
curtain! Come out here!
You and your friend
can become my lifeforce!
Dio!
This isn’t a “trick” I’m using to stop you!
It’s courage!
This fire won’t kill him.
Speedwagon, escape from the mansion.
What?
Mr. Joestar!
Don’t run upstairs!
(The flash of flames,
illuminating the dark)
Come, Dio.
I’m up here.
Is that an invitation, JoJo?
Very well, I’ll take care of you first
(The flash of flames,
scattering the light)
I’ll put an end to you and
your cursed powers here!
It’s useless! Useless! Useless!
I’ll suck you dry!
(The flames are pulsing)
JOJO: Father! I’ll mourn you
DIO: I offer you my thanks
(Flickering from light to dark)
JOJO: Please give me strength
DIO: For giving me strength
I always walked in your shadow
You were always right behind me
My youth was with you
It’s time for us to say goodbye to it
JoJo!
The Joestar manor is burning
And Father is dead!
I’ve lost everything, save for my life
I’ll let that burn to ash too.
I’ll stop you, Dio!
Mr. Joestar was surely thinking,
That a stronger fire could overpower
that demon’s healing ability.
{\ T: The stronger the firepower, the more the monster's recovery power can't keep up.}
“If only the flames were
even hotter!” But by then...
The fire had already engulfed the
mansion, even overtaking the roof.
Damn it! Mr. Joestar!
This body is immortal.
The only one dying will be you!
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
(Equally doling out love and judgement)
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
(Equally doling out love and judgement)
-JoJo!
I won’t let go of this knife,
The knife you stabbed Father with!
It’s useless! I’m immortal!
With this final bit of strength
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
(Equally doling out love and judgement)
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
(Equally doling out love and judgement)
This can’t be how my life ends—
JoJo!!
Can you hear me?
You can hear me.
Good.
I hope you had a nice intermission.
I’ve returned in order to
continue telling our story,
Of the world to which all of
you have become witnesses.
And so that we can continue our
show of love for these characters.
I want the whole acrylic stand collection.
Just a few more until it’s complete!
I hope you get the merch
you’re looking for too.
Well, let’s continue where we left off.
The story up to this point
seems like a bit of a fairytale, but...
Make no mistake, it’s the truth.
Things are going to get more
and more bizarre from here on out.
Yes.
Much more bizarre.
Previously, the mansion was
shrouded in flames and burnt down...
But Mr. Joestar survived.
He beat Dio,
But lost everything.
Three days later...
I found it!
The mask that man wore!
If I have this mask—
JoJo...
JoJo, can you hear me?
My voice calling for you?
After carrying the unconscious Mr. Joestar
to the hospital, I came back to visit him!
I’m not much,
But I want to do what I can at least,
To give him some small
hope to keep on living!
Can I help you?
This room doesn’t allow visitors.
But that’s why I’m here!
I’m doing enough for him as his nurse.
Please come back some other day.
Is he alright?! Oi, hold it—
JoJo...
Can you hear me?
My voice,
You recognise it, right?
From that bright, fleeting moment
when we were drawn together
I want to hear your voice again too
Where am I...?
You slept for three whole days!
The mansion! Everyone is—
Please, just relax for now!
You’ve made it through the worst
of it, but you’re still in bad shape!
I’m so glad you’re alive!
Have you been caring
for me this whole—
You’re—
No, it couldn’t be.
But you look like...
Look like who?
Like Erina Pendleton?
It’s been a while, Jonathan Joestar.
How?
This is my father’s hospital.
We moved to India seven years
ago, and just recently returned.
It’s really been too long.
I was weak back then,
I couldn’t run to your side
I was childish back then,
I couldn’t face you
Your voice is still the same
My feelings are still the same
There’s nothing but blue skies
here in vibrant Liverpool
Erina
JoJo
Our happiness is right here
The clouds are proud, and
the wind’s a little sweet
Erina!
Oh, I’m sorry! I must have
lost my focus and fainted.
My goodness, you caught
me with your broken arm!
I’ll always be there to catch you.
When our
Eyes meet
I can see it there
That little bit of courage
to move towards tomorrow
Your hand
Meets mine
I can feel you there
Our fates entwined forever
Now our hearts
resonate, beating as one
Drawn together on that fleeting day
We’ll continue from there
Just the two of us
Fate? That’s right.
Maybe some people are
just fated to meet one another.
Speedwagon coolly withdraws.
Extra, extra! Read all about it!
He’s struck again,
that bloodthirsty maniac
It was the same method, another woman—
Her throat was slit
(And she had her guts ripped out!)
The utmost cruelty!
No known motive at all!
The truth of the
matter is out of reach!
(Like it’s made of fog)
(Don’t go out walking at night!)
(You’ll be killed! He’ll find you!)
(The plague of London,
that bloodthirsty killer!)
(Only killing prostitutes,
throwing their guts up on the wall)
(Only found in fog and
darkness, that’s Jack—)
Jack the Ripper!
You’re kidding!
Oh, it’s already so late!
I have to return home soon...
It’s not late at all!
But we might run
into Jack the Ripper!
It’s a terrifying thought!
Terrifying, is it?
It is!
Well, as a matter of fact...
You’re talking with him right now!
You’re out playing too late,
You dirty harlot!
Who goes there?
You...
I like you.
Now that you’ve seen me, I’ll—
I don’t feel any pain, I’ve
got nothing to fear anymore
I’ve been reborn, now’s the
time for my life to start!
Oh, I must heal these wounds,
and for that I’ll need lives!
Not to mention a
faithful servant—Jack!
Don’t you want power?
(Power and pleasure!)
This I will grant you!
(Wry! Wry!)
Humans are bound by notions of virtue.
They fear that which is spectacularly evil.
However, very rarely there are
those not constrained by goodness.
Those are the evil elite.
Like myself, and you as well!
How about it? Will you
become my, Dio’s, companion?
What do you know about me?!
I understand you, Jack.
You’re angry at them, right?
Those women who
indulge in pleasure
Women who are
dripping with ecstasy
Go and spill more guts! There’s
no need to be afraid anymore
Me, afraid?!
(Power and pleasure!)
That’s right!
(Wry! Wry!)
Jack! You don’t have
to worry anymore
I’ll give you pleasure greater
than you’ve known before
I’m not scared of anything!
Break out from the narrow
confines of your prison
You—
Come to my side, Jack the Ripper!
Take my hand!
Who are you?
Seeing stars, or seeing mud?
We’ll change the tune of
that tired old philosophy!
I’ll start to live from this moment on
A life that forsakes the sun!
(Blood, flesh, devour it all!)
I don’t need it anymore!
(Blood! Flesh!)
This is Dio’s World!
The Stone Mask...
I want to believe it turned
to dust like everything else.
Yes.
It has to have been.
It’s alright.
I’m alright.
Let’s go.
Eh?
What’s wrong?
Who’s that?
Has he been here
this whole time?
Jonathan Joestar!
And Miss Erina Pendleton.
You’ve done well to survive
the power of the Stone Mask!
The Stone Mask?!
JoJo!
(Pow!)
Squeeze out
Every last ounce
Of air inside your lungs!
How could you, he’s injured!
What?! My broken arm—
It doesn’t hurt anymore!
I am Baron Zeppeli!
Courage alone won’t defeat
the power of the Stone Mask
I am on your side!
I manipulated your breath, your
breath made the pain go away
I am your ally, Jonathan Joestar!
Who are you?
What did you do to me?!
How do you know my name!
Hey JoJo, one question at a time!
I’ll show you the answer,
just come along with me
If you do, your fate will change
Whether you accept that or not
The choice is up to you!
What will happen now?
Let me demonstrate for you
The power that this breathing awakens!
(Breathe in, breathe out)
(In, out!)
(Pow!)
With this special breathing
(Pa-pa-pa-pow!)
You carry special oxygen
(In, out, in)
In the blood it sends racing
All throughout your body!
(Pow!)
And energy is born!
(Pa-pa-pa-pow!)
Its name is—
(In, out, in)
Ripple Energy!
(Memetaa!)
[TN: Sound of a frog being punched]
The ripple’s power
passes through the frog
Making this miracle happen—
That is the power of the ripple
The power this breathing
infuses into your blood!
(In, out)
Breathing?
Everyone has a little bit of energy
flowing through their bloodstream.
It does things like carry nutrients
and regulate your body temperature.
The power of the ripple gathers that small
amount of energy from all over the body.
This is made possible by the rhythm
of a particular breathing technique.
Breathing created that power?!
Yes! The power of breathing!
In, out!
Yes, I know it all
They’re two sides of the same coin,
this breathing and the Stone Mask
So too are you and Dio!
Dio!
Yes!
The mask is not broken—he has it!
The man wearing the mask, Dio,
walks in the darkness even now!
I’ve travelled the world
Pursuing the mask
So that I can destroy it!
Dio is alive?!
(Pow!)
We must fight!
(Pa-pa-pa-pow!)
We must destroy it!
(In, out, in)
And you must wield this
ripple energy, or you will die!
That’s right, your fate,
and the fate of the world
(Pa-pa-pa-pow!)
It has been set in motion!
(In, out, in)
I finally found it!
Will I get my hands on it? Our fates
Are all tied together. This is—
(In, out!)
Destiny!
To fight... That is my destiny!
Mine and Dio’s!
The Stone Mask’s bone needles
draw a strange power from the brain,
That turns humans into vampires.
Beings who must get energy
by taking the blood of others.
However, the ripple also derives its
power from the flow of the bloodstream.
It’s the same energy, like
two sides of the same coin.
Ah, let’s put it this way.
What must you do to stop that ripple?
I think I’ve got it!
Use a ripple!
If you hit them with another
ripple, they’ll break apart!
And that wave of energy
Has the same shape as the light of the sun!
You see?
The power to defeat Dio!
We’re already out of time.
You must learn how to turn
your courage into power!
JoJo?
What do you mean, Dio?
Erina...
I can’t get you involved in this!
For now, please just go along with it!
I swear I’ll come back here again.
How...?
Is this the power of JoJo’s ripple?
The clouds are drifting by
and the wind is swirling round
Leaving memories behind
I nodded along, to your resolve
To the sorrow you held
Stars are drawn together
Guided by this hapless fate
As I wander here, mired in mud
I am left behind
I live in a dream,
waiting by the window
Tell me, why am I left in solitude?
Even if it doesn’t reach you,
even if it won’t bring you back to me,
I want to scream!
Because you left for my sake
You are drawn to me
Forever guided by fate
I’ll live my days, spinning its thread
While looking up at the stars
Waiting right here
So that one day you’ll tell me the story,
I’ll keep living with pride
I’ll accept every part of you
So that I can call this
destiny one of love
Yes, so that I can call it that
Guided by this hapless fate
JoJo!
Stars are drawn together
Our stars shine together
No matter where you are, I will, I will,
I will live on!
Wang Chan, you’re alive?!
Yep!
C’mere!
Why are you so strong?!
Don’t tell me... It’s
because of that damn Dio!
Speeeedwagon!
You know too much about
the secret of the Stone Mask!
JOJO: Stop right there!
Mr. Joestar!
I wa-ha-ha-was looking for you too!
Because, because Lord Dio
said I could slurp up your blood!
Licky licky? Licky licky!
Licky licky! Licky licky!
Lickithan Joestar.
JoJo, be careful.
He’s strong enough to rival you.
What was that, you old fart?
Old fart?
Time for a taste!
His arm... got longer!
It’s useless.
I’ve been given new life!
And a body that transcends humanit—
That’s not what’s important here.
M-My body...
It’s hot!
What the—it’s hot! So hot!!
Ah! Wait!
It’s amazing!
In this short time, you’ve
learned the ripple so well.
What’s wrong, JoJo?
I lost so much...
That’s why I wanted power.
But not this...
Not the same as Dio’s!
Yours is fundamentally different
from those who gain power by stealing!
But it’s the same power!
There’s a saying in the
northern country of Norway:
“The north wind created the brave vikings!”
Because they knew the pain
of the harsh northern winds,
They became vikings with backbone!
You are different from Dio and his ilk!
Because you feel the pain.
Pain...
The pain of losing friends
The pain of inheriting your family’s pride
Even for those you want to protect—
Pain is proof they’re alive
You need to listen to that pain!
I was always told to be a gentleman
Forever walking in my father’s footsteps
I still don’t understand what
it means to be a true gentleman
But the Joestar blood
resonating in my heart burns hot
The Stone Mask bursts with light
Staining the darkness red
So that this tragedy will never repeat
We embrace this pain
It was pure coincidence!
I was the one who excavated
that cursed Stone Mask!
What was that?!
It’s a wedge driven into the
wasteland of my memories
My father and I once
crossed the seven seas
One quiet and calm night
The mask burst with light
And all 58 men of my
crew were massacred
Mr. Zeppeli!
The man in the mask came forward
ZEP: Clothed in blood and darkness
JOJO: The same as it was then!
What I saw in that moment, illuminated
by the salvation of the morning sun, was—
It was my father!
Under the red light of the
morning sun, my father disappeared
My soul’s clock has been
frozen in that moment ever since
We embrace this pain
ZEP: I’ve been chasing after it
JOJO: So that it won’t repeat
ZEP: I swore to take revenge
JOJO: I won’t let you down!
ZEP: So that tomorrow will be
JOJO: Shining bright
We embrace this pain!
What you need is the courage
to make that pain your own!
And the resolve to face the consequences.
JoJo!
Hey JoJo.
JoJo JoJo JoJo.
Ha-hey JoJo.
Hey-ha-hey-ha JoJo.
Don’t forget this goal.
Yes, sir.
I believe in the power of the ripple.
Yep.
I like your fringe.
JoJo!
Hey JoJo, JoJo!
Why, why?!
Jonathan Joestar!
Lord Dio! It hurts! Where are you?
Are you angry?
You’re good company, huh?
Oh! It burns! It burns!
My body, it—
Is that Mr. Horse?
Look Wang Chan!
Your, your ancestors—
Clippity clop, clippity clop!
There he is.
The lovable sweetheart, Mr. Joestar,
has finally got a handle on the ripple
Hey yo yo! We’re coming
to collect payment
These bills been piling piling up
Your underworld rep, AKA
Speedwagon, is here to give a full report
Who else would be your guide
To this 16 bar showtime?
South of London, in total daylight,
We drove, no stopping sites
When we pass through this
tunnel, you’ll see the sights
That famous city of knights
This is Windknight’s Lot
A natural fortress like an augite rock
Windknight’s Lot
Fate’ll have it—Dio’s hideout
While the sun’s out
We’ll knock it out
Clean this vampire nest out
Ay, Dio, dick, you make me sick
You play with life, that’s bullshit!
No more tomorrows Dio, that’s it
Now’s the end, ya gonna get hit!
Thanks for keeping watch, Speedwagon.
My underground sources say that
Wang Chan definitely fled here.
Without a doubt, this is where
Dio is building his own empire.
It’ll be better if we search for
them while the sun is still out.
The entrance to the town
is through this tunnel.
Yes, we’re arriving according to plan.
Oi, driver, why are we stopped here?
Whaaat?!
Be careful! The sun doesn’t reach here.
L-Look!
T-The horse!!
What is he...
He’s inside the horse’s body!
Give me a little taste of your fresh blood!
Mr. Joestar!
Stand down, you two.
I will fight!
JoJo, here’s a battle lesson!
You’ve heard of fleas, yes?
They come after us humans
even though we’re giants to them.
Could you call something
like that “courageous”?
What are you yammering on about!
So then, what exactly is “courage”?
“Fear” sends your breathing awry!
Surrendering to that fear
throws your breath out of sync.
The ripple breathing technique
is a product of courage!
The hymn of humanity
is a song of courage!
The greatness of humanity
is the greatness of courage!
These zombies, no matter how
strong, know nothing of courage!
They’re just like fleas!
Hot, so hot!
How dare you! I’ll kill you!
Yes... I’ll eat every
shred of you in one bite!
There’s a hidden passage in the tunnel!
Windknight’s Lot...
I’ve heard it has many tricks, because
it was once a training ground for knights.
There’s also a vast catacomb underground.
They’re inviting us. We must go farther.
Yes. Dio’s surely at the end of the trail.
Can you hear me?
Sleeping knights...
Follow me, serve royalty once again
Get your revenge on the past,
let’s rewrite history
Upend righteousness,
go for total victory
That’s this world, the
unwavering world of Dio
This is Dio’s World!
Your long silence has
left this world to rot
Now raise your voices,
from crushed throats
Crying out from the mud,
conquer the stars
I’ll allow you this and more!
(My sword, it’s yours!)
(Now is the time to raise our voices)
Wrrryyy!
(We’ve been sleeping for 300 years,
us rotten and forgotten corpses)
Wrrryyy!
Get your revenge!
300 years asleep, haunted
by painful thoughts
(Wry wry, we vow to kill!)
(Wry wry, we vow to destroy!)
(Wry wry!)
Wait, Dio!
Come quick, JoJo.
(Wry wry!)
My world is in the palm of my hand now!
(Wry wry, we vow to kill!)
(Wry wry, we vow to destroy!)
I will dominate life at last,
Tearing its natural
order from God’s grasp
I will dominate history too,
Rewriting and upending it anew
I will dominate even time,
My body eternal and sublime
(Eternal life!)
I will dominate everything,
rise above all my cares
(We vow to steal them away!)
Win it all, negate righteousness
In this peacefully unaware country
(This country is ours!)
I will dominate everything,
I’ll face them now
And demand peace of mind!
(Wry wry, we vow to kill!)
My world, this world!
(Wry wry, we vow to destroy!)
Wry wry!
This is Dio’s World!
It’s melting...
It’s really melting away...
So much that there’s a hole in my cheek...
My tongue is sticking out of the hole!
Your cheek is melting,
And your tongue is sticking
out of the hole? Really, Jack?
Dio!
Oh, it really is.
The sun has set.
It’s time for your lives
to go down with it!
I’ve been building up my
courage for this moment!
Even so, I can’t help
this feeling of dread.
As a human, I can’t let
you get away with this!
JoJo!
Put your training to use.
(We’ll feast! On your blood and flesh!)
(Steal it away!)
(To heal all of our wounds!)
JoJo, here’s a lesson for you
The north wind made the vikings!
This battle will be an exercise—
You’ll defeat them without spilling
a single drop of wine from this glass!
SPW: We’re not here to play around, have you lost it?
ZEP: You shut your trap!
The north wind made the vikings!
JACK: I’ll kill them!
DIO: Ah—wait, wait—
Tough vikings were born
from the harsh north wind
Will this wine make a viking out of you?
(Give us your blood!)
Make fear your own!
Here’s a battle lesson:
Muster up your courage! When the time
comes, don’t let your breathing go awry!
The hymn of humanity is a song of courage!
The greatness of humanity is
the greatness of courage!
Everything is connected!
There’s a meaning to it all!
Don’t let your breathing go awry!
(Wry!)
This wine will be my north wind!
(Give us your blood!)
The ripple of the wine!
(We’ll feast on your flesh!)
I can feel it flow, I’ll find my
way through the darkness!
The waves of the ripple!
(Give us your blood!)
Are resounding through my body!
(We’ll feast on your flesh!)
With the power of the sun!
Find your way through the darkness!
Oh, my heart resonates!
Pa-pow-pow-pow with unrelenting heat!
(Heat!)
Sunlight...
(Sunlight...)
Yellow...
(Yellow...)
Over...
(Over!)
Sunlight yellow, sunlight yellow
Overdrive!!
The ripple of the sun! Dio!
This is the power
that will defeat you!
Dio Brando?
Yeah?
I don’t know you, but...
Let me say this to the Stone
Mask that awakened your brain:
Finally, we meet.
Don’t get carried away!
Perhaps you can heal this
wound in my stomach, JoJo.
You’re the one who put it there!
Then I’ll be completely healed from
the damage you dealt me in that fire.
I’ll be using your lives...
To purge this wound!
You bastard!
Just how many lives did you
extinguish to heal that wound?
Do you remember how many slices of
bread you’ve eaten in your lifetime?
I’ll make you submit!
By the ripple of the sun!
Pow!
Utterly pathetic!
It’s freezing?!
I guessed that this energy of yours
is related to the flow of your blood!
I am able to control my own body at will.
If I freeze up all of your veins,
Then you won’t be able to use that power!
I can’t—I can’t catch my breath!
Mr. Zeppeli!
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
Breathing techniques? Ripple?
If you’re going to be
blowing all this hot air,
You ought to use it to
play me a little fanfare!
Looks like your companions
are just as weak as you.
JOJO: What did you say?
DIO: Companions...
That’s right. Do you remember?
The story of the knights
your father told us that day?
What?
The tragic queen who was sentenced
to beheading by Elizabeth the First,
After a failed assassination
plot in the 1600s...
Yes!
We listened to it together, didn’t we?!
Mary Stuart!
It was about the ones who served her!
The story of those two proud knights...
Father told us...
JoJo, Dio!
I will regale you with
a tale of two knights,
Which has been passed down for
generations in our great England.
Those who lived with a gentleman’s spirit—
This is a story of knightly pride!
Long ago, 300 years before today
Two queens battled for the throne
One was Queen Elizabeth the First
And the other, the beautiful Mary Stuart
Two legendary heroes came forward,
Offering up their swords to serve Mary
Tarkus’s strength cleaved
through rocks like butter
Bruford, with his skill and spirit,
cut down foes like a phantom
Without any family, the
two honed their powers
While wishing for a nest to rest in
After finding peace in Mary’s affections,
They swore their loyalty to her
But one day, Elizabeth
accused their master, Mary,
Of murdering her husband,
and she was captured.
The two heroes would not rest
When it came to saving their Mary
In order to stop those two heroes,
Elizabeth made an appeal:
“You two, surrender at once!”
“And I will spare your master’s life!”
This, we cannot refuse
In this, we hold no regrets
For our queen is our life!
But in the moment they
were to be executed—
I’ll give you a little souvenir
before your trip to Hell!
Your master isn’t being held in the tower.
I cut off her head myself just yesterday!
Look at her lying over
there like a piece of rubbish!
After all, if she was left alive,
we’d risk a rebellion!
You’ve betrayed us, Elizabeth
We curse you with our grudge!
We curse you for all eternity!
Stiff with rage, Tarkus’s
muscles were like iron
They couldn’t cut through his neck!
Bruford, filled with regret,
ensnared them with his hair
As though it were alive!
And that is the story,
Of those knights who lived
according to their hearts
Until the very end!
Such blind devotion—
it gives me goosebumps!
Oh, what loyal hearts!
But those two should
have done a better job!
In the end, they couldn’t do
anything from down in the mud.
The only thing to call
their deaths is useless!
It might be as you say, however—
There is nothing that is without meaning.
The same can be said about the
fact that you came here to this house.
Everything is connected!
I want to believe that they
kept on looking at the stars!
All people live in a prison called fate
Reaching out through those bars,
Do they see the stars? Or the mud?
Either one—
JoJo
Dio
Could be said to be correct!
I turned those two
Into vengeful revenants that
would send even the devil running!
Even history bends before me!
It can’t be!
Such grotesque forms!
It’s the perfect form for
taking their revenge!
Don’t you think so?
Kill them all!
Continue from where
you left off on that day!
Tarkus!
Bruford!
Play me a fanfare with their screams!
Our grudge!
Our pride!
Great Dark Knight Bruford!
And you, Tarkus!
The way you feel—
Your pride, your resentment.
Mr. Joestar!
Alright, go ahead!
We’ll duel as knights!
Run away, you two!
Tarkus!
I can’t even imagine it!
I won’t let you interfere!
But I also bear my own burdens!
I’m gonna be the one to eat ‘em!
My master—I, Bruford,
I’ll savour every bit of his cartilage!
Would like to be the one to bring
an end to this brave man’s life!
That man’s pride...
I will stand to meet it, as a knight!
A wedge driven into the
wasteland of my memory
At dawn, a blood-red sun
rose over the Atlantic Ocean
Old man!
Don’t come any closer!
Damn it...
Fucking hell!
There’s nothing I can do,
I’m a mere spectator
I’ve got nothing, I’m powerless
Come on, get real,
even at a time like this?
Even if I give up, the pain
will just be for another day
And tomorrow, yes tomorrow,
I’ll still be over here crying like a loser
Honourable knight,
Is revenge your answer?
Is that what you take pride in?
If you want to preach, then fight
with your pride on the line!
You can lecture me after you win!
Now’s the time, to let
courage resonate in my heart
I’m not scared of pain
I must find the strength to stand up
Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow,
Tomorrow is right now!
Old man!
Melt!
I didn’t follow you to
become a hindrance!
Speedwagon...
I’ll let courage resonate in my heart
And look the enemy in the eyes
Won’t wait for a distant tomorrow
I’ll start walking,
Find the strength to
get back on my feet
Tomorrow is now!
JoJo!
Cut finely, beat of my blood!
Please... This knight’s proud heart,
Let it somehow be restored!
I am the Dark Knight Bruford!
This pain means nothing to me!
Why aren’t you moving?
Just now,
Pain?
That’s why...
You said “pain”.
That means that now,
You can feel pain!
Pain...
I stopped fighting you.
That’s why you stopped your sword.
You are a great knight.
You are human!
Is proof of life!
So this is what it means to be human?
Because of this pain, I can also feel
the joy of being alive in this moment.
I feel a bizarre sense of peace now.
Bruford...
I dedicate to you the word
engraved in my sword.
Luck!
And also...
Pluck!
To think, I had to kill him
in order to save his soul...
Damn you!
JoJo!
I can’t believe you actually
defeated the Dark Knight!
Just as I thought...
I, Dio, will—
Hey baby!
I bet the blow from that
ripple-charged flower must hurt!
What the...
Your ripple is more vulgar than frog piss!
Watch out, Mr. Joestar!
What an embarrassment of a knight!
He never got his revenge!
What did he have to be joyful about!
JoJo!
No!
How could you!
For victory!
I take pride in victory!
Fuck!
I’ll get you!
I’ll get you for this!
JoJo...
JoJo!
My final ripple...
My... dying wish is...
That you take my ripple
and continue on, JoJo!
He collapsed.
I’ll vanquish your wicked soul!
Drown in the murk of history, Tarkus!
Old man!
Mr. Zeppeli!
If we lose you—
There’s no time to be sad.
The Stone Mask must be destroyed!
Old man!
I...
I lived my own life to the fullest.
In the end,
I leave everything I have to you.
JoJo,
You are my hope.
Once again, life is
spilling out of my arms
You showed me my purpose
Who I am meant to be
You taught me that humanity’s
greatest gift is courage
The light you’ve given
to me will shine through
Into my spirit
It felt like...
I had a friend and a son
in you at the same time.
From here on...
I live within you.
JoJo.
Everything is connected
There’s a meaning to it all
That’s what I’ve come to believe
Even this pain...
Even this pain
My father left to me
what you leave to me now
The golden light that
shines from within me
It’s the one thing in my heart
that I can hold on to now
I embrace it tightly
And from this prison...
I see the stars
A golden spirit
Humanity’s glow in the darkness
Will light up
The way to you...
Dio!
Light up the way to you...
JoJo...!
Dio...
Can’t you hear my voice?
The voice calling for you?
I can’t hear you
Dio...
I already killed my past
Don’t call my name—
You and I are different
We’re not so different, you’re my son
I have changed into something new
You’re not so changed,
you did it to survive
I’ll use any means
DIO: I’ll steal it all
DARIO: You’ll steal it all
DIO: Upend righteousness
DARIO: You’re my clever boy!
DIO: I will conquer it all
DARIO: What will you want next?
DIO: I will dominate everything
Go ahead and dominate,
what will you want after that?
What do I want?
DARIO: What do you want?
DIO: What do I want?
I want...
Dio... Dio...
So you’ve come...
JoJo.
Is this...
The world you wished for?
What?
The world...
That you’ve been trying
to obtain for so long...
Surrounded by death...
It’s a pitiful world, isn’t it?
It’s a splendid world where
I’ve dominated everything.
{\ T: It's a wonderful world where I control everything. Even death and history...}
I’ve dominated death, and even history too.
For that reason, you stole
from uninvolved innocents?
They were a noble sacrifice for
the sake of the future that I designed.
You’re just afraid.
Of being human...
That’s why you rejected your humanity.
For the sake of obtaining this world...
I’ve transcended humanity!
You ran away from it.
The ends justify the means.
I will win,
And that means conquering
everything, of course.
All of this is fate!
No!
This is just how you
chose to live your life!
Opposing fate...
What will your legacy be?
Such righteousness!
Just like the one who gave me this power...
And then died!
Just like...
Your father.
That’s right.
As a gentleman, it pains
me to say this, but...
Now I, Jonathan Joestar...
For the sake of revenge...
Dio...
I will kill you!
We’re one and the same; you want
to exact your revenge! I admire that!
No! I’ve come to right your wrongs!
I’ve accepted this as my legacy!
Speedwagon!
Right!
Ironic, isn’t it? Now
you’re the have-not, JoJo!
I’ll suck you dry
Become my next meal!
I’ve lost so many loved ones but
their light lives on in me, Dio!
I’ve come to cleanse
your corrupted ambitions
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
I obtained this power
My heart’s aflame
So I could steal everything from you
I’ll dull this pain
If you think about it, you’re just like me
You were just like me,
two sides of the same coin
Like fire and ice, my body is burning
JOJO: I’ll kill you
DIO: You’ll kill me
JOJO: You’ll kill me
DIO: I’ll kill you
Just like Mr. Zeppeli taught me!
I’ll channel my ripple through this sword!
You did it! You defeated Dio!
Not a chance!
You fools!
What! The sword is freezing—
Utterly pathetic!
Mr. Joestar!
JoJo!
Utterly pathetic! I’m grasping
your carotid artery, JoJo!
With this, you’ll become
one of my undead servants
Ironic, isn’t it, Dio?
Just as I thought, you were
running away from humanity
Why don’t you freeze me now, Dio!
My fist... Just from hitting him!
I transcended humanity!
None of you are on my level.
You’re nothing but a monkey, JoJo!
JOJO: No, for as long as I have faith,
DIO: Compared to me, Dio!
DIO: Let’s test your willpower
JOJO: I will reach you!
As long as we have faith, we can grow
JOJO: Us humans...
DIO: To be human is to have limits
JOJO: That’s what he taught me
DIO: You can’t reach me!
Like fire and ice
DIO: I’ll chip away at this body to prove it
JOJO: I’ll burn up this body to prove it
He put his hand in the
fire! If he does that—
Like fire and ice
My lost friends, my father’s spirit
JOJO: Our connection, it’s here
DIO: Even when I’ve thrown away my humanity
Like fire and ice
With my life on the
line, I’ll prove it now!
-Dio! Dio! Dio!
-JoJo! JoJo! JoJo!
“I was only trying to be friendly!”
“I like being number one!”
“My eye!”
“I think my finger went in his eye.”
Dio!
I won’t stop beating you
until you’re finished!
This is impossible!
The heat is coursing through me!
I’m melting!
Crumble to dust!
I can’t be...
Not yet!!
Watch out! He’s shooting
hot liquid out of his eyes!
Lord Dio...!
Dio...!
Extra, extra! Read all about it!
(In 1888 on December the 4th)
(The London Press reported)
There was a small incident
(In Windknight’s Lot)
(That little village, there was
a missing persons incident)
A very bizarre case
73 people vanished
In just one night,
they abruptly disappeared
Moaning could be heard from underground
But no one was found
(In 1888 on December the 15th)
(In the Windknight’s Lot Paper)
An eye-witness reported
That the following day, below a cliff
Men were seen burning clothing
(And destroying something with a hammer)
It seemed to be a stone mask
(In 1889 on February the 2nd)
(In the announcements section)
(The Joestar heir)
(Jonathan Joestar, of Liverpool, was wed)
(To the Pendletons’
daughter, Erina Pendleton)
In a small notice, they announced:
The honeymoon would be a trip
to the United States by steamer
(Now, on to other news...)
Mr. Joestar! Both of you!
Best of wishes!
I’ll always be there for you!
If you’re in trouble, I’ll rush anywhere!
Happy honeymoon!
I can’t wait to hear all about it!
America, how nice!
I wanna go there too,
And try to dig up some oil for myself!
Damn it...
But after this, a fateful
moment was soon to come...
This story will be passed down
until the world has come full circle.
That will be the life’s work
of Speedwagon the meddler...
But, the one to tell you what
happens right now won’t be me...
I pray that today will never end
In the midst of a carousel of stars
Let my hand always be in yours
What’s wrong?
When you’re next to me...
I have lured him here.
I’m happy!
I feel the same.
I wish you could’ve met my father...
Well, let’s go and eat!
Jonathan?
That’s...
Erina,
Go back to our cabin.
Don’t forget to lock the door!
My body...
Have you come?
Dio...
JoJo...
I dare show myself in this pitiful
state in front of you for a reason...
I used to despise you so much,
But now I respect you...
That’s because I’ve realised something!
If there is a God that controls fate,
Then there’s never been a relationship
orchestrated as perfectly as ours...
You’re the reason I got this power,
And you’re the reason why...
The world has slipped from my grasp!
When will it...
Be enough for you?
That’s exactly what our destiny is!
I’ll obtain the body of the one and
only person I respect in this world.
And live in eternal glory!
JoJo...
You and I...
Are one and the same in this world!
Lord Dio! Look, look, look!
Please look!
Jonathan!
From light to darkness
I will end it all
This is the start of my mythos
And restart it all
For this is Dio’s World!
Right, Erina Joestar?
Dio!
I can’t speak—can’t breathe—
My ripple!
Erina! Not you too!
This is the start of his mythos!
This ark is swarming with his followers!
Please, spare the child!
Run!
Shall we torture him to death?!
Or maybe enjoy watching him asphyxiate?!
Wang Chan!
Painlessly cut his head
from his shoulders!
I won’t tolerate any insults!
My friend, Jonathan Joestar—
I’ll take you as my own
Your blood will become my future!
I’ll tie our futures together
With my final ripple!
JoJo!
I felt it tear. Something
important inside me just tore
Jonathan!
ERINA: How could this be?!
JOJO: Get out of here!
I won’t, JoJo...
I will burn with you
Until everything turns to ash
(The flash of flames)
Everything is connected
You can’t ask me to live!
There’s a meaning to it all!
JOJO: It’s alright if you cry
ERINA: Your courage is too cruel!
JOJO: You will be
ERINA: I will be
The one to spin the thread of fate
(Flames are burning everything up)
Just like my mother
died for me, I’ll—
(Light and darkness flicker and flash)
(Flames are burning everything up)
Farewell!
I’m still alive!
In the end, I, Dio, will triumph!
(Light and darkness flicker and flash)
JoJo?
My mythos begins here
JoJo!
You would strike...
Before I...
Lost consciousness.
I know what you’re like...
I figured...
Let me go, JoJo!
He’s...
Dead...
[AZTEC CHANTING]
That proud life of his
Vanished into the dusts of time
But this fateful adventure
Will become an inheritance
Passed down forever
His golden spirit
(Phantom Blood)
Like two who make one,
We feel a bizarre friendship
Isn’t that right, Dio?
If it weren’t for you...
No, it’s because of you
Hey, JoJo
Now I’ll...
Keep looking at the stars
Guided by this hapless fate
We’ll reach out to the stars
Our two fates
Have become one
(That immortal poem echoes quietly)
Until the world
(One saw stars)
Is born anew
(The stars are shimmering)
(Like blood through a vein,
mud is pulsating)
I’ll live
(One saw mud)
I’ll disappear
JOJO: With you!
DIO: I will live!
(The sunlight yellow gleam shines)
(Let the golden wind blow)
(And the shadow of midnight
blue darkness grows)
(Living in the shadow of history)
(We’ll stop the flow of time)
(Even when the world resets)
(The tale will keep on being told)
(This bizarre adventure)
(Our golden spirit will shine)
Speedwagon coolly withdraws.
Thank you for coming
to today’s performance.
This is a public [streamed] performance.
Since it’s my and Zeppeli’s actor,
Hirose Yusuke’s, final performance,
We each wanted to say a
few words if you don’t mind.
Take it away, Mr. Hirose.
I had the honour of performing the double
cast role of Zeppeli. I am Hirose Yusuke.
Thank you for today.
The musical will close tomorrow, though.
This type of role has been
played by others before,
Although personally, I
found that to be relieving.
There have been many
things that led to this day.
So even now, I have a lot of
thoughts and a lot of emotions, but...
Aside from that, the fact that we
have come this far is really thanks to...
Each and every one of the cast members
on this stage, and the wonderful and skilled staff.
And foremost, the people
who came every day—
You’re not coming every day?
Well, every day—
Truly a lot of fans came
and filled the whole theatre.
I would like to think our performance’s
quality is thanks to your support.
Truly, you’ve made each member of
this performance happy. Thank you.
From the bottom of my heart,
Pow.
MAMORU: From the bottom of the heart, pow!
Well, I played the role of Jonathan
Joestar, I’m Matsushita Yuya.
Thank you for today!
Did you have fun, everyone?!
The best, hearing this is the best, yeah.
Uh, right. Really, tomorrow’s
truly the final performance.
That curtain call will
be the grand finale, too.
I think that Shotaro will
do perfectly tomorrow.
I—are you worried?
Nah, it’s probably okay.
-I’m worried, so please do the speech instead!
-He’s—that’s in the past.
Yeah, no. Anyway I think he’ll be fine.
I wanted to voice some
personal thoughts here.
First off, as Mr. Hirose said before,
It’s been a long road to
arrive at our final performance.
And I’m relieved that we made it.
Truly, I’m truly happy to
be on this stage. Thank you!
Back in February, right?
Opening night was delayed.
But when we made it to opening day,
At that curtain call, really, at that time,
the audience cheered and applauded a lot,
Which has continued up through today.
Truthfully, at that time, I was feeling, within
me, that we became something unforgettable.
Yes, that’s right. Truly,
thank you for everything.
For having supported us up to this point.
And to Mamo, who supported
me like a partner in this.
Isn’t it seriously amazing that
he did this role without a double?
MAMORU: It’s alright.
YUYA: No, it was wonderful.
Before you even started,
I almost cried when I saw your face.
Yeah, me too a bit! I got emotional!
MAMORU: Yes.
YUYA: Sorry, I had to excuse myself.
Excuse yourself...
YUYA: It wasn’t because of you or something like that that I left.
MAMORU: I get it.
Nah, you were really incredible.
Really spectacularly incredible.
MAMORU: Not at all.
YUYA: No, no, I’m sorry.
It might be unusual for a performer to say this,
but I truly respect you. Really, you’re wonderful.
MAMORU: No, no really.
YUYA: I thought he really rejected his humanity.
You were just that wonderful.
[INAUDIBLE]
MAMORU: Thanks.
YUYA: Yes. So then...
We’re not on the same stage
tonight as we were then, but—
From the first day of rehearsals until now, he’s
supported me, helped me improve, and encouraged me.
Shotaro too. I truly believe that without those
two, I would never have achieved this JoJo.
So, this has been my first time
acting in a double cast performance.
Thank you everyone in the cast!
It was wonderful. Thanks!
And above all, above all, truly,
thank you for being devoted like this!
Now to everyone at the theatre,
And everyone watching the stream,
I don’t know where the cameras are but—
Thank you from the bottom of my heart!
Thanks!
I was already so relieved that
I could raise my voice today.
Yes, and tomorrow Mr. Hirose and I will
be watching the final performance together!
Everyone, do your best!
I’ll be giving it my all along with you!
Everyone, make sure
to—what are you saying?
I’m doing it! I was
just getting to it, okay?!
I’m gonna watch it too!
Yeah, I’ll watch too.
Pardon me.
And so, please support everyone
through tomorrow’s final performance!
Truly, thank you for today!
[TN: Everyone’s muted for about 2 min]
[INAUDIBLE]
MAMORU: It’s already over.
Thank you! Thank you!
Definitely, please support
tomorrow’s performance too!
Shotaro, do your best tomorrow!
MAMORU: Do your best!
Thank you!
MAMORU: Thanks!
Brought to you by Ossan Subs
Transcription & Translation
Bug, FlanPucci, Jama Kitten,
Kitkuni, S_Mage, and Twincam
Proofreading
Bug, FlanPucci, Jama Kitten, Kitkuni,
Mayo, Ne0ntetra, S_Mage, and Twincam
Subtitling
S_Mage and Jama Kitten and Juels
Special thanks to our wonderful
Japanese friends who helped us along the way!