hard
This is also on screen and can be spoken about.
It's okay. It's okay.
You have been chosen.
Yes, you guys.
I decided it was trustworthy.
Time has started to move again
after standing still for 49 years.
That is why I have to
create this record now.
If something should
happen to me, I—
That is why I have to
create this record now.
This record must be kept.
Back to the story.
No, let's get back to the topic.
As you all know, this foundation
was created to support various fields,
All with the goal of contributing
to the welfare of humanity.
Medicine, government studies, high school studies, etc.
There is a secret to why I established
this foundation here in the USA,
And created our branches around the world...
Please listen carefully.
I founded this foundation here in the United States.
And created our branches around the world...
That secret is...
The Stone Mask.
The mood is,
The true purpose of the foundation
is to solve the secret of the Stone Mask.
And also to tell you the story
of the golden spirit I once knew.
That’s why I’m here today, to leave
behind a record of the tale of that mask.
It all began in the 13th century.
And also to tell you the story
of the golden spirit I once knew.
It all began in the 13th century.
It all started with the 16th generation.
Deep in the Central Mexican Plateau,
a tribe was raising a battle cry.
They were members of the
people of the sun—the Aztecs!
About once in Afteka.
Dear Osamu,
Blessed man,
Eternal! Power! Eternal! Life!
Shalt thou become our life?
The power in this hand
(With pleasure!)
When will it be time to breathe history?
(For us Aztecs, life becomes power!)
(We, Aztecs, have drawn the sun’s wrath!)
Widespread
The mystery of this disappearance
lies in the Stone Mask.
This is the story of how the Stone Mask
Became entwined in the
unfortunate fate of two young men.
Bloody hell! This rain is awful,
it came outta nowhere!
1868 Years Old Ronto's son
Watcher!
It's Ikeame
I won't leave again
I have to apologize for doing it
I'll finish you up, Ikeri
Today is
I'm sleepy
That carriage has gone and wrecked itself!
-Wait!
No one’s swarmed it yet! Alright!
First come, first served! Let’s go!
Everyone's still gathered
It's coming
The first person will go
Darling, wait! We really
shouldn’t be doing this!
Look at that fancy carriage,
they gotta be nobles!
Yahoo!
Hurry, hurry
Wooooooooooooo!
This bloke must’ve died instantly.
I'm sorry for not being friendly with you
Look at that! What a
pretty necklace! All mine!
It’s a treasure hunt! C’mere and look!
What the—
This box’ll have somethin’ good...
Oh, it's in this box. It's the next best thing.
Don’t need that!
One man’s misfortune is
another man’s fortune!
The valuables are gone, Yuriya and I are scared
Aren’t these nice teeth?
They’ll fetch a pretty penny.
Look, find it
Just one night
No thanks
You... Did you rescue us...?
She croa—
Passion
Oge
Did you buy it?
Your wife has already passed away
it seems, but your child is safe.
So this too is fate...
What about Red?
Morning
I helped
Is this also a dream?
Race saved my life
My name is
Used
I don’t have a fancy name, but
please call me Brando.
Dario Brando!
Ah, Dario, beat Brando!
It’s an era filled with frenzy.
(Like the ground before a storm,
we’re thirsty with desire)
Let's talk, it's terrible
I'm getting on well
Their hands were reaching out!
(The era is changing, and now is
the time to make ourselves rich)
The times have changed them!
(In sunlight yellow day, with pride
in our queen, we pierce the horizon)
(In midnight blue darkness)
When will ordinary darkness come, I'm waiting
That voice, even
A suspicious voice
Speedwagon’s in da house!
Press the middle button and listen carefully
Let me explain
Kupy's Wamoerea
This More Gutary
O'Cataly
Why does Tsugumono
Let me tell you what’s going
on in this era and this land
Let Speedwagon tell you
all about this era and this land!
(The world is speeding up)
(The lamplight of the Industrial
Revolution burns bright)
Between the light and darkness!
(So we sleep with hope in our hearts)
Hakumeyuno
This is so nostalgic
Color is important
Oath hai ga ga
(Reach out your hand to
the sunlight yellow beam)
Sugar block
I was born now
The light!
Skill Reference
Love, if you will
Failure
A lineage of destiny, Phantom Blood
This is my place, just mix it up
, properly 'me' no more
Fate’s thread is woven without any end
And just as with any adventure of men,
Always gorgeous but bizarre now and then
That’s right, this is
one Bizarre Adventure!
Untied umenoita
My friend's bouquet
what is it
How do you feel?
merged e me
Congratulations!
Behind me,
I'm in a car rush
yeah
oh!
Oi!
Stop!
Killing him!
Hey!
Makusuki!
Nice!
Makusu!
ah!
oh!
What should we do?
Don’t let this brat go!
Go!
nice!
Oi!
This idiot
oh!
At this level, the arrow of life is returned!
Word’s going around that
yer mum died in the plague!
White mountain.
He should have sold her off
before she kicked the bucket!
I don't want that to happen!
What is it, Father?
He should have sold her off
before she kicked the bucket!
Oh no!
Nah, I don’t need that.
What's wrong?
a
Medicine
I haven’t got much longer. I know it.
Oh no
I know
Hey
Since I disappeared as a new
Take this.
Oh, dear dear dear dear
And he owes me one.
He’s a noble.
Okay?
When I die, send him that letter.
Go to him.
Oh! Make sure you put a stamp on it!
He’ll take care of you, you can
go to school. Sounds good, don’t it?
Father...
Oh! Make sure you put a stamp on it!
Listen up...
Now you start acting like a parent?!
Dio!
You’re a smart boy.
Seriously to no one
Don’t lose to anyone! Become
the richest man in the world!
Dio
They keep taking from me,
and it’s driving me mad
How’s it going, I ask myself
Stolen
Keep going
That's right
Unbeatable
I feel nauseous
It's hell now
Hakie wo Moyoko
I might already be in hell,
the way it makes me sick
She held me and taught me to be proud
Nedio
“Hey Dio, look up at the stars”
She kept on saying that,
until the illness took her
Why are my hands always empty?
openly
Am I just here to be taken from?
What a star
Tell me, Joestar, the sky
that you have over you
Is it blue?
It happened
Blowing in my ears
The worst father
A deadbeat will always be a deadbeat
Under this murky sky,
I was already running and dying
Let's receive Issan now
Use all
I may have nothing in my hands yet,
That means I’ll start from here
It happened
You have it
Tell me, Joestar, in the sky over you,
That's it.
Usually
It is, isn’t it, Joestar?
Hey Erina, I heard that
your old man’s a quack!
My father’s a real doctor!
Stop it! It was a birthday
present from my mother!
Oh really? This hat looks expensive!
Stop right there!
What are you doing?! Take this!
I hate when guys try to
act cool in front of girls!
-Hey, do you know who this guy is?
It's Jouster Keljouna.
More copy and copy parts under the eyes.
He is the Joestars’ Jonathan!
It's Kanemochiki Day for both of us!
Eh?!
Let’s go already! Shit!
Uh... Are you alright?
I did this because I wanted to.
I didn’t do it to get you to thank me.
My goal is to become a true gentleman.
You were a damsel in distress,
so I had to stand up for you.
Someday you'll be able to win.
Oh, wait!
Ah, wait a minute!
Jona-san Jowstar.
Okay, let's go!
You must be Dio Brando!
And you’re...
You're Diopransola!
That's you, Jona-san Jouster.
Everyone calls her Chocho.
Oh, and don’t worry about him biting!
Danny!
Let's go.
We’ve been waiting for you, Dio Brando.
friend?
Lord Joestar!
What are you doing?
Gyul-san!
You’ve travelled all the way from
London, Dio. You must be tired.
Starting today, you are part of our family.
You’ll be given the same
kind of life as my son, JoJo.
I’m Police Inspector Archer!
I’m an old friend of the Joestars.
Jowstar, thank you for your service today.
BLADDOG!
-He came at me so suddenly.
police?
Is something wrong?
Danny is the Joestar household’s
wonderful guard dog.
He’s a friendly creature, but
I’m sorry he surprised you.
That was sudden!
He’s a friendly creature, but
I’m sorry he surprised you.
JoJo has lost his mother too—
and you both are the same age!
He's quite friendly, but it was great that he surprised you.
Make sure to get along with each other.
Now, allow me to show you to your room.
Nice to have met you!
Please get along well with each other.
Now, let me show you to your room.
BLADDOG!
JoJo!
Don’t touch my bag!
Your hand is covered in dog drool.
Pardon me if I don’t want
it all over my things!
I'm driving.
Alright JoJo, I’ll tell
you from the get-go.
What are you two doing?
Listen, JoJo.
And one more thing—
The way they grovel and suck
up to humans disgusts me.
I hate dogs.
One more thing.
Thus, with this meeting, the
two boys’ youth had begun.
Thus, the two proofs met and the two players began.
Hitaka Jojo.
Dioc.
Okay?
I aye raa
The same mistakes once again
Still no good, get it on your hands.
Dio has all of them correct!
Wait and see next time
No matter what, I want to do it to you
Being reborn and illuminating
It’s just because I love reading so much!
But they haven’t even
taught us this in school yet!
This is the sixth time
All of the answers are correct.
We behave like true gentlemen
This much
It's still not easy to play,
Ikane
We are
Here as a high memory
real
Check it out
What’s this, JoJo? JoJo!
Pesh thing
I almost believe
Do you call yourself a gentleman?
Nothing is always
Without passing by the beauty
Look at Dio’s elegant touch
His manners are perfect!
To be loved
Really high
Azukasa
a little bit
nevertheless
Do you believe it?
Look at it
I'll tell you
Perfect supporter
Shockley, too.
Aventine
That's it
Riwo
I don't see it
I
Embarrassing
You
I was spoiled
Such
My mother gave it to me.
always
Correct the festival
Ikane
We are
Were you born?
As a memory
Philosophy
However,
The exit
Always in mind
And so she gave them this condition:
There are two models
One day
Their master
By the enemy
Captive
It became
Here is my question for you:
Huge power
have
The two models
fear
I put forward the conditions
Instead
You guys
Once menarche occurs
Was it the mud that lay before their eyes?
Life is
To try to guarantee
where
Or was it the stars shining above them?
yes
To save my master
What do you think?
Captive
The stars?
Or the mud?
Railway City
First
What I'm looking at
Or the mud?
Or
I think they were looking at the mud.
Shine
want
I wonder
What’s your reasoning?
think
I wanted
Draw?
I
Draw
I think...
Why
They held onto their honour!
Death unexpectedly
They were looking at the stars!
If I die,
They held onto their honour!
So what!
Even if you put down the work
Alive
Something
Nasaneba and
But they—
I
The way one lives, and the things
one does, those are important!
But they—
They were left empty-handed
in the end!
But they—
It's a kiss
In history
What they saw was the mud!
So
How did you live?
How it happened
Cherish it
They held onto their
pride until the very end!
They
Listen!
Nothing in hand
Not included
Listen!
解鋼
Helplessness
They
What I saw
It's a draw
They
Teaching
Alive
What
I—
That’s enough, you two.
There’s no right answer to this question.
you
It's a rule
There’s no right answer to this question.
Bear in mind—
I'm alive
If so
To fulfill that responsibility
Alive
What to do
Shouldn't you think about it?
I
Both of them
That far
Reaching out through those bars,
Either one could be said to be correct
Is that okay?
People
Either one could be said to be correct
live
So
Reach out
What you can see is
Do you want
Or
Which one
Both
To the correct answer
Lyrics
Everyone, gather around!
The winner is a sweeping hero
moreover
I came with you
Eskikar
Who will be declared king?!
a lot
The opening bell rings
Here comes today’s challenger!
Shukyo
Hey hey, JoJo JoJo!
yes
Basso
Everyone
That far
Hey hey, JoJo JoJo!
That's how we deal with each other
Who
Decide who is the king
Return
The conch sounds
Today's Challenge
So
Come out
What is this move!
I’ve never seen it before!
With this rail, it keeps coming out!
It's Hong!
It's Feeket!
Yay!
Nodknocky!
That’s a hit to the face!
Ah...
Our king! Our king!
My eye!
Hey, how are you?
D ص PAR!
Ichikowa
Everyone! Everyone!
My finger seems to have landed in his eye.
Why is Dio always trying to bring me down?
So why don't you stop!
Hubber, everyone!
For some reason, Dio is trying to get me to fall for him.
I feel like I'm being trusted more and more
Would anyone cry for me?
I'm full of anxiety
If mum were still here,
would it feel this way?
Would she love me this way?
Thank you for being by my side
If I had a mother, would it be like this?
Is this how you loved me?
Hey, I’ll be back here tomorrow too,
My half
Has it caught your fancy?
Please excuse me for
grabbing it without permission.
It’s alright.
Are you curious?
That was the time your dear
father saved us, you know.
I don't care
That was the time your dear
father saved us, you know.
Mekishiko
When girls were just born
JoJo is always out playing
with Danny, isn’t he?
It’s because of the trust and
friendship Danny has in JoJo.
I had bought Danny when JoJo was young.
Are you interested?
Aie, nothing in particular
that
And he didn’t get on well with JoJo yet.
Danny's attitude towards women
There wasn’t even one person
around who could hear his voice.
Friendship Is it a dog?
Just when JoJo was about to drown...
I won it.
A figure, hearing his screams,
flew down to the river.
But one day
Danny was brave to have risked
his own life to save another.
Young JoJo was moved by Danny’s bravery.
That’s when JoJo truly
became friends with him.
Young JoJo was moved by Danny’s bravery.
Eh? Ah, that’s right.
Is that so?
Danny's spirited actions
A young woman
Danny's feelings
The two met once more!
Since then they
JoJo was instantly
head over heels for her.
Dangaso too
ah
it was
Believe
Butterfly
The two resumed
love
Hey JoJo, what are you carving over there?
It’s nothing interesting.
What are you hiding?
I won’t laugh.
Danny
Be well behaved
You eat in separate scenes
Erina, just saying your
name makes me feel at ease
no
Nothing
Why hide it?
Any musician would fall
in love with its melody
You'll laugh
I won't laugh
It puts me in such a good mood
Any musician would fall
in love with its melody
Oh!
butterfly
Elina
Just call
Erina
Relax
What kind of music
The sound
Our happiness is right here
What's going well
already
Laugh like that
Morning or quite
Bab
There aren’t enough words
Elina
butterfly
For these ever overflowing feelings
The wind is a little sweet
butterfly
Elina
I'm short of words
Scoundrel!
Overflowing
forever
One word
I'm happy
Then find a reason,
let’s make it our reason!
Your hand,
Here
tickles
Your hand,
People who can't hear
I don't know
I'm being asked by you
Put on Jariun
Our hearts are resonating,
beating in time
Hands and
My hands
Touching
be confused
Towards tomorrow
It’s already this late!
Erina!
surely
compete
Hawatsu
Preconceived notions
The one I’m so strongly
drawn to, his name is...
Because a customer is coming today
I have to hurry back
Elina
see you tomorrow
Huh, okay?
Huh
compete
Suyoku
you
What do you...
Isn't that right?
Ugh
It's Erina Pendleton.
Today is
With my superior
They were just playing
that
something
wall
Ugh
Udo Yaa
It was me, Dio!
Cling
today
What can't be done on broken ground
Do a transformation and get out
I can see it locked there
What are you doing washing
my kiss away with mud?!
Not yet
My first partner is not Chojo
Dio...
If it's ratey, what does that mean?
Get up, bitch!
This guy!
Oi, why’s the booze gone?!
What’re you sleeping for?
Wow!
What's going on?
Of course you shouldn’t go to the shops!
Who is responsible for Peter's food shortage?
Namaruka
yes
Please, you’ve got to get well!
Can’t you hear my voice?
Please give me an illustration that doesn't look like a kaza.
Dio boy, go and buy me booze!
The voice calling for you?
Izawa Hiamatress
宙zech
You go buy some alcohol
Already money
Eni
The alcoholic beverages have arrived.
You and I are different!
at least
Eat money to buy medicine
Your mouth is big
How long will I remain?
I thought he was shy, but
Magara
Crack
Well, my breasts are always twisted and swaying.
I noticed it too early and stepped on it
Yes, it's Joes.
If you see a hand
Follow
I am
With you
Haa
Aren’t you using my name
Hurt her
Haa
Aren’t you using my name
So you’ve heard? What I
did to your beloved Erina?
Why?
Oh
Haa
-You’ve disgraced her!
Much more than me
I respect that.
Only in my heart
One thing is for sure
There is something burning
Oh no
Haa
Many people's names
Easy to wear
A small person
I heard that
My love
you
Kyusana
I'm the one
I don't care
nine
Haa
Stand up to it
No shoulders
this
It feels so good!
Oh
Emotions
Dominate
You’re the one who lit this fire in me
Slippery Heart
Her name
Get it back
Oh no
Generation rate
Battle
I won’t stop beating you until you cry!
Oh no
Haa
you
I miss you
Get to know
That's a good impression.
Haa
You scum of the earth!
You
Me, the great Dio!
Only
Oh no
You
Until Naku
Me, the great Dio!
Lost
Don't bend
Haa
often
too
To me
Bukase
surely
Konoha
Better
Like this
Like winning
Cheap
This me
this
That stupid kiss of yours hurt
me more than you intended!
Like this
Like winning
Cheap
This me
This suits you
Haa
One
What's going on?
Both of them
Give a penalty
Go back to your room
Haa
So that I can take everything from him!
He looked down on women.
His explosive power
I need to develop that mental strength even more.
So that I can hold my head high in faith
I need to calm down and control my mind more.
What’s that noise?
But
What's that sound?
Is there anyone in honesty?
Are you going to try to go outside?
Oh my god
Someone please
Hmm
The one excavated from Mexico?
First place
Bistriest
Ride behind
Aprekaeru Korori
A while?! Could you please clarify?
Timekeeper Piakorak is a building star
No one can stop us
Some gentleman’s wife
fell in love with it,
And bought it from me at a high price—
Some gentleman’s wife
fell in love with it,
Chaochao
Wartwack Osaka
Top Runner
Cattrell Dawser
Now, where could I find this gentleman—
Wait a minute!
Port Levy
Same as the current situation in Maldea
Who the hell are you anyway?
I came from Italy to
find the Stone Mask.
All the way from Italy?!
Stone Turtle
I’ll go check in the books!
All the way from Italy?!
Wait, he said he was
a nobleman from up north...
Just a little word of warning...
But there's no doubt about it
The sun will be setting soon.
I hate it
It’s better if you don’t
go beyond that street.
Okay
I did it
I bought it
in
Where is Soroshinshi now?
It seems a bit suspicious
Generally you
What is it?
This is a gracious
My name is
Seteri
It's a downshake
By the stone turtle
I'm from Italy
(And soon it’ll swallow the sun whole)
Like I said
I'll do some research
Please wait
April
Ha
I'll give you a little China.
Will the sun soon set?
You'd better not go beyond that street.
Kiri appeared
The sun stops
Until then
When I'm in town
topknot
Please drink it
I don't know you
Kiritomo Sky
Not yet
chase
Second-rate
Reach out your hand
Is comforting to us
I don't want to fall
Laughter and no laughter
Mix it up
Drinking stops
Thrown away in the dump
Better
Talking about Autumn
Legs
This darkness
Worth going
Something's wrong
I'm sure it's because I'm dry
Until then
surely
Itchy
give
Kisakisa
Seriously awesome
Hated and scorned
Hateful Agebokoe
Right now
Their graduation year
Magical
That's it
Inagein
Ageing
Save Trafalda Stare
I can hear
Iodine
He’s got it!
Canelo
Kirino
Shokiri
Kirashiyo
Firmly
Red
surely
Kobotuya
The flow also came
That's it
Kut
Hii
butterfly
Trafalda
Nun
Choyo
Firmly
Red Ant
So
Sasa is
What is it?
Woah!
Hey
Oh
Uuuuu
The final match of the
season ends in victory!
Dio!
That was magnificent!
Silence
It was all thanks to your pass!
Night night night night night Shalal ...
Let me get changed first.
Just a little
The best thing about bad behavior
Chochocho Maca's family car
Time passed like the
endless flow of water
I think of that word
which is so familiar to me
a little bit
It's on the bottom right
Thanks to your parts
First, let's tell Dad about this victory.
Magician's Palace
Thanks to you
In the school scene
Seven years spent studying diligently
thank you
Please change your mind and wait for me
My friend, who’s always
pushing me to be better
You’ve repented for the
wrong you did to Erina
Time passed
You
With Dad
Since I started calling
To me
Those familiar words
think
7 years
I always followed in your
footsteps, one step behind,
You are
beautifully
It was believed
Make my Elio come true
Friends
think
Elinae's
Ayamachi
You are
I was eating
Danny's replacement
You are
How are you feeling?
Your back
7 years
Where
walked
However
Why am I
To you
JoJo and Dio Brando, they...
Thanks to
How do you like it
His recent archaeology thesis is superb!
I admire you! Back then—
teeth
My lord!
Yes?
ah
That's quite something
Skilled
Dioplant
Father!
I can’t get rid of this cough...
Dio is already one of Joestarke's
Joe was Dibbala Singh Singh
They say it’s a problem in London too.
I feel safer at home.
I give in.
Danda-sama
I just got home
Dio is back
And Jojo too
You already know?
My sanity won't stop
Inspector Archer here told me.
I'm against it.
Hospitals these days are all about making money
I truly am proud.
I have such wonderful sons.
There was a time
The swelling in my hands and the pain in my chest will subside.
Congratulations to both of you on your wins
But you gave me a chance.
I was born poor...
Cave
we
Inspector, thank you for always visiting.
I have a busy night ahead of me, with
the likes of Jack the Ripper out there.
I'm here
Really big nose
wonderful
There are already few
Especially Dio
You did really well
After the measures
Be what you want to be
To me, born of poor origins
Give it a chance
thank you
Who on earth made this...
And for what reason?
thank you
The spring mechanism only reacts to blood...
Who on earth made this...
If I solved this riddle, it might cause a
sensation in the archaeology department.
anywhere
Like that guy
If that happened, this mask that my
mother bought would have a fate of its own.
So
do
staff
It's a living mechanism that responds only to
“My heart hurts,”
“And I can’t stop coughing.”
If you do that
Also for the shape
There's something destined
I am
Dario Pland
I'm always sorry
Rio-san
About giving medicine
Speed
thank you
I
I don't want to take a picture
I endured no matter what
perhaps
Yes, until the day finally came
My heart hurts
Hands waving
The stone won't stop
My voice
A voice calling you
My mother died.
Two of my fathers
yes
Those shoes and
What
Pawn
It has changed
yes
Until that day
He died.
Zexal
I’ll stay on top, even to
the limits of my humanity
Yes.
How to fight him
Right now
Lowering scum
Battle and
Aha
Hardness
Threw it
Assembled
Because I don't need it anymore
The match is
Without love
A world where everything is perfect,
Stolen
Shall I enter?
Name
It's different
In the palm of your hand, Dio!
Flowing
This hell
Zexal
white
This hunt
All
What’s that in your hand? Medicine?
Win
Human
What’s the matter, JoJo?
Be prepared
Show me that.
Huh?
brando
Father
They’re the same symptoms as my father’s.
Answer me!
all
world
Get in and out
Come out
As a gentleman,
What's wrong?
Swear on that guy?
Name
Your
Swear on that guy?
Swear on it.
Magi
Your father's
Symptoms
Swear on it.
Wow
Give me the medicine back!
My
My father and symptoms
Same
You
To Dad
was carrying
What
Start talking
Answer me
you
Go
What
I won’t ever let you go
near my father again!
I’m convinced now...
I’ll protect the Joestar family.
Excellent
This is all a
misunderstanding, JoJo!
I’ll protect the Joestar family.
Our
Besides...
Doubt
Your
地獄
Yes,
Nothing more than a flimsy theory.
I
Never again
I won't talk about this
To that guy
close
In the palm of your hand, Dio!
Father!
Infection
-Father!
What’s all this ruckus for?
yes
Excuse me, but—
We’ll do as he says.
It got cut
Joe John
Did Jojo do Jojo?
no
It's okay
No no no no no no no no no
No, no, no, no, no
I can't draw anymore
A perfect world
Get it
no
How about it?
What's going on? Yes, Master
Speaking out loud like that
Well, I'll be doing my second and third thesis. In the meantime, I've decided to give them a perfect tour. I will not be receiving any medicine or medical treatment except from them.
But please let him do what he wants. I don't know why, but I believe in my son. Thank you.
Time’s nearly out, so I gathered
my resolve and took off!
8 years
Use this,
Before my eyes lies
the underbelly of society
Gradually
Your research will kill you
field
This is Ogre Street and
we’re the ogres, duh!
Dunno what the hell
you came here for
Want a taste of the
edge of this knife?
The country in front of me is on the other side of the world, there are reasons why I can't move forward
From your life to that foolish
heart—we’ll steal ‘em away!
It's finally here, Mr. Aird, Barabolet
(Ogre Street, we’ll even fill
our stomachs with your life)
Who's coming? I'm the one who's good now.
(Ogre Street, go on and leave it all behind)
(Ogre Street, why don’t we
put that resolve to the test?)
Treplatzitzcuiscocoscue
Hogar is the problem.
Quit bluffin’! Let me have a
go at this soft little rich boy!
Hoga Street, now I know we're just a little old
Bowery, life is Ongar
If you keep moving like this, you won't be able to escape to the cracks
Hikatonare Tsukkoikasa Hoga Street
That’s the sound of blade hitting bone!
Hoga Street Now I know our image chronology
There is in the family
I, Speedwagon, won’t allow you
to lay a hand on that gentleman!
I thought you must have a father,
or mother, or siblings too.
I came here for the sake of my father.
So in the moment I kicked,
Someone bandage his wound.
‘Cause I’ve taken a liking to ya!
(Ogre Street)
Stop it
(You, who have the courage)
Why didn't you kick it as you pleased?
(To see the stars down here in the mud)
(Light up the darkness with
your unwavering heart!)
Brought me completely to my knees
Jora-san, Joestar-san, in the case of Dokkuek, the name is Wanchi
If you're not careful, you'll get caught out. Be careful.
I'll guide you through the process of speeding you down
Why did I like you?
Gantdown Slis Hwaga Street
It's a hidden flame
Quickly take out the
See which run
JoJo has gone off to London...
With my pure heart, I will light up your darkness
Or could he have found
evidence of the medicine?
This plum blossom, this encounter,
Up
leisure
Please get it today
JoJo...
Huh...
…
How dare you! You bastard!
What did you do to my mate?!
…
What’re you mumbling about?!
Just now?
It’s a live human experiment!
Is it because of the earthquake?
My voice
Dio Dio Dio Dio Dio!
It's being born
You're the only one I care about
What is this light?
Oh no!
Kitsutsu's face is blue
When you first
I gave Bamma a good sleep.
I'm sure
He’s dead...
He’s not dead!
Back of face
Wow
It's not even possible that it will be born
He’s not dead!
Earthquake Floyd
Delicious
It's your fault
Wow
Make it plump
Pukula
Should I do it or paint it?
This white machine
Also, the company
Let me come over
It's a journey of success
Hehehehe
Well then
Your research is dissolved
His face is...
Do it
Ah
, not easy
What
What is this, what did you do?
Benge Gong
Dead
If this much koshin is stabbed in the head, it's only natural that he'll be punished.
It's an ancient Guomon tool.
Not dead
Mamachi
He turned into ash...
Sue
m
Change
Undevide apply
Dragon
then
in
Also
already
ambitions
I'm excited about you
graders
Thank you.
andin Glish
maybe add orca Bureau
This Asian fellow,
Wang Chan—take him away.
me
Dio’s father...
In sunlight
Did it turn to ashes?
This is
Yes, it’s the ring I had made with my wife.
So, Deo
I arrested the criminal!
Would you like to see for yourself?
thank you
Hey
That way of asking
I see.
Oh, bollocks.
Then that means—
picture?
I
But a thief!
Dario Pland
That is to say
For you
I'll tell you
You
This is from my time as an Akanbo.
surely
That I gave him this ring?
But
Finger speech
A man who fell in and out
Corresponding
Yes, he said that. A lie!
Jostar Kyoga
It’s not a lie.
This is what I gave him.
Something special made in pairs
picture?
This is yours.
Today is
My wife
Lord Joestar! Are you taking the piss?!
He had tears in his eyes.
I
If only I had caught Hajiri
Would you like to wish me a happy birthday?
Recorded items
What came off
The lineage of 10-year-old Rutou
It's a cultural fact
Understood
curler
Hey
Woody
Planned
Stop
Well then
Dario Pland is
I would have done the same
thing, yes, for the ones I love
Nothing
Just
It's Nust
Just a lie
That
I know
Dio
I was being careful.
Why
I
Today's
At that time
On the current road
Tears
you
he
Didn't I say this?
This sign language is
He gave it to me.
There was a picture
Ugh
Yes.
this is
What I gave him
He is innocent
Yao's wife
That may be true,
Mr. Pland
yes
This scumbag will laugh at
you tomorrow morning!
That may be true,
hand
Please buy me something
Just a lie
Why that?
Deserveo
If I
In a strange way
suffering
If we had met
That pain
Did you?
picture
There’s a meaning to it all
Light Yes
That’s why...
Shibi
Darkness
I’ll keep on believing
Prayer place
thank you
you
You're too kind
This evil and
With all of my resolve...
Maybe so
But
Will shine one day
I will defy fate!
from
People
Tell me
Forget
That courage
That loneliness
Let's hug
I’ll wait for Dio.
To everything
Garu
I
Believe in people
I heard a bizarre rumour on the streets.
Good
it is
someday
Kakaya
Gudarou
There is another
And then...
I
Shichizuki
Aki's Ambulance
a
bothersome
Noroi
nine
I
Full of passion and yearning
for the unknown world
still
Can be stopped
You
I heard Nauwa-san
Frosia's man
Maybe not today, but
there’s always tomorrow
I swore I’d get revenge,
that I’d take it all back
And the man
Maybe not today, but
there’s always tomorrow
Can't enter
I heard
It's the same as 30 years ago
There’s a saying that goes like that.
The Stone Mask...
nailed down
Kusabi
Systemic training
That morning sun
Like this
It was red
I, Dio, was...
Longing for the road world
My respected father
Hit the rolling sea
I have the antidote now.
At my exact moment
Day 1
It’s a shame it had
to come to this, Dio.
It truly hurts me.
Although you might not believe me,
Those are my true feelings.
You’re honest like that.
The final one
I will ask of you.
Can you give me more time?
The final one
I will ask of you.
I...
Therefore
My ambition was relentless.
It's a shame, really.
You may not understand, but this is the truth
I understand, girl
I can see from your face that
you’re wondering who I am.
Growing up in the darkest slums,
Can you give me some time?
Mr. Joestar, you should call
for the police right away.
I
I’ve heard everything I need to.
Born into a poor family
I got a palm.
You won’t succeed in arresting that man...
When words
He was born with an innate destiny.
I am
Anyone
For the sake of those seven
years we spent together.
I want you to be the
one who handcuffs me.
I am
I was allowed to introduce myself
I'm Speedwagon of Osekkaiyaki
I've been driving since it got stuck.
I've seen a lot of different people
To be human is to have limits
That’s what I’ve come to realise
The more I see the limitations of this life
I’m always coming up empty-handed
or
I don't want to see you get caught
That man won't give up
I was born with that fate
Sores!
Don’t you get it?
You'll be released, but at least
We've been together for seven years.
Be careful!
Understood
Can’t wash the filth out of mine
For humans
The stars!
I am
The Stone Mask?
The limits of life
What are you talking about?
I'm so frustrated
My humanity!
There is nothing
The empty logo
With a glance next to me
I can't see beyond
No matter how much I write
Lord Joestar!
That smiling sky
I want you to know me
This is...
I wrote that
On that beautiful day
A doctor’s coming, he’ll save you! Hold on!
Your late mother’s ring.
The stars
Light
One
I am
Mom
Life
It’s not so bad...
Right
Yes
please
Hahahaha
Yes
I knew I made a mistake, back then.
You always told me to be a gentleman
Firmly
To always live with pride
Even though I said I’d save you,
Maybe when I got home I felt it was fair.
Shoot
What does it mean
to be a gentleman?
Gradually
What’s the purpose of
In my son's arms
father
Do it.
I’ll accept it all, and
look up at the stars
It was a mistake
Your resolve to shine a beacon
through the dark wastelands
Survey
Whether it's a hearing or not
Take pride in this heart
that shines like gold!
Proudly
everytime
I said I'd save you
I believe
This Joestar blood
flowing through my body!
I'm powerless to have been unable to protect you
What do you believe?
With just one drop of courage!
What is pride?
Flowing through this body
Survey results
Inspector! It’s an emergency!
What did you say?!
Proudly
Rishiki
The voice of darkness
Inspector!
Look up at the stars
Even though we shot him into Swiss cheese!
What the hell?! He came back to life!
Dance your heart out
Shoot him! Don’t just
stand there! Quickly!
Send it to the stars that will become the future
Flowing through this body
Survey results
H-He’s sucking his blood!
It all makes sense
I'm sad about this fate
I’ve gained such incredible power!
It's Keiban and Daiyan.
what up?
From the Stone Mask...
Dion's body is missing.
It became
Satsuma
Run away, Mr. Joestar!
You’ll only get killed!
Massage
Keiban
If that’s the case...
Even though I was interrupted by forgetting
Tomare
Stop!
Don't be silly
It's early
I don't know above
I must make my will stronger!
I must...
Suddenly puffed up...
Hiriamado is hard to laugh at
Mr. Joestar!
Let me enjoy this amazing power
for just a little longer!
From someday
Your father's power
A quick fix to the running.
Stop this useless struggle of yours.
I told you, didn’t I?
Humans have limits!
If it stops
Quit hiding behind that
curtain! Come out here!
Stop it!
Menoeka!
Already
It’s courage!
Crab Cui Crab Cui
a!
Wow, that's fun
I'll enjoy this wonderful power for a little while longer.
(The flash of flames,
scattering the light)
Both specialists
It’s useless! Useless! Useless!
I’ll suck you dry!
JOJO: Please give me strength
DIO: For giving me strength
I always walked in your shadow
Kisamalabop
You were always right behind me
I'm not even screaming that I can fly you
And Father is dead!
Speed ​​Low
Confusing
Don't run upstairs
ah
Run in the dark
It's going up
Mr. Joestar was surely thinking,
I'm here
Do you understand?
Ladies, ladies, you first
“If only the flames were
even hotter!” But by then...
Damn it! Mr. Joestar!
Finish eating
It's useless, it's useless
If you suck that life out
This flickering
Not from afar
Let's give one
Give me your strength
From now on, always
From your back
On my back,
The only one dying will be you!
This body is immortal.
Final exam
The only one dying will be you!
Women
Women's Palm
You are burning
I'm dead
I lost it immediately
I won’t let go of this knife,
That too
Burning
The knife you stabbed Father with!
That is
I'll close you
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
More firepower
That Mamoru's recovery power
After placing it
more
More firepower
Throw away
The force of instinct
If you do
This can’t be how my life ends—
Shit
Jasasasa
It's your fault, I almost fell into the basement
Where do you approach? I've grown fond of you
As I thought, this crying that won't let go was there
You can hear me.
I hope you had a nice intermission.
Of the world to which all of
you have become witnesses.
I want the whole acrylic stand collection.
Janshah
Refreshing
But lost everything.
Can you hear me?
I can hear you
I mentioned the Astika people before.
That was a 13th century mistake, not a 16th century one.
The mask that man wore!
JoJo, can you hear me?
As someone said, I don't want to get old.
it was good
But I want to do what I can at least,
This room doesn’t allow visitors.
Can I help you?
Refreshing
I did a complica
The story so far seems like a fairy tale
is definitely a reality
And it gets weirder from here
Yeah, strangely.
At that time, the mansion was almost completely engulfed and collapsed.
But Chosa was still there
I was attacked by Dio
But I lost everything
Then see
there were
Did you see it over there? If you have this screen
It’s really been too long.
I was childish back then,
I couldn’t face you
This is me, but...
Your voice is still the same
There’s nothing but blue skies
here in vibrant Liverpool
That's why I came
I have enough vocabulary
Please come on the 5th.
Are you okay?
My goodness, you caught
me with your broken arm!
I can see it there
That little bit of courage
to move towards tomorrow
Once again, when I see a vivid person
Your hand
I
Now our hearts
resonate, beating as one
All the mansions
Please stay calm now
Now our hearts
resonate, beating as one
I'm glad you're alive
You've been nursing me
You are Yamasaka
Just the two of us
Who do you think looks like me? Erina Pendleton
It's been a while
Fate? That’s right.
Why
This is my father's hospital
Maybe some people are
just fated to meet one another.
I recently planned
It's really been a while
I was weak
It wasn't my first time with you
It was me who was young
I couldn't face you
He’s struck again,
that bloodthirsty maniac
This voice remains unchanged
Vivid reverb
(And she had her guts ripped out!)
(Like it’s made of fog)
(Don’t go out walking at night!)
The truth of the
matter is out of reach!
Elina
sorry
My mind is shaking and I lose consciousness
With me and my arms
I'll always support you
Eye to eye
Oh, it’s already so late!
Plainness is courage
I have to return home soon...
It’s a terrifying thought!
Terrifying, is it?
You’re talking with him right now!
overlap
attract
fit
You dirty harlot!
Continue with the two of us
destiny
yes
The encounter of people
Maybe it's decided by fate
Kitty Dwagon
Cool!
lover
See you again soon
Don’t you want power?
Oh, I must heal these wounds,
and for that I’ll need lives!
A girl
Early afternoon
(Power and pleasure!)
This I will grant you!
However, very rarely there are
those not constrained by goodness.
Those are the evil elite.
Like myself, and you as well!
It's going to happen. He's going to appear.
London is also popular
I understand you, Jack.
You’re angry at them, right?
Black people don't eat
Women who are
dripping with ecstasy
Me, afraid?!
That’s right!
Jack! You don’t have
to worry anymore
That’s right!
I won't go home early
Break out from the narrow
confines of your prison
But there might be a Jap who will be the first to appear.
Is that a lie?
It's scary
Who are you?
I’ll start to live from this moment on
Relax
This is Dio’s World!
you
I liked it
Because I was seen
I don't feel any pain
There's no more of that
Reborn now
Let's start my life
I have to heal my ache
I need life
So I feel less fulfilled
Don't you want power?
The Stone Mask...
I want to believe it turned
to dust like everything else.
It has to have been.
I’m alright.
But very rarely
It’s alright.
Eh?
You are
Who’s that?
Has he been here
this whole time?
To you
What’s wrong?
Jonathan Joestar!
So you
And Miss Erina Pendleton.
You’ve done well to survive
the power of the Stone Mask!
Such
The Stone Mask?!
That's good enough now.
It seems like it will change
There's already one
Yes.
Well then
You don't have to worry anymore
More spinning than ever before in my hands
This is
Such as
do not have
It's crowded
Because of this
You
Come stretch
Jack
Zalipa
This hand
Anyway
Atanosa
I am on your side!
Together
What did you do to me?!
Who are you?
Hey JoJo, one question at a time!
What did you do to me?!
nine
My
Restoration
That's it
Your
It's a hobby
The choice is up to you!
Kekari
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
Messy tears
became
(In, out!)
Ban Duan
Its name is—
他の棚同城細相信台
yes
It's okay
Are you okay
let's go
Huh?
Making this miracle happen—
Who is it?
That is the power of the ripple
Jora-san Choustar-kun
Huh? And
That is the power of the ripple
I'm surprised I survived
That Iskamen's power
Isukamen!
Wait!
Jola-san
Oshipa
Keep it open
By air
Yes! The power of breathing!
Breathing created that power?!
That's lame!
Yes! The power of breathing!
No appearance
I am Separi Danshak
All I have is courage
Yes, I know it all
So too are you and Dio!
Your breathing
To him
I’ve travelled the world
The mask is not broken—he has it!
Jora-san Jowstar
So that I can destroy it!
Dio is alive?!
Appearance
We must destroy it!
Dio is alive?!
Follow me
We must destroy it!
Eyes change
It has been set in motion!
I finally found it!
Will I get my hands on it? Our fates
This breathing
The place to wake up
Now is the time to show it and run
Smart
Destiny!
Country Petunassau
The concussion
Hackopping
Tyaeaars
Energy is generated
Mine and Dio’s!
Hamon Energy
Horororororororororororororororororororororororororororo
That turns humans into vampires.
Thank you
This miracle
Dropped
Ah, let’s put it this way.
The Power of Hamon
Kokum brings
The power of liquid
Smart
Use a ripple!
Everyone can create a little bit of energy in the flow of life.
Carrying heroes and adjusting responses
And that wave of energy
The power to defeat Dio!
What do you mean, Dio?
I frown at this breathing technique
Dios
I swear I’ll come back here again.
The amount of treasure we have now is
For now, please just go along with it!
I followed Kamen
Destroying and eating
Dio is alive
Just catch cute
If you don't destroy it
In the hands of destruction
Well, is there any more?
Yours
Your world
Fate is weak and sluggish
I finally found it
Tattered and worn
Do you accept it?
Eyes working hard
Everything was discussed
Sma
destiny
fight
That's my destiny
You mean me?
The will of the person
Extracting the power of the path from "no"
Guided by this hapless fate
it is
You must take blood energy from others.
On the other hand, Hamon's power
Mizukaru's blood flows
Extracting energy
I am left behind
Yeah
It's Smari
To remove this jamon
I live in a dream,
waiting by the window
Jamon
I want to scream!
They'll explode
And the tears of energy
It has the same shape as the sunlight
You are drawn to me
yes
Develop an attitude that turns courage into strength
woman
Dio
Energy
While looking up at the stars
Right now I just want you to stay
I'll definitely come back to this place
This is
Is it a female jamon?
Yeah
Haa
Clouds flow
The wind carries my thoughts
Measurement
go around
I nodded.
Our stars shine together
In sadness
Shining stars
I won't lead you to the fate you desire
I got stuck in the mud
I will live on!
Left behind
Living the dream
Wang Chan, you’re alive?!
Loneliness is
For whom?
Even if it doesn't reach
Even if it doesn't shine now
I want to scream
I
Even if it doesn't shine now
Why are you so strong?!
I
Because
you
There is light
anytime
You know too much about
the secret of the Stone Mask!
I
Spending my days
Let's live
I wa-ha-ha-was looking for you too!
While
This place
He’s strong enough to rival you.
Proudly
Let's continue to exist
Your everything
Acceptance
His arm... got longer!
yes
So that you can call
The stars
Daylight
Your
Don't let your destiny lead you
It’s useless.
Daylight
Where
I’ve been given new life!
I
Me
Live on
It’s hot!
Alive
Go
Kiev
I lost so much...
Going
Otsuku
Go
Wear
Wihaha
Weано
Wear
“The north wind created the brave vikings!”
Maza KAL
Dion too
Because you feel the pain.
Wearcon
You
Because you feel the pain.
That's it!
Sioster!
Aa ...
Oooooohhhh!
Even for those you want to protect—
Because! Because!
Pain is proof they’re alive
You need to listen to that pain!
Licky?
Lick lick!
Lick lick lick!
Vero up and down?
picture?
Be careful of the skilled
I was always told to be a gentleman
What's with this weirdo Pojnock?
Forever walking in my father’s footsteps
Gutega what's wrong...
We we we we we we we we we we we
It was pure coincidence!
Humans are like this Jikro'a
Daizara doesn't have a phone
Gon!
My body...
Why this?
Ah! It's hot! Which one is it?
The mask burst with light
見事だ、少少
I'm surprised I was able to see Hamogo on such a short trip.
yeah…
what up?
JoJo...
It was my father!
But that's...
Not the same as Dio
To insult someone
It's fundamentally different from the power he was stealing.
Another is the same power
We embrace this pain
A harsh coming will wake you up
ZEP: I’ve been chasing after it
JOJO: So that it won’t repeat
The Vikings who heard it
We embrace this pain!
You
pain
We embrace this pain!
And the resolve to face the consequences.
Pain is life
Red
I'll listen to the pain
Believe me
I was always told
Don’t forget this goal.
everytime
I like your fringe.
Dosuta no Chi
Hot
The day screen
Emits light
Perspective
Repeatedly, the liquid
Holding this pain
The screen is not a word
I happened by chance
Jonathan Joestar!
nailed down
rust
I will win
My Father and the Seven Rabbits
Oh! It burns! It burns!
You’re good company, huh?
Is that Mr. Horse?
Oh! It burns! It burns!
50 First Time
Is that Mr. Horse?
He had been murdered.
There he is.
Protect the darkness
Love you
These bills been piling piling up
What illuminated
Who else would be your guide
We drove, no stopping sites
That famous city of knights
disappeared
While the sun’s out
Catch up
Don't look back
Approaching excellence
I won't talk
No more tomorrows Dio, that’s it
With pain
Without a doubt, this is where
Dio is building his own empire.
and
The entrance to the town
is through this tunnel.
Right?
The entrance to the town
is through this tunnel.
yes
I believe in the power of this conger eel
let's go
What is he...
I
depressed
Surprise fall
It's a horse
good
Ah, okay.
Wow, across the street
I'm a novice
So then, what exactly is “courage”?
Could you call something
like that “courageous”?
What are you yammering on about!
I occasionally watched it.
Surrendering to that fear
throws your breath out of sync.
“Fear” sends your breathing awry!
The hymn of humanity
is a song of courage!
Of course I'll be your guide
The hymn of humanity
is a song of courage!
Juul Lauction
Shaodar
The greatness of humanity
is the greatness of courage!
Opposition Party Email to City
They’re just like fleas!
Sacrificial Mast Usue
This Wind Knight Roto
Teipenorosaimarniagit
How dare you! I’ll kill you!
Yes... I’ll eat every
shred of you in one bite!
Dayon Arbunchiri
How dare you! I’ll kill you!
Yes... I’ll eat every
shred of you in one bite!
Windknight’s Lot...
thank you
They’re inviting us. We must go farther.
Yes. Dio’s surely at the end of the trail.
Dio will realize his empire here.
This is the entrance to the city.
The projection area is as planned.
Hey! Win the race!
Why stop place
Be careful
Dio doesn't have a strong hand here.
Look!
No no no rail
Summoner's magic is a demon bon
I fight
Reverse bone door
Jasuke Fighter Shikoda
I’ll allow you this and more!
This recruitment is for us humans
Crying out from the mud,
conquer the stars
I’ll allow you this and more!
Goddess
(We’ve been sleeping for 300 years,
us rotten and forgotten corpses)
Republicans who saw the breath
Who is it?
Eye Base
Hamoho Country is an organic acid
Human oxidation is organic oxidation
The wonder of humans is the wonder of organics
How strong is
These zombies don't know anything about organic matter.
Wait, Dio!
Dolly
Hot Hot
Yackoma
My world is in the palm of my hand now!
Cover
why?
Small tree trainer
Kutcha
I will dominate life at last,
This is Kisstats' training ground.
There are various tricks
And there's a big deal at that time.
He is thriving
Who should be the one to end it?
Rewriting and upending it anew
This too
azz
so
surely
vague
I wonder
Be aware
Kun
Retreat
I will dominate everything,
I’ll face them now
Huh, uhh, realized?
Answer: Law, I want to make you my own Law
Now let's reveal the truth behind the parliamentary
Fuji Ha Well He vomiste
That is the world, this unshakable world
So much that there’s a hole in my cheek...
And your tongue is sticking
out of the hole? Really, Jack?
The sun has set.
It’s time for your lives
to go down with it!
Even so, I can’t help
this feeling of dread.
I’ve been building up my
courage for this moment!
Even so, I can’t help
this feeling of dread.
Put your training to use.
Match the search
I remember shouting from the sky
(Steal it away!)
Shout from the sky, "Losing!"
The north wind made the vikings!
This battle will be an exercise—
SPW: We’re not here to play around, have you lost it?
ZEP: You shut your trap!
Hair Child and Varialli
Make history solid
Will this wine make a viking out of you?
I feel empty so I have to be strong
Scream from the heart
It's scary
Search
All seems solid
Don’t let your breathing go awry!
The ripple of the wine!
I can feel it flow, I’ll find my
way through the darkness!
With the power of the sun!
It's shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking
But it's amazing Didhy
Igu Shichiraku Intercom
A strange child will jump out
Body de jai
Data
The water comes out here
Because, oh, it's true!
Popping out
The sun has set
This is the power
that will defeat you!
The ripple of the sun! Dio!
This is the power
that will defeat you!
You have to forgive me as a human being
上書
It's a fighting mindset
I'm bored
At first
Eclact is delicious
By this bisabigi
Bu-go attack
It's Lesland.
Sakasei
Let's ride a bike
went
It's just a good thing
Then I’ll be completely healed from
the damage you dealt me in that fire.
To purge this wound!
I didn't come back later,
You bastard!
To purge this wound!
I'll book it and give it a go
Yokkapinu
Hitatakawara Viking
Severe living activity is born
Do you remember how many slices of
bread you’ve eaten in your lifetime?
Where is my west today?
Warm thoughts
I’ll make you submit!
Won't open
Human participation is
Courageous Participation
I’ll make you submit!
By the ripple of the sun!
All
Connect
Utterly pathetic!
It’s freezing?!
Hmm
There's no cold
My Hallow
is
Then you won’t be able to use that power!
Shoes
Yana
Mr. Zeppeli!
Tears
It was a dream where I told my boss
It's gone
Cragbeshable
Society too
soon
Bullbearly
Instagram
Let's pull
Wrapped in cherry blossoms Wrapped in cherry blossoms
The color of the house
Don't ask for more yet
DRA I want to see
Grz
Gather at Gabo Japma Ra
That’s right. Do you remember?
The story of the knights
your father told us that day?
Dio Brando!
a?
I don't know you personally
But
It was about the ones who served her!
Mary Stuart!
Don't ride it
bard!
Father told us...
This is a story of knightly pride!
Which has been passed down for
generations in our great England.
At Kisamara's command, I will disinfect this wound in the air.
Two queens battled for the throne
And the other, the beautiful Mary Stuart
I'll let you sleep.
The width of the sun!
bread!
品積品積!
While wishing for a nest to rest in
I can control my body freely.
They swore their loyalty to her
Help!
Waste waste waste waste!
breathe?
Conger eel?
Hehe, if that's the case, it would be fitting for you to play a fanfare for me.
Hahaha
There's no stock strategy that suits you, friend.
This, we cannot refuse
Do you remember?
“And I will spare your master’s life!”
Elizabeth's assassination attempt
But in the moment they
were to be executed—
Mary Stuart
Your master isn’t being held in the tower.
Two people
It's about an angry Kishi.
Dad's
Now
You’ve betrayed us, Elizabeth
Jojon, Dion
Today, this tradition is passed down in England.
We curse you with our grudge!
Living in the spirit of Shingeru
Kishi's
They couldn’t cut through his neck!
Once upon a time, 300 years ago
Let's cheer on the two of us
Jojohn, Elizabethan
Beautiful Mary Stuart
And that is the story,
Until the very end!
Hahahahahaha
From now on
Ophiry like you
Until the very end!
Oh, what loyal hearts!
There is nothing that is without meaning.
The same can be said about the
fact that you came here to this house.
Find peace
Use clothing
Flowing Time
Do they see the stars? Or the mud?
By Elizabeth
A friend's container is placed on it
I'll be caught
Do they see the stars? Or the mud?
To save Mary
Either one—
Elizabeth calls out
You guys should mess with us
Save Shugun's life.
To Elizabeth
There is no denying it
Our difficult story
Even history bends before me!
It's so easy to get caught up in it
I'll scoop up the maid
This system is unacceptable
I bowed my head
It’s the perfect form for
taking their revenge!
Kill them all!
Continue from where
you left off on that day!
Wow
Play me a fanfare with their screams!
The way you feel—
But I also bear my own burdens!
Your pride, your resentment.
I can’t even imagine it!
I'll wait
I’m gonna be the one to eat ‘em!
Would like to be the one to bring
an end to this brave man’s life!
A goosebump-inducing proposition
Alright, go ahead!
But they should have done better.
I couldn't do anything in the first match.
I won’t let you interfere!
You may be right.
But nothing is meaningless
The same goes for when you came to this house.
I won’t let you interfere!
I want to believe
People are like destiny
A wedge driven into the
wasteland of my memory
Are you seeing stars?
Or either one
Gradually
Say it's your fault
The two of them
Come on, get real,
even at a time like this?
Even if I give up, the pain
will just be for another day
Got it?
Is that what you take pride in?
If you want to preach, then fight
with your pride on the line!
Is that what you take pride in?
Everyone looks happy
A continuation of that day
Tarkus Bellaford
I must find the strength to stand up
I’m not scared of pain
Tomorrow is right now!
That's it
Slow Idiom Kiss Bellaford
and Tarkus
I think that's a bit
I didn’t follow you to
become a hindrance!
But I also have something to carry
I’ll let courage resonate in my heart
How many were filled?
The man's anger
And look the enemy in the eyes
My master
Won’t wait for a distant tomorrow
I would like to draw every day of this man's life.
Okay, that's good.
Make a good list and get it
If it hurts, run away
Survey
Cut finely, beat of my blood!
I am the Dark Knight Bruford!
nailed down
Wedge
Anyway
This pain means nothing to me!
Like this
It was red
Osa
Why aren’t you moving?
Just now,
You can feel pain!
I am, I am
Nothing to try
I'm not good
Pain?
That’s why...
Even at a time like this
Even if you give up
Come
Carefully
I stopped fighting you.
Make Irumide
I kept chasing
Remember
You are human!
Pain...
I was just angry.
Is proof of life!
So this is what it means to be human?
What's scary is
It's not pain
already
What you should know
regain
Morning tomorrow
Tomorrow
Now
There
picture
Tokewa
I feel a bizarre sense of peace now.
When
I dedicate to you the word
engraved in my sword.
Kiki's
Looking back at the station
Is it urgent?
Don't wait for tomorrow
I start walking
Should believe
It should be said that
Tomorrow Now
girl
The Beat of Decision with You
Just as I thought...
When I looked into it
That
I, Dio, will—
Pikima
pain
No or
Watch out, Mr. Joestar!
You are feeling pain now
pain
That's why I stopped being that Sarakai
So you stopped the prefecture
You are a proud wrecker
Human
What I saw
Sennorakashi
This is a human being
Because there are similarities
I can feel the joy of being here now
I can be here now
I’ll get you!
I feel now
Bravo
That you take my ripple
and continue on, JoJo!
Something like this
and
Let's go
To save souls
He collapsed.
Come
Affection
No way
To think he would defeat Kurokiko
If we lose you—
There’s no time to be sad.
Haybay Day
The Stone Mask must be destroyed!
In the end,
What changes is not the outcome but the vile Hamon
It's dangerous, Tama
Once again, life is
spilling out of my arms
Brami's brother
Loss of motivation and enthusiasm
驚
Lots of Ou
From now on
Into my spirit
I'll do it, I'll do it!
JoJo
From here on...
My companion
JoJo!
Wow
always
Search Chokil
My father left to me
what you leave to me now
Please stop it
Carlton!
Oklaine!
Windows 4
Hey, Jebel, Jebel, if you're gone, I'll be sad, but one day I'll destroy my eyes, but hey, I'm happy with my life. Finally, I've entrusted it to you.
Hey, you're my hope.
The way to you...
You taught me the meaning of my life, my destiny, and the greatness of being human - courage.
The light that was received would seep in. In my heart, I felt as if I was both dead and breathing at the same time.
Can’t you hear my voice?
I can’t hear you
You and I are different
You’re not so changed,
you did it to survive
I’ll use any means
There is one thing that is so certain that it is in my heart right now.
Embrace it, because this moves,
Look at the stars.
What remains is the brilliance of humanity,
Light up the darkness and bring your return,
Come back,
happiness.
You’re just afraid.
I hear a voice calling to you,
I’ve transcended humanity!
You ran away from it.
Unlike you.
It's my fault.
The ends justify the means.
I will win,
And that means conquering
everything, of course.
Disobey justice,
All of this is fate!
Use and take everything,
Disobey justice,
What will your legacy be?
Laughing,
I want it,
it is,
And then died!
Here it comes,
Your father.
Well then,
Is this the world you've left behind?
what,
The world you lost long ago,
For the sake of revenge...
It's a wonderful world where I control everything
Lion
I’ve accepted this as my legacy!
Ironic, isn’t it? Now
you’re the have-not, JoJo!
You're just scared
Humans
That's why I gave up being human
To get it
Beyond human
If you think about it, you’re just like me
I won
The only result is that you are in control.
It's all just a dream
But
You did it! You defeated Dio!
Rumbling, rumbling, rumbling
To me
Give me strength
dead
Your
It's my father
That's right
smile
As long as we have faith, we can grow
The current situation is
To tell the story behind
Ko how proprio
JOJO: That’s what he taught me
DIO: You can’t reach me!
When I tell you the inside story like that,
I've been forced to ask you out
He put his hand in the
fire! If he does that—
Like fire and ice
hahhh
Finally, a name that stands out
What's left now
With my life on the
line, I’ll prove it now!
務 manual you
Like fire and ice
Holy and low
merged
for that
pain
No problem
“I was only trying to be friendly!”
“I think my finger went in his eye.”
I won’t stop beating you
until you’re finished!
Omelo, kill me
I’m melting!
You threw me away and taught me the best, so I'll pour in the bargain sale in front of the meaning of selling you
Yes, I did it. I knocked my hand down. That's wrong.
Watch out! He’s shooting
hot liquid out of his eyes!
緊弱緊弱
Sasasa, no no
It's so tense, but it's actually deceiving you
JoJo
Now you too will come to me, and death will resonate with you
You ran away from humans
What's not making me spill right now?
Extra, extra! Read all about it!
There was a small incident
I can't keep up with you guys
I'm already curious, girl
There was a small incident
73 people vanished
Let's do it. Inlencer grows.
In just one night,
they abruptly disappeared
If you say that, you can just run away
(In the Windknight’s Lot Paper)
Let me sacrifice my life and reveal it to you
That the following day, below a cliff
Men were seen burning clothing
(In the announcements section)
(In 1889 on February the 2nd)
(The Joestar heir)
Let me shed my life on this and reveal it to you.
Yagaragaragaragara
Yagaragaragara
I want to sleep
I'll make anything happen
Roughly
Megan
The meaning of our relationship has been stripped away
Yep.
I’ll always be there for you!
Osnagel's
I can’t wait to hear all about it!
Huh?
That's why
Damn it...
Pokentique!
Waking up!
This Tio
still
There's more!
Caution!
Then like this
I've unleashed my strength!
That's disgusting!
Yo
Simple!
Simple squid
Inezy!
AEG!
When you’re next to me...
I feel the same.
Well, let’s go and eat!
The Efrazy Case
Such a worrying incident
713 people
The person who disappeared
And then Kotzen disappeared
But the groans I heard coming from
No one yet
Go back to our cabin.
D.A.D.
D.S.M.R.F.D.
Wind Knights Lord Article
Complex Company Speaks
The day after the incident
Running under
I have lured him here.
and
The screen of the day
AEG!
Sempraridasekaamshakoland
Have you come?
At night
Up and down
second-mover
Female Female
The insertion
Married
I used to despise you so much,
Pendrcon species
More than a voice
Einar Pendrkon
Philisarnasilas
That’s because I’ve realised something!
Then there’s never been a relationship
orchestrated as perfectly as ours...
Sirisana Sirus
Joster-san
Both of them
push up
I am
Always Hey Prussie
You’re the reason I got this power,
The world has slipped from my grasp!
It's a ball
Harnem
Miya did sign language
And you’re the reason why...
When will it...
That’s exactly what our destiny is!
Shhhh!
And live in eternal glory!
Tell this story until the world is a flash
That's the job of this meddlesome YATII Speedwagon introduction.
Are one and the same in this world!
On planet Meguru, where Eien prays for today
And restart it all
Erina! Not you too!
This is the start of his mythos!
Please, spare the child!
Run!
Shall we torture him to death?!
Don't forget to lock it
I won’t tolerate any insults!
【伝ir】
Your blood will become my future!
Wagapodi
Here you go,
JoJo!
Therefore I will split this stone in pieces before you.
I now respect you for having made so many holes.
Because I realized that
I felt it tear. Something
important inside me just tore
There's no relationship more calculated than ours
ERINA: How could this be?!
JOJO: Get out of here!
I won’t, JoJo...
How far are you?
That's why this is destiny
I got the body of the only person in the world I respect
Everything is connected
JoJo
Because we are one
The one to spin the thread of fate
(Light and darkness flicker and flash)
In the end, I, Dio, will triumph!
The world of Pingo
No, John
(Light and darkness flicker and flash)
There's no breathing
Only you
When the spirits scatter
I figured...
Elemental Creation
Only this child
You would strike...
Can you get the dial?
nevertheless
All people
Before I...
fun
Need
Lost consciousness.
That neck
Right next to the iron steps
Inaccuracy
I won't forgive
Let me go, JoJo!
John
You
This child
My
Someone
all
Dose
Something inside me snapped, something decisive
Chomazo!
This is it!
Run away
Chocho
Until I burn with you
Until everything disappears
Flames run, everything is connected
Like two who make one,
All live
We feel a bizarre friendship
Now, I'm going to be in trouble.
Maybe this time
Isn’t that right, Dio?
Sell ​​happily and live
Guided by this hapless fate
Until you don't need it yet
Okay then
We’ll reach out to the stars
Have become one
Our two fates
Speak
Have become one
This guy
Dead
(This bizarre adventure)
The destiny and adventure
Dead
Let's talk forever
Of course,
Something in my eyes
Two in One
Feeling the friendship of a dog
That's right
Without you
Because you were there
something
Now I
want
Find
To your favorite destiny
Beautiful Mikade
In the stars
I drink
The two
That fate
It was terrible
Another breast
Quietly unknown
One saw the stars
Tour
Is it polar?
pick up the station
my frightenedzz
Speedwagon is so cool!
Yuishie, Yoishie!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuisi, Yuisi!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuisi, Yuisi!
The best thing about this park was that the smiles of all the customers were the biggest smiles. I felt that very strongly at the park.
I was truly happy that such a miraculous park had been able to survive to the very end.
Thank you for watching.
Now, Mr. Kong, please.
Great staff, great cast.
Then they brought the outbreak to the theater.
I'm glad to meet everyone who has watched the video.
I easily overcame the progression.
The players were able to go home after today's academy.
I'm happy for people.
I let it happen.
thank you.
And I was struggling as a single person.
My son!
That's amazing!
I'm so happy!
It's great.
thank you.
Then, I received the greeting I just mentioned.
Thank you for watching.
thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Everyone, please check out Fauci's Prround Funding.
thank you.
MAMORU: It’s already over.
Thank you! Thank you!
Shotaro, do your best tomorrow!
He doesn't know either.
So Misha, please.
yes.
It was a huge hurdle.
I'm not sure if I can speak well,
This is Elina Tendul and her character Shimis Misha.
Thank you very much for coming to the audience today.
Brought to you by Ossan Subs
I was able to reach this great war retreat,
The strength of each and every cast member,
Subtitling
S_Mage and Jama Kitten
For supporting this work,
Special thanks to our wonderful
Japanese friends who helped us along the way!
Please do, everyone.
Please look at the stars, everyone.
So please have a great war.
yes.
It's your job to burn the speeder!
It was my first experience and it was really difficult for me.
But really.
It was really hard, but
Already, somehow,
To get support,
Thanks,
It was really hard, but
Already, somehow,
To get support,
Like supporting them,
Supporting each other,
Those words truly mean,
It just seemed to enter my body.
It's a really wonderful place,
Thanks to that,
I was able to cut it thickly.
So, I have nothing but the best to say,
With everyone here on stage,
As Kochi-san also said,
Not at all.
Although he's not here now,
The staff who helped me create it,
and,
This role,
For five months,
I really put it together,
I want to make it a treasure in my life.
Love women,
Thank you for taking an interest in Speedwagon again.
Including everyone who loves me,
Really,
thank you very much!
Shirae-san...
Good job, Dig putting is burning well.
I certainly understand.
Honchitsu,
To Sepulija,
RPM improved office
Wang's school committee came to the event.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you very much.
Really,
The first thought is,
There were a lot of different things that happened.
The two of them, Shotaro, and now, here
The one who finished the tree, and another Teperi,
Hiro-kun and I accomplished so much on our own.
Mom, this company is a one-lens camera for people.
With the determination to align
I came here with the aim of becoming a teacher of Wang's music.
Really, without anyone calling
Of course, I'm really grateful that I've come this far.
Medical support from staff
It is the result of your efforts.
Every single stage, really
I just want to omit it.
The applause of the Baraline and 5000 yen are us
Now the cast is
The truth is, it's your Hamon energy.
How much courage it gave us
I think that's what we really feel.
I was really close to Hantoshi and Okabetsu right now.
It really is like a family
It means that today will be a valley from tomorrow onwards.
Hey hey
Annie
A little Syriaria please
Just a little bit
I feel lonely though
I really love myself
This woman's world
And with these beloved members
In this theater
Being able to breathe the same air
That's right.
The one who touched everyone's hearts was
I have become a treasure too
I am proud to have been able to do this with you all.
Thank you so much everyone
thank you
It will end again
Blatzer
Please watch
I changed my boss's environment.
Another ironworker
Thank you for today
It's totally free
So many
As you have written earlier,
Right from here on
As in the title above
It was a strange adventure.
There are so many people like you.
Only the curtain of Hara
Born at the Imperial Theatre
The Imperial Theatre
The current theater is closing.
As a final review
By producing
Not Minami
Memories
Participated
My friends are cast members here.
It is staff
And the original author
The main cast members
And here are the books.
After five years of work
Apparently it was rewritten 17 times.
It was in this flow that I was born.
This work
Being accepted by everyone like this
Like this
Many musicals
We have some works from overseas.
Such works are
Zahiozic Zero is
On Broadway and in the West End
That's what we're here for
In books
While making large replicas
Let's fight
Japanese style
We provide information.
This work is
What you all saw
Exactly
From zero to one
Became Zahiozic
I think it's a work of art.
This work
Someday again
Inherited
It may be a big performance,
This Zahiozik
I was at Zero 1
The friends here
Really I
It's just for the time being.
Zayn
I feel like a son or daughter to you.
Only one person was different
Since they share the same father
One as a father
Mud and Stars
University
A work ticket
As a friend
from now on
At the Shibutoku Musical
I want to survive
Truly amazing
Two sons
Like this
I can have it
A little bit today
You might be watching from anywhere
Also serving
As a son
Nice to meet you
Truly amazing
Yesterday
As a father
I was able to participate
Hello everyone
If you have any worries
Finally
What is it?
Within myself
It's all connected
That it all has meaning
a little bit
If you think so
surely
Beyond that
There is light
There are stars
If you think so
I think it's that kind of work.
thank you
Well then
I will do my best
Where should I start?
Already
But anyway
I'm glad we met
Hotz
We
Entertainment and
I'm trying not to
Sometimes after all
There are times when it's difficult
There are times when it's scary
but
The Minister just said
As you said
Something
In the purely literal sense
Don't do it right away
In the truest sense
Do it now
That's what it means
I am this
I felt it at Campari.
of course
A lot of things happened
Something like that
Only in those words
I might not be able to tell you right now, but
And more
I
now
As a treasure
I was able to have
Above all
It
so
lots of
To humans
That you can enjoy it
After all, it's ours
It's the happiest thing
It
With this member
It can be closed on paper
I am happy
Women
Giant player fun
I welcomed
My father just now
As you said
We will continue to do so
Look forward
Surely soon
Each on their own path
Various expressions
I think I'll pursue it
Not yet
It will be useful
Dad too
Let's definitely meet again
and
Also this woman
I think it would be a good story if we could meet.
It's all connected
I dream of such a day
Today is really
To everyone
I want to express my gratitude
everyone
thank you
amazing
I'll say something good.
I think Bappy will decide.
thank you
Woman
I pushed the woman down.
This is Arisa Shotaro
everyone
Really
Those who noticed
I don't know, but
I
Because I'm this kind of person
Even if I stand in the middle
After all, everyone
Many people
For holding me and supporting me
already
Warm
Someone like my older brother
He was already a family man
People like
Because that's fine for you
You can go with that humanity
Just those words are enough
I really have come this far
But still
When I look around,
After all, this time everyone
After all
Cress
I've seen your face after all
Really everyone
too
After all, the curtain won't open
There were many things that caused me anxiety.
I think there is.
That voice also reached me
It arrived directly after all
However, I also received a lot of criticism from the people around me.
What's going on?
Ride and enjoy
There are various messages
I saw the power of seeing.
just
I
I really believe in everyone
I'm working hard here
Because I've been watching everyone
Watch it.
Feelings
I just want you to wear it
That's really the only feeling
Not
Together
There are so many different
Overcoming a big wall
already
Even if the conversation doesn't change
Invisible
It's a bond
That's already the case
Don don don don
That means we're connected
I've been feeling this trend for a long time now
After all
Makuha is open
Jonah Joshi's
What is the other Yuya-san?
Really
We've talked about a lot of things up until today
Yesterday's Yuya's war loss
Watching Hiro's wartime success
After all,
There was today
One more
I feel like I've really completed it.
I got into the mood.
I've seen some really amazing things
on second thoughts
I'm glad I worked hard
Really already
As of yesterday, I felt
So today, everyone
so
I can see that face in Chi-up
Really I
With a heartfelt joy
There are lots
As it was at the beginning
I
I think it's a historic evolution.
To the world
Really already
We all worked hard to create it
already
This guy
This guy gave it to me in the field.
Together
I want to keep up
already
try as hard as one can
Climb, climb, climb, climb up the mountain
today
Really
I think I was able to make everyone happy.
Thank you so much
Me too
Really
I spoke without thinking
Maybe
no
That's not true
Some people may think that
This is definitely
already
It's my feelings
Campari's feelings
I
today
It may be a mistake
I think I've made everyone happy already.
It's okay to think that
Me too
where
Everyone did their best.
everyone
thank you
I
To dry this
Also
I hope that I will be able to meet you all in person soon. I also hope that this work will continue to remain not only in Japan, but all over the world.
I want to teach with big dreams.
Thank you very much.
So, I hope to finish it again soon, and thank you for watching today.
Thank you for watching.
Everyone, everyone and a little bit of everyone.
Because there are a lot of things going on.
Thank you everyone!
Thank you for watching.
Artwork
Gabies
。
I love you