WARNING
Everything’s working.
I’ve decided you’re worthy
of being confided in.
You have been chosen.
I’ve decided you’re worthy
of being confided in.
I’m leaving this record of my
will behind for the next generation.
After this, I am headed to an
archaeological site in Mexico.
Time has started to move again
after standing still for 49 years.
That is why I have to
create this record now.
If something should
happen to me, I—
Back to the story.
As you all know, this foundation
was created to support various fields,
All with the goal of contributing
to the welfare of humanity.
That’s how it looks on the outside.
Now, listen carefully.
And created our branches around the world...
There is a secret to why I established
this foundation here in the USA,
And created our branches around the world...
That secret is...
The Stone Mask.
[AZTEC CHANTING]
The true purpose of the foundation
is to solve the secret of the Stone Mask.
And also to tell you the story
of the golden spirit I once knew.
That’s why I’m here today, to leave
behind a record of the tale of that mask.
And also to tell you the story
of the golden spirit I once knew.
It all began in the 13th century.
They were members of the
people of the sun—the Aztecs!
Deep in the Central Mexican Plateau,
a tribe was raising a battle cry.
They were members of the
people of the sun—the Aztecs!
(Chief! Chief! Chief!)
[AZTEC CHANTING]
Blood be life, life be power
Eternal! Power! Eternal! Life!
Taken in this hand
Shalt thou become our life?
(With pleasure!)
The power in this hand
(Chief! Ha!)
(We, Aztecs, have drawn the sun’s wrath!)
However, at some point, that
tribe abruptly disappeared.
The mystery of this disappearance
lies in the Stone Mask.
This is the story of how the Stone Mask
Became entwined in the
unfortunate fate of two young men.
With that, let’s pick up the narrative
on the outskirts of London in 1868.
Bloody hell! This rain is awful,
it came outta nowhere!
Oi Cammie, you feelin’ cold?
I’ll warm you right up!
Why don’t we stay up all
night, you sweet little thing?
Your voice is sweeter
than birdsong, Debbie!
Wot have we here!
That carriage has gone and wrecked itself!
No one’s swarmed it yet! Alright!
First come, first served! Let’s go!
-Hurry up! C’mon, c’mon, c’mon!
I said wait!
Darling, wait! We really
shouldn’t be doing this!
Yahoo!
Look at that fancy carriage,
they gotta be nobles!
It’s a treasure hunt! C’mere and look!
Look at that fancy carriage,
they gotta be nobles!
It’s a treasure hunt! C’mere and look!
Look at that! What a
pretty necklace! All mine!
This box’ll have somethin’ good...
Don’t need that!
In the carriage! A baby survived!
One man’s misfortune is
another man’s fortune!
Aren’t these nice teeth?
They’ll fetch a pretty penny.
Nice teeth!
Aren’t these nice teeth?
They’ll fetch a pretty penny.
Nobles can buy replacement
teeth! And he’s a noble!
No bad deed done here. Just calm down.
You... Did you rescue us...?
Are my wife and son...?
She croa—
Your wife has already passed away
it seems, but your child is safe.
What about Red?
So this too is fate...
My name is Joestar...
I will never forget your kindness!
I don’t have a fancy name, but
please call me Brando.
Dario Brando!
Ah, Dario, beat Brando!
It’s an era filled with frenzy.
(Like the ground before a storm,
we’re thirsty with desire)
(The era is changing, and now is
the time to make ourselves rich)
Their hands were reaching out!
(In sunlight yellow day, with pride
in our queen, we pierce the horizon)
(In midnight blue darkness)
Those oh-so-familiar voices!
That voice, even
A suspicious voice
Speedwagon’s in da house!
While I’m passing down this
story to the future generations,
Let me tell you what’s going
on in this era and this land
Let Speedwagon tell you
all about this era and this land!
(The world is speeding up)
(The lamplight of the Industrial
Revolution burns bright)
(So we sleep with hope in our hearts)
(Should strife and inequality judge you)
And reach for the heavens!
(Reach out your hand to
the sunlight yellow beam)
(Set your soul aflame in
the beat of the steam)
The light!
(Throw away your fears,
and cut ties with your weaknesses)
(The midnight blue darkness is growing)
(The light!)
Rip through the wasteland!
Newborn babes crying out
in the midst of disparity
Fate’s thread is woven without any end
And just as with any adventure of men,
Always gorgeous but bizarre now and then
(The light!)
And just as with any adventure of men,
Always gorgeous but bizarre now and then
That’s right, this is
one Bizarre Adventure!
See with your own eyes the whole venture
That’s right, this is
one Bizarre Adventure!
(The dark!)
Behind me,
I'm in a car rush
yeah
oh!
Stop right there! I’ll kill you!
Oi!
Stop!
Shit—
C’mon, let’s go!
Nice!
Hey, look at ‘im. Bastard!
Don’t let this brat go!
Oi!
I haven’t seen him since
his pub went under!
He croak or somethin’?
I haven’t seen him since
his pub went under!
Word’s going around that
yer mum died in the plague!
He should have sold her off
before she kicked the bucket!
Dio! Can’t you hear me?! Dio!
He should have sold her off
before she kicked the bucket!
What is it, Father?
Oh... Do you need your medicine?
a
C’mere, I gotta tell you something.
I haven’t got much longer. I know it.
I’m worried that after I die...
My only child will be all by
himself. In that case... Dio,
Oi!
Take this.
Oh, dear dear dear dear
And he owes me one.
He’s a noble.
Okay?
When I die, send him that letter.
Go to him.
He’ll take care of you, you can
go to school. Sounds good, don’t it?
Oh! Make sure you put a stamp on it!
Now you start acting like a parent?!
Dio!
You’re a smart boy.
Don’t lose to anyone! Become
the richest man in the world!
Dio
How’s it going, I ask myself
They keep taking from me,
and it’s driving me mad
This place reeks of all these deadbeats
I might already be in hell,
the way it makes me sick
She held me and taught me to be proud
“Hey Dio, look up at the stars”
She kept on saying that,
until the illness took her
openly
Why are my hands always empty?
Am I just here to be taken from?
Tell me, Joestar, the sky
that you have over you
Is it blue?
This disgraceful father of
mine, the lowest of the low
A deadbeat will always be a deadbeat
Under this murky sky,
He struggled and struggled,
and this is how he’s gonna die
I’ll use any means, yes,
to set me on my path
I may have nothing in my hands yet,
That means I’ll start from here
Tell me, Joestar, in the sky over you,
Is the sun shining?
It is, isn’t it, Joestar?
You’ve got something good today too, eh?
Hey Erina, I heard that
your old man’s a quack!
My father’s a real doctor!
Oh really? This hat looks expensive!
Stop right there!
What are you doing?! Take this!
I hate when guys try to
act cool in front of girls!
-Hey, do you know who this guy is?
If he’s that Jonathan kid
from the Joestar family,
He is the Joestars’ Jonathan!
Snotty little rich boy! You think
you’re so high and mighty?
Eh?!
Let’s go already! Shit!
Uh... Are you alright?
I did this because I wanted to.
I didn’t do it to get you to thank me.
My goal is to become a true gentleman.
You were a damsel in distress,
so I had to stand up for you.
Let’s go, Danny!
Oh, wait!
Ah, wait a minute!
Jona-san Jowstar.
Okay, let's go!
You...
And you’re...
Jonathan Joestar?
Ah, Danny! I’ll introduce you.
This is my friend, Danny.
He’s a clever old hound!
Oh, and don’t worry about him biting!
Danny! What was that for!
We’ve been waiting for you, Dio Brando.
Lord Joestar!
From today on, you’ll be
living here in our mansion.
Something wrong, JoJo?
You’ll be given the same
kind of life as my son, JoJo.
I’m Police Inspector Archer!
I’m an old friend of the Joestars.
Although, I could hear Danny
whimper a moment ago...
-He came at me so suddenly.
When I jumped in surprise,
I think my leg may have hit him!
Danny is the Joestar household’s
wonderful guard dog.
He’s a friendly creature, but
I’m sorry he surprised you.
You’ll let this Danny matter go, right?
JoJo has lost his mother too—
and you both are the same age!
Make sure to get along with each other.
Now, allow me to show you to your room.
Nice to have met you!
Ta-ta, JoJo!
BLADDOG!
JoJo!
Don’t touch my bag!
Your hand is covered in dog drool.
Pardon me if I don’t want
it all over my things!
Alright JoJo, I’ll tell
you from the get-go.
I don’t care who you are,
no one looks down on me!
I was only trying to be friendly!
And one more thing—
I hate dogs.
Coming, Lord Joestar!
Thus, with this meeting, the
two boys’ youth had begun.
Thus, the two proofs met and the two players began.
We take on the duty of
becoming true gentlemen
Dioc.
Okay?
And arm ourselves with logic!
(The honourable Joestars!)
The same mistakes once again
How many times have
you made them! Six times!
It’s just because I love reading so much!
But they haven’t even
taught us this in school yet!
This is the sixth time
Bear in mind, as proud nobles,
We behave like true gentlemen
Sit up straight, use your knife with grace,
So that your mouth always remains spotless
For the sake of being loved as a Joestar!
Under the guidance of
the goddess of familial love
What’s this, JoJo? JoJo!
(The proud Joestars!)
Do you call yourself a gentleman?
What’s this, JoJo? JoJo!
Look at Dio’s elegant touch
His manners are perfect!
Take away JoJo’s plates!
You will go without dinner tonight!
Observe and follow Dio’s example
I am embarrassed by
how much I’ve spoiled you
My mother taught me well. She
always made sure I sat up straight.
Riwo
My mother taught me well. She
always made sure I sat up straight.
I
Bear in mind, as honourable nobles,
You
Such
Bear in mind, as honourable nobles,
In our hearts we must always consider
questions of philosophy and justice
Ikane
In our hearts we must always consider
questions of philosophy and justice
In our great England, a tale of two knights
has been passed down for generations.
One day, their master was
taken prisoner by the enemy.
The enemy was afraid of the
two knights, who had great power.
One day, their master was
taken prisoner by the enemy.
And so she gave them this condition:
“If you two will be executed in her place,
I will guarantee the life of your master.”
Here is my question for you:
-Yes, sir!
Those two knights who gave themselves
up as prisoners to save their master;
What was the first thing they
saw through their prison bars?
Those two knights who gave themselves
up as prisoners to save their master;
What was the first thing they
saw through their prison bars?
Was it the mud that lay before their eyes?
Or was it the stars shining above them?
What do you think?
The stars?
Or the mud?
Or
I...
I think they were looking at the mud.
What’s your reasoning?
In the end, they had no choice
but to die for their master.
Draw?
I
Draw
You can’t achieve anything if you’re dead.
So no matter what tricks
they would have had to pull,
I think...
They were looking at the stars!
The names of those two knights
will be etched into history!
They held onto their honour!
So what!
So what?
The way one lives, and the things
one does, those are important!
I
The way one lives, and the things
one does, those are important!
But they—
They were left empty-handed
in the end!
But they—
They were left empty-handed
in the end!
Such regret...
Such powerlessness...
What they saw was the mud!
They held onto their
pride until the very end!
They were looking at the stars! I think
they’re teaching us how we should live!
They held onto their
pride until the very end!
Listen!
解鋼
They
You’re a noble! You have it all!
You’ve lived by taking
from those beneath you!
What
this
So isn’t it your responsibility to think
about what you’ll achieve with your life?
That’s enough, you two.
There’s no right answer to this question.
Bear in mind—
All people live in a prison called fate
What to do
I
Reaching out through those bars,
Do they see the stars? Or the mud?
Either one could be said to be correct
So
What you can see is
Do you want
Or
Which one
Both
To the correct answer
A world without disparity, that’s sports
Everyone, gather around!
The winner is a sweeping hero
Who will be declared king?!
Here comes today’s challenger!
The opening bell rings
Shukyo
Here comes today’s challenger!
Hey hey, JoJo JoJo!
Oi!
That's how we deal with each other
Who
Decide who is the king
Return
The conch sounds
Today's Challenge
So
Come out
What is this move!
I’ve never seen it before!
With this rail, it keeps coming out!
It's Hong!
It's Feeket!
Yay!
Nodknocky!
I've never seen that before!
That’s a hit to the face!
He lost!
Our king! Our king!
My eye!
Guys, guys, guys!
-Hey, hey!
Dio, you were amazing!
How do you move like that?
Teach me!
Guys! Ow...
It was a foul on my part.
Danny...
Why is Dio always trying to bring me down?
Hey, Danny, my heart aches
Would anyone cry for me?
Thank you for staying by my side!
If mum were still here,
would it feel this way?
Would she love me this way?
You’re...
Is this how you loved me?
Hey, I’ll be back here tomorrow too,
So stop by again!
Hey, what's the flower pressure?
Has it caught your fancy?
It’s alright.
On the way back,
we had a carriage accident.
That was the time your dear
father saved us, you know.
On the way back,
we had a carriage accident.
That was the time your dear
father saved us, you know.
Are you interested in it?
Oh, no. Not especially.
JoJo is always out playing
with Danny, isn’t he?
It’s because of the trust and
friendship Danny has in JoJo.
I had bought Danny when JoJo was young.
And he didn’t get on well with JoJo yet.
There's friendship and trust
But one time, JoJo was drowning in a river.
There wasn’t even one person
around who could hear his voice.
Just when JoJo was about to drown...
A figure, hearing his screams,
flew down to the river.
He dove in and saved JoJo’s life.
Danny was brave to have risked
his own life to save another.
Young JoJo was moved by Danny’s bravery.
That’s when JoJo truly
became friends with him.
Young JoJo was moved by Danny’s bravery.
Eh? Ah, that’s right.
Is that so?
A young woman
Friends...
The two met once more!
Love! That wonderful curiosity
that guided JoJo’s actions.
JoJo was instantly
head over heels for her.
ah
JoJo was instantly
head over heels for her.
Come boy!
Oh, you’re so clever to eat
the fruit but not the core.
Hey JoJo, what are you carving over there?
What are you hiding?
I won’t laugh.
Be well behaved
Erina, just saying your
name makes me feel at ease
no
Any musician would fall
in love with its melody
It puts me in such a good mood
Any musician would fall
in love with its melody
To be laughing like this
There’s nothing but blue skies
here in vibrant Liverpool
Erina
Our happiness is right here
The clouds are proud, and
the wind’s a little sweet
Erina
There aren’t enough words
For these ever overflowing feelings
I want to hear your voice
say, “it makes me happy”
That would be so
embarrassing, you—
Scoundrel!
forever
Then find a reason,
let’s make it our reason!
I don’t know why, but I’m drawn to you
Then find a reason,
let’s make it our reason!
Your hand,
My hand,
When they’re apart I feel so lost
It gives me a little courage
to move forward to tomorrow
Our hearts are resonating,
beating in time
Drawing us together, these
fleeting feelings surround us
Touching
Drawing us together, these
fleeting feelings surround us
It’s already this late!
Erina!
I’ll see you tomorrow!
Yes, JoJo!
The one I’m so strongly
drawn to, his name is...
Jonathan Joestar
Huh, okay?
Huh
You’re Erina Pendleton, right?
I heard you were hanging
out with JoJo today.
What do you...
Ugh
It's Erina Pendleton.
Today is
With my superior
They were just playing
that
something
wall
He...
He did it!
Ugh
You haven’t, have you?
It was me, Dio!
You know what this sort of thing
means for a lady’s reputation, right?
She’s—!
What are you doing washing
my kiss away with mud?!
My first partner is not Chojo
This is Dio
Dio...
Get up, bitch!
What’re you sleeping for?
Mum! Mum!
I’m sorry! Please forgive me!
Of course you shouldn’t go to the shops!
In tough times like these, I’ve
gotta work for your sake too.
Please, you’ve got to get well!
What's the big sale?
Dio...
Can’t you hear my voice?
The voice calling for you?
But our money’s already—
Father!
Why don’t I send him a letter...
No...
You and I are different!
Dio...
Magara
Crack
Dio...
Dio, how could you do such a thing?
How could you hurt her like that!
Follow
What in the world have I ever done
to you?! Can you tell me, Dio?
Haa
You’re so amazing, so
much more than I am
Haa
Dio!
Aren’t you using my name
So you’ve heard? What I
did to your beloved Erina?
-You’ve disgraced her!
So you’ve heard? What I
did to your beloved Erina?
-You’ve disgraced her!
DIO: I bet you’re mad with jealousy!
JOJO: This is for her sake, not mine!
Only in my heart
I have to stand up to him, even
if I can’t beat him. I cannot lose!
Haa
Control your emotions, you’re
different from that drunken lout
On the blood resonating in my heart,
I swear to restore her honour, Dio!
you
I’ll put you back in your place,
I’ll teach you a lesson you won’t forget
On the blood resonating in my heart,
I swear to restore her honour, Dio!
I’ll put you back in your place,
I’ll teach you a lesson you won’t forget
nine
Haa
Come at me!
This new power arising within me
It feels so good!
Dominate
You’re the one who lit this fire in me
Dio!
I won’t stop beating you until you cry!
Haa
I miss you
How dare you do this to me?
You scum of the earth!
How dare such scum like
you come at me, Dio!
Me, the great Dio!
Lost
Haa
What on earth is going on?!
too
You two! You’ll be punished for this!
Now go back to your rooms!
surely
Konoha
Better
Like this
Like winning
Cheap
This me
this
Looks good on you
Like this
Dio...
Cheap
That stupid kiss of yours hurt
me more than you intended!
Ah... Eri—
Give a penalty
I feel so miserable!
Haa
Erina!
Yes, Father.
Haa
Erina...
His resilience...
I have to become stronger...
So that I can become
a gentleman at heart!
So that I can take everything from him!
He looked down on women.
His explosive power
I need to develop that mental strength even more.
However...
What’s that noise?
But
What's that sound?
Is there anyone in honesty?
Are you going to try to go outside?
Oh my god
Someone please
Hmm
You’re... You’re certain,
that it was the Stone Mask?
The one excavated from Mexico?
It was quite a while ago...
A while?! Could you please clarify?
Yes, I’m certain, sir.
Some gentleman’s wife
fell in love with it,
Yes, I’m certain, sir.
And bought it from me at a high price—
Yes!! Finally! I found it!
Now, where could I find this gentleman—
Wait a minute!
Who the hell are you anyway?
I apologise. My name
is Zeppeli, and I’m a baron.
I came from Italy to
find the Stone Mask.
All the way from Italy?!
Wait, he said he was
a nobleman from up north...
I’ll go check in the books!
Thank you.
Just a little word of warning...
The sun will be setting soon.
Okay
It’s better if you don’t
go beyond that street.
in
It’s better if you don’t
go beyond that street.
A fog has rolled in...
(A palpable shadow stretches over the city)
(And soon it’ll swallow the sun whole)
(Don’t let it get you,
fight as hard as you can!)
April
Ha
(Don’t let it get you,
fight as hard as you can!)
(Fog and smog cover the city,
hiding the smell of crime)
(Stretch out your hands towards the light)
The filth rubs off on the clean
and gathers like grime
topknot
The filth rubs off on the clean
and gathers like grime
Thrown away with the rubbish
Pressed together, our
lot gives off a stench
The sweet smell of darkness
Is comforting to us
(Something’s wrong, people
are thirsty, distorted, broken!)
Is comforting to us
(Something’s wrong, people
are thirsty, distorted, broken!)
(Jack the Ripper has drawn first blood!)
(Hate the poor, hate the
rich, and raise your voice)
(Gather here and now, Jacks of this town!)
Legs
(Rebellion is now!)
In 1887, in Trafalgar Square
(We raise our voices!)
The rich in their ivory towers
(Give us equality! Work! And money!)
(Give us food! Every day! Let us live!)
(The world is ever accelerating)
Away from there now, in Liverpool,
seven years have flown by
Rebellion is stopped in its tracks,
blood floods the streets of London
Away from there now, in Liverpool,
seven years have flown by
Their graduation year
Their graduation? But who are “they”?
So dazzling, brightly
shining, a pair of stars
(Now is the time to raise our voices!)
Canelo
He’s got it!
The star of Hugh Hudson, our very
own Jonathan Joestar, grabs the pass!
Firmly
Red
(He’s like a heavy locomotive!)
(Keep pushing forward, JoJo!)
(The pride of our school!)
(Is he finally wavering?)
(Dio Brando)
(Leaving them all behind)
(Once again, Dio catches the pass)
So
(Our school’s pride!)
(JoJo and Dio!)
Oh
Uuuuu
(In perfect harmony, they
make the best partners!)
The final match of the
season ends in victory!
That was magnificent!
It was all thanks to your pass!
Right, JoJo?
Let’s go and tell Father
about it right away!
Can we write about your friendship
with JoJo for the school newspaper?
Shall we go home together?
Let me get changed first.
Time passed like the
endless flow of water
Ever since you started
calling him “Father”
I think of that word
which is so familiar to me
Ever since you started
calling him “Father”
Seven years spent studying diligently
You’re... beautiful,
and a true gentleman
Seven years spent studying diligently
You’re... beautiful,
and a true gentleman
My friend, who’s always
pushing me to be better
You’ve repented for the
wrong you did to Erina
You’ve offered me a shoulder
to lean on, now that Danny’s gone
think
We walked this path
together for seven years
I always followed in your
footsteps, one step behind,
beautifully
I always followed in your
footsteps, one step behind,
So why is it that I don’t
feel any friendship for you?
You are
I was eating
Danny's replacement
You are
He supported me.
How are you feeling?
Well, I’m old enough now that
a mere cold can last a long time.
Sir, you’re not that old yet!
Well, I’m old enough now that
a mere cold can last a long time.
Sir, you’re not that old yet!
JoJo and Dio Brando, they...
And JoJo has become
a splendid gentleman.
His recent archaeology thesis is superb!
And Dio is projected to graduate
top of his class in law school.
I admire you! Back then—
I’m home!
Yes?
Dio! Welcome back!
Ah, and JoJo as well!
Father!
Dio! Welcome back!
Ah, and JoJo as well!
Are you alright?
Today, the doctor recommended
I be admitted to hospital.
I object!
They say it’s a problem in London too.
It’s true...
I feel safer at home.
I give in.
Dio is back
Enough of that. You two...
Congratulations on your victory!
You already know?
Inspector Archer here told me.
We wanted to see Father’s face light up...
Oh no, silly me!
I truly am proud.
I have such wonderful sons.
Feel free to do whatever
you like after graduation.
But you gave me a chance.
I was born poor...
Well then, I’ll be off.
Inspector, thank you for always visiting.
I have a busy night ahead of me, with
the likes of Jack the Ripper out there.
But this is Liverpool!
There are men like him without
any humanity everywhere.
Now, if you’ll pardon me.
Especially Dio
You did really well
After the measures
Be what you want to be
To me, born of poor origins
Give it a chance
thank you
The spring mechanism only reacts to blood...
Who on earth made this...
If I solved this riddle, it might cause a
sensation in the archaeology department.
If that happened, this mask that my
mother bought would have a fate of its own.
So
do
Thank you again, Master Dio—
“Right now... I’m sick.”
“My heart hurts,”
“And I can’t stop coughing.”
Dio...
Also for the shape
Mum died and left me alone
Yes, alone with that piece of shit!
I
I endured no matter what
Yes, until the day finally came
Bloody hell! Ever since that wench
died I’ve been crumbling in debt!
Yes, until the day finally came
Bloody hell! Ever since that wench
died I’ve been crumbling in debt!
I don’t bloody need it anymore!
Are you bloody deaf, Dio?!
yes
How hellish that your blood
is flowing through my veins
Pawn
I’ll bury you and this damn curse
yes
I will take everything
into my own two hands!
Zexal
I’ll stay on top, even to
the limits of my humanity
Yes.
I’ll stay on top, even to
the limits of my humanity
I will find the resolve, plan ahead,
And then, hiding behind a mask—
Dario Brando, my wretched father
May you rot in hell,
together with the past
Stolen
A world where everything is perfect,
In the palm of your hand, Dio!
Flowing
Zexal
white
This hunt
All
Dio!
What’s the matter, JoJo?
I found this letter from your
father, from seven years ago.
It details your father’s symptoms
at the time of his death.
Huh?
They’re the same symptoms as my father’s.
Are you always the one who
brings Father his medicine?
What is this non—
Answer me!
I’m going to have this
medicine investigated.
What on earth are
you trying to say?!
Then you doubt our very friendship.
As a gentleman,
If you can swear on your father’s honour,
Swear on that guy?
Dio,
Swear on it.
DIO: Swear on it?
JOJO: Come on, swear on it!
My
Give me the medicine back!
That scum has never had any
honour for me to swear on!
You
Give me the medicine back!
was carrying
What
Start talking
Answer me
you
Go
I won’t ever let you go
near my father again!
I’m convinced now...
I won’t ever let you go
near my father again!
That there was never any
friendship between us to begin with!
This is all a
misunderstanding, JoJo!
I’ll protect the Joestar family.
Just a misunderstanding...
Besides...
It’s not like you have
any proof, do you?
地獄
Nothing more than a flimsy theory.
I
I despised my father, hated
him more than anything.
I just lost my temper when
you started suspecting me...
JoJo! JoJo!!
JoJo...
Is something the matter, Master Dio?
No...
I’m alright...
close
It’s too late to turn back now.
In the palm of your hand, Dio!
Father!
-Father!
What’s all this ruckus for?
yes
Please don’t accept any care
or medicine from anyone else.
Excuse me, but—
We’ll do as he says.
I don’t know what’s going on...
Thank you, Father.
no
Seven years ago, this thing...
It moved in reaction to my blood.
Get it
no
How about it?
With this...
I’ll make it appear as if he had
an accident during his research.
Will be the death of you!
Seven years ago, this guy reacted to me, what happened?
8 years
Ogre Street, the place
where plagues are born
Before my eyes lies
the underbelly of society
But I have a reason why I must move forward
(Ogre Street, we devour anything we can)
(Ogre Street, here everything meets its end)
Dunno what the hell
you came here for
Got no problem with you bein’ naïve,
I’m just showin’ you the simple reality
Want a taste of the
edge of this knife?
We’re gonna strip you of all that you got
Put up a fight and your life will be lost
From your life to that foolish
heart—we’ll steal ‘em away!
Is this guy insane?!
(Ogre Street, go on and leave it all behind)
(Ogre Street, we’ll even fill
our stomachs with your life)
(Ogre Street, why don’t we
put that resolve to the test?)
Hold on! I only came here
looking for a poison seller!
Quit bluffin’! Let me have a
go at this soft little rich boy!
Hoga Street, now I know we're just a little old
Bowery, life is Ongar
If you keep moving like this, you won't be able to escape to the cracks
That’s the sound of blade hitting bone!
Three, two, one!
There is in the family
Stop, everyone!
I came here for the sake of my father.
So in the moment I kicked,
Someone bandage his wound.
‘Cause I’ve taken a liking to ya!
(Ogre Street)
With your determination to fight
(You, who have the courage)
(To see the stars down here in the mud)
(Light up the darkness with
your unwavering heart!)
Brought me completely to my knees
Jora-san, Joestar-san, in the case of Dokkuek, the name is Wanchi
If you're not careful, you'll get caught out. Be careful.
I'll guide you through the process of speeding you down
Why did I like you?
Gantdown Slis Hwaga Street
It's a hidden flame
Quickly take out the
See which run
Dio...
JoJo has gone off to London...
Or could he have found
evidence of the medicine?
-Shut up, get out of my head!
-You piece of shit, we’re not the same!
Oi, are you listening, you stupid brat?
JoJo...
Huh...
…
How dare you! You bastard!
What did you do to my mate?!
…
Is another man’s fortune!
What’re you mumbling about?!
…
It’s a live human experiment!
Dio Dio Dio Dio Dio!
JoJo!
[AZTEC CHANTING]
What is this light?
Was I hallucinating?
He’s dead...
This mask is just some ancient
sacrificial torture device.
Wow
He’s not dead!
Delicious
Fangs?! What is he?!
Wow
Make it plump
Pukula
Should I do it or paint it?
This white machine
Also, the company
Let me come over
It's a journey of success
Hehehehe
I’m thirsty, thirsty, so thirsty!
He’s sucking my blood!
His face is...
Ah
I don’t want the morning sun
to be the last thing I ever see!
Benge Gong
Dead
If this much koshin is stabbed in the head, it's only natural that he'll be punished.
I was saved...
Mamachi
By the sunlight...
m
Change
Undevide apply
Dragon
So this...
Is the power of the Stone Mask.
already
I'm excited about you
So, where is Dio?
It seems he hasn’t come
home since last night.
Please use the foyer.
This Asian fellow,
Wang Chan—take him away.
Yes sir!
Dio’s father...
I’ll tell you about it.
This is certainly my ring,
It was obvious that it was stolen!
Yes, it’s the ring I had made with my wife.
Tears welled up in his eyes.
I arrested the criminal!
Stealing from a noble is a heavy offence.
Here he is! Oi! Wake up! Brando!
Brando?!
I
But a thief!
Even knowing this,
Lord Joestar adopted Dio.
Why?
I was moved to tears by
what Lord Joestar said next.
Did he tell you...
But
That I gave him this ring?
Yes, he said that. A lie!
It’s not a lie.
This is what I gave him.
He is innocent.
This is yours.
With this ring, please buy
what you need for your family.
Lord Joestar! Are you taking the piss?!
With this ring, please buy
what you need for your family.
I
If only I had caught Hajiri
Would you like to wish me a happy birthday?
If I were suffering from poverty
curler
Hey
If I were suffering from poverty
Planned
I would have done the same
thing, yes, for the ones I love
Stop
I would have done the same
thing, yes, for the ones I love
Just
I would have done the same
thing, yes, for the ones I love
When the stars in the sky
shine, they start to tell a story
Dio
When the stars in the sky
shine, they start to tell a story
Why
I
When the stars in the sky
shine, they start to tell a story
you
he
Let’s pray that this light
will illuminate the darkness
Ugh
Yes.
Thank you, sir!
You are too good-natured!
This scumbag will laugh at
you tomorrow morning!
yes
This scumbag will laugh at
you tomorrow morning!
That may be true,
From the prison called fate,
people reach for the stars
But think about it the other way around.
From the prison called fate,
people reach for the stars
Let’s embrace that courage,
that loneliness,
That pain
Everything is connected
There’s a meaning to it all
I believe in humanity
and all of its resolve
I can’t see stars or nothin’!
That’s bollocks!
I believe in humanity
and all of its resolve
I’ll keep on believing
That this gold I’ve passed on
you
With all of my resolve...
But
Will shine one day
I will defy fate!
from
Inspector.
I’ll wait for Dio.
To everything
Garu
I
Believe in people
With a secret
For your viewing pleasure
Good
I heard a bizarre rumour on the streets.
someday
And then...
I
It’s the same as what
happened 30 years ago...
a
It’s a wedge driven into
the wasteland of my memory
At dawn, a blood-red sun
rose over the Atlantic Ocean
Full of passion and yearning
for the unknown world
I
Full of passion and yearning
for the unknown world
still
I crossed the seven seas
with my respected father
You
The Stone Mask took
everything away from me
I swore I’d get revenge,
that I’d take it all back
Maybe not today, but
there’s always tomorrow
“A man is what he thinks
about all day long.”
There’s a saying that goes like that.
Kusabi
The Stone Mask...
If I don’t find it, I can’t
recover what I’ve lost.
It was red
Full of passion
I, Dio, was...
Shit...
My beloved father
I see you’ve returned from London—
I have the antidote now.
From this hand
It’s a shame it had
to come to this, Dio.
It truly hurts me.
Although you might not believe me,
Those are my true feelings.
You’re honest like that.
Although it’s selfish,
I have a favour to ask—
The final one
I will ask of you.
I...
Because I was born into squalor...
My ambition was relentless.
I want to repent for my sins!
Don’t believe a word he says!
I can see from your face that
you’re wondering who I am.
Growing up in the darkest slums,
So I can tell all I need to know
about a person just from their smell.
Worse than vomit!
He was born evil!
This man has confessed already.
I’ve heard everything I need to.
I will return to my bed to rest.
I don’t want to see my son
being taken away in handcuffs.
You won’t succeed in arresting that man...
He was born with an innate destiny.
Come on—
JoJo, I understand!
Arrest me.
I want you to be the
one who handcuffs me.
I am
For the sake of those seven
years we spent together.
I will handcuff you.
I've seen a lot of different people
To be human is to have limits
That’s what I’ve come to realise
The more I see the limitations of this life
I’m always coming up empty-handed
or
This prison I’m trapped in,
it’s slathered in mud
I can’t see the stars, and no
matter how hard I struggle,
My eyes are still blinded
Don’t you get it?
It’s crushing me!
I can’t reach up this way
Yes, Joestar, even
your purest pedigree,
Can’t wash the filth out of mine
To break free, from this cage
The stars!
The Stone Mask?
I...
Reject...
My humanity!
JoJo!
Stop!
-JoJo!
-Father!
Shoot him!
Lord Joestar!
Father! Father!
JoJo...
This is...
Your late mother’s ring.
Please... don’t blame Dio for this.
Maybe... the fact that
I was so hard on you...
Mom
Life
It’s not so bad...
Right
To die...
Yes
In my son’s arms.
Hahahaha
Yes
I knew I made a mistake, back then.
You always told me to be a gentleman
To always live with pride
Even though I said I’d save you,
Even though you said you believed me!
What does it mean
to be a gentleman?
Father, open your eyes!
What’s the purpose of
This Joestar blood
flowing through my body?
Carrying yourself with
discipline and pride
Your resolve to shine a beacon
through the dark wastelands
Survey
I’ll engrave your will into my soul
Take pride in this heart
that shines like gold!
This Joestar blood
flowing through my body!
I’ll fight against this fate,
keep sorrow at bay
With just one drop of courage!
Survey results
Inspector! It’s an emergency!
What did you say?!
Inspector!
Look up at the stars
Even though we shot him into Swiss cheese!
What the hell?! He came back to life!
Shoot him! Don’t just
stand there! Quickly!
I don’t get it! I can’t make heads
or tails of what’s happening!
JoJo!
Can you hear my voice?
H-He’s sucking his blood!
I'm sad about this fate
You’re—
From the Stone Mask...
From your father’s blood!
Run away, Mr. Joestar!
You’ll only get killed!
That monster is too bloody strong!
The brain!
If that’s the case...
I’ll have to completely destroy his head!
Utero
Don't be silly
It's early
I don't know above
I must...
I must make my will stronger!
Suddenly puffed up...
JoJo!
Weak! So weak!
Let me enjoy this amazing power
for just a little longer!
After all, I still don’t know
what I’m capable of yet!
A quick fix to the running.
JoJo...
That running thing appears.
I told you, didn’t I?
Humans have limits!
You and your friend
can become my lifeforce!
Already
It’s courage!
Crab Cui Crab Cui
a!
Come, Dio.
Is that an invitation, JoJo?
(The flash of flames,
scattering the light)
I’ll put an end to you and
your cursed powers here!
It’s useless! Useless! Useless!
I’ll suck you dry!
(Flickering from light to dark)
I always walked in your shadow
You were always right behind me
It’s time for us to say goodbye to it
The Joestar manor is burning
And Father is dead!
I’ve lost everything, save for my life
ah
Run in the dark
Mr. Joestar was surely thinking,
That a stronger fire could overpower
that demon’s healing ability.
“If only the flames were
even hotter!” But by then...
Damn it! Mr. Joestar!
It's useless, it's useless
If you suck that life out
This flickering
Not from afar
Let's give one
Give me your strength
From now on, always
From your back
On my back,
This body is immortal.
The only one dying will be you!
Women
(Equally doling out love and judgement)
-JoJo!
I won’t let go of this knife,
The knife you stabbed Father with!
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
With this final bit of strength
(The goddess of familial love
is flickering in flames)
(Equally doling out love and judgement)
more
This can’t be how my life ends—
JoJo!!
It's your fault, I almost fell into the basement
Where do you approach? I've grown fond of you
Can you hear me?
You can hear me.
I hope you had a nice intermission.
I’ve returned in order to
continue telling our story,
Of the world to which all of
you have become witnesses.
I want the whole acrylic stand collection.
Yes.
Much more bizarre.
But Mr. Joestar survived.
But lost everything.
Can you hear me?
I can hear you
I mentioned the Astika people before.
The mask that man wore!
If I have this mask—
JoJo, can you hear me?
it was good
I’m not much,
After carrying the unconscious Mr. Joestar
to the hospital, I came back to visit him!
Can I help you?
This room doesn’t allow visitors.
Is he alright?! Oi, hold it—
Refreshing
JoJo...
Can you hear me?
You recognise it, right?
From that bright, fleeting moment
when we were drawn together
I want to hear your voice again too
Where am I...?
You’re—
Like Erina Pendleton?
How?
It’s really been too long.
I was childish back then,
I couldn’t face you
Your voice is still the same
There’s nothing but blue skies
here in vibrant Liverpool
Oh, I’m sorry! I must have
lost my focus and fainted.
I can see it there
Your hand
I
Now our hearts
resonate, beating as one
Please stay calm now
Now our hearts
resonate, beating as one
Drawn together on that fleeting day
Just the two of us
Fate? That’s right.
Maybe some people are
just fated to meet one another.
Fate? That’s right.
Why
Maybe some people are
just fated to meet one another.
Speedwagon coolly withdraws.
It's really been a while
I was weak
It wasn't my first time with you
It was me who was young
He’s struck again,
that bloodthirsty maniac
Her throat was slit
(And she had her guts ripped out!)
The utmost cruelty!
The truth of the
matter is out of reach!
Elina
sorry
(Only killing prostitutes,
throwing their guts up on the wall)
(Only found in fog and
darkness, that’s Jack—)
Jack the Ripper!
You’re kidding!
I have to return home soon...
It’s a terrifying thought!
Terrifying, is it?
You’re talking with him right now!
attract
fit
You’re out playing too late,
You dirty harlot!
yes
Who goes there?
I like you.
Now that you’ve seen me, I’ll—
I don’t feel any pain, I’ve
got nothing to fear anymore
Oh, I must heal these wounds,
and for that I’ll need lives!
Don’t you want power?
Not to mention a
faithful servant—Jack!
(Power and pleasure!)
This I will grant you!
Humans are bound by notions of virtue.
Those are the evil elite.
Like myself, and you as well!
How about it? Will you
become my, Dio’s, companion?
What do you know about me?!
I understand you, Jack.
You’re angry at them, right?
Women who are
dripping with ecstasy
Go and spill more guts! There’s
no need to be afraid anymore
(Power and pleasure!)
Jack! You don’t have
to worry anymore
That’s right!
I’ll give you pleasure greater
than you’ve known before
I’m not scared of anything!
Break out from the narrow
confines of your prison
Come to my side, Jack the Ripper!
Who are you?
I’ll start to live from this moment on
I don’t need it anymore!
(Blood, flesh, devour it all!)
you
This is Dio’s World!
I don't feel any pain
There's no more of that
Reborn now
Let's start my life
I have to heal my ache
I need life
So I feel less fulfilled
Don't you want power?
The Stone Mask...
I want to believe it turned
to dust like everything else.
It has to have been.
It’s alright.
Let’s go.
How about it?
What’s wrong?
Jonathan Joestar!
Has he been here
this whole time?
And Miss Erina Pendleton.
Such
You’ve done well to survive
the power of the Stone Mask!
The Stone Mask?!
It seems like it will change
There's already one
Yes.
Well then
Squeeze out
Every last ounce
Of air inside your lungs!
How could you, he’s injured!
What?! My broken arm—
It doesn’t hurt anymore!
Jack
I am Baron Zeppeli!
I am on your side!
I am your ally, Jonathan Joestar!
I manipulated your breath, your
breath made the pain go away
I am your ally, Jonathan Joestar!
What did you do to me?!
How do you know my name!
Hey JoJo, one question at a time!
I’ll show you the answer,
just come along with me
If you do, your fate will change
Whether you accept that or not
The choice is up to you!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
Let me demonstrate for you
became
(In, out!)
In the blood it sends racing
他の棚同城細相信台
Its name is—
It's okay
Are you okay
(Memetaa!)
The ripple’s power
passes through the frog
Making this miracle happen—
That is the power of the ripple
The power this breathing
infuses into your blood!
That is the power of the ripple
(In, out)
Breathing?
It does things like carry nutrients
and regulate your body temperature.
The power of the ripple gathers that small
amount of energy from all over the body.
By air
The power of the ripple gathers that small
amount of energy from all over the body.
Breathing created that power?!
Yes! The power of breathing!
Yes, I know it all
In, out!
So too are you and Dio!
The mask is not broken—he has it!
The man wearing the mask, Dio,
walks in the darkness even now!
Pursuing the mask
So that I can destroy it!
We must fight!
Dio is alive?!
We must destroy it!
And you must wield this
ripple energy, or you will die!
That’s right, your fate,
and the fate of the world
It has been set in motion!
Will I get my hands on it? Our fates
Are all tied together. This is—
Smart
Destiny!
To fight... That is my destiny!
Horororororororororororororororororororororororororororo
That turns humans into vampires.
Beings who must get energy
by taking the blood of others.
It’s the same energy, like
two sides of the same coin.
However, the ripple also derives its
power from the flow of the bloodstream.
It’s the same energy, like
two sides of the same coin.
Ah, let’s put it this way.
What must you do to stop that ripple?
I think I’ve got it!
Use a ripple!
If you hit them with another
ripple, they’ll break apart!
And that wave of energy
If you hit them with another
ripple, they’ll break apart!
Has the same shape as the light of the sun!
The power to defeat Dio!
You must learn how to turn
your courage into power!
What do you mean, Dio?
I can’t get you involved in this!
For now, please just go along with it!
How...?
Is this the power of JoJo’s ripple?
If you don't destroy it
In the hands of destruction
Well, is there any more?
Yours
Your world
Fate is weak and sluggish
I finally found it
Tattered and worn
Do you accept it?
Eyes working hard
The clouds are drifting by
and the wind is swirling round
Sma
Leaving memories behind
Stars are drawn together
Guided by this hapless fate
As I wander here, mired in mud
I am left behind
I live in a dream,
waiting by the window
Jamon
Even if it doesn’t reach you,
even if it won’t bring you back to me,
I want to scream!
You are drawn to me
Because you left for my sake
Forever guided by fate
I’ll live my days, spinning its thread
While looking up at the stars
This is
Is it a female jamon?
So that one day you’ll tell me the story,
JoJo!
Guided by this hapless fate
Stars are drawn together
Our stars shine together
No matter where you are, I will, I will,
I will live on!
Left behind
Living the dream
Wang Chan, you’re alive?!
Even if it doesn't reach
Even if it doesn't shine now
C’mere!
I
Even if it doesn't shine now
I want to scream
I
Why are you so strong?!
Speeeedwagon!
You know too much about
the secret of the Stone Mask!
I
You know too much about
the secret of the Stone Mask!
Mr. Joestar!
I wa-ha-ha-was looking for you too!
Because, because Lord Dio
said I could slurp up your blood!
He’s strong enough to rival you.
What was that, you old fart?
Let's continue to exist
Your everything
Acceptance
His arm... got longer!
yes
The stars
Daylight
Your
Don't let your destiny lead you
The stars
Daylight
It’s useless.
I’ve been given new life!
I
Me
That’s not what’s important here.
M-My body...
It’s hot!
Go
Kiev
I lost so much...
Going
But not this...
Not the same as Dio’s!
Go
Wear
But it’s the same power!
Wihaha
Weано
Wear
“The north wind created the brave vikings!”
Because they knew the pain
of the harsh northern winds,
They became vikings with backbone!
Because you feel the pain.
The pain of losing friends
The pain of inheriting your family’s pride
Oooooohhhh!
Even for those you want to protect—
The pain of inheriting your family’s pride
Pain is proof they’re alive
You need to listen to that pain!
I was always told to be a gentleman
I still don’t understand what
it means to be a true gentleman
We embrace this pain
It was pure coincidence!
It’s a wedge driven into the
wasteland of my memories
Gon!
My father and I once
crossed the seven seas
One quiet and calm night
The mask burst with light
見事だ、少少
The man in the mask came forward
ZEP: Clothed in blood and darkness
JOJO: The same as it was then!
What I saw in that moment, illuminated
by the salvation of the morning sun, was—
It was my father!
Under the red light of the
morning sun, my father disappeared
We embrace this pain
ZEP: I’ve been chasing after it
JOJO: So that it won’t repeat
ZEP: I swore to take revenge
JOJO: I won’t let you down!
ZEP: So that tomorrow will be
JOJO: Shining bright
You
We embrace this pain!
What you need is the courage
to make that pain your own!
And the resolve to face the consequences.
Red
I'll listen to the pain
Hey JoJo.
JoJo JoJo JoJo.
Hey-ha-hey-ha JoJo.
Don’t forget this goal.
I like your fringe.
Hey JoJo, JoJo!
The day screen
Emits light
Perspective
Repeatedly, the liquid
Holding this pain
Why, why?!
Jonathan Joestar!
Lord Dio! It hurts! Where are you?
Are you angry?
You’re good company, huh?
Oh! It burns! It burns!
Is that Mr. Horse?
Look Wang Chan!
Your, your ancestors—
There he is.
The lovable sweetheart, Mr. Joestar,
has finally got a handle on the ripple
These bills been piling piling up
Who else would be your guide
To this 16 bar showtime?
We drove, no stopping sites
That famous city of knights
Windknight’s Lot
While the sun’s out
We’ll knock it out
Clean this vampire nest out
You play with life, that’s bullshit!
Thanks for keeping watch, Speedwagon.
and
Without a doubt, this is where
Dio is building his own empire.
The entrance to the town
is through this tunnel.
Yes, we’re arriving according to plan.
Oi, driver, why are we stopped here?
Be careful! The sun doesn’t reach here.
What is he...
I
Give me a little taste of your fresh blood!
Surprise fall
It's a horse
JoJo, here’s a battle lesson!
You’ve heard of fleas, yes?
They come after us humans
even though we’re giants to them.
Could you call something
like that “courageous”?
What are you yammering on about!
So then, what exactly is “courage”?
Surrendering to that fear
throws your breath out of sync.
“Fear” sends your breathing awry!
Surrendering to that fear
throws your breath out of sync.
The ripple breathing technique
is a product of courage!
The hymn of humanity
is a song of courage!
The greatness of humanity
is the greatness of courage!
These zombies, no matter how
strong, know nothing of courage!
The greatness of humanity
is the greatness of courage!
These zombies, no matter how
strong, know nothing of courage!
They’re just like fleas!
Hot, so hot!
How dare you! I’ll kill you!
Yes... I’ll eat every
shred of you in one bite!
Windknight’s Lot...
There’s also a vast catacomb underground.
They’re inviting us. We must go farther.
Yes. Dio’s surely at the end of the trail.
This is the entrance to the city.
The projection area is as planned.
Hey! Win the race!
Why stop place
Be careful
Dio doesn't have a strong hand here.
Look!
Can you hear me?
Follow me, serve royalty once again
That’s this world, the
unwavering world of Dio
Your long silence has
left this world to rot
Now raise your voices,
from crushed throats
I’ll allow you this and more!
Crying out from the mud,
conquer the stars
I’ll allow you this and more!
(My sword, it’s yours!)
(We’ve been sleeping for 300 years,
us rotten and forgotten corpses)
(Now is the time to raise our voices)
(We’ve been sleeping for 300 years,
us rotten and forgotten corpses)
Wrrryyy!
300 years asleep, haunted
by painful thoughts
(Wry wry, we vow to destroy!)
(Wry wry, we vow to kill!)
(Wry wry!)
Wait, Dio!
Come quick, JoJo.
Cover
(Wry wry!)
My world is in the palm of my hand now!
I will dominate life at last,
Tearing its natural
order from God’s grasp
I will dominate history too,
Rewriting and upending it anew
azz
so
My body eternal and sublime
I will dominate everything,
rise above all my cares
(We vow to steal them away!)
Kun
Win it all, negate righteousness
And demand peace of mind!
(Wry wry, we vow to kill!)
This is Dio’s World!
It’s melting...
So much that there’s a hole in my cheek...
And your tongue is sticking
out of the hole? Really, Jack?
It’s time for your lives
to go down with it!
I’ve been building up my
courage for this moment!
Even so, I can’t help
this feeling of dread.
Put your training to use.
I remember shouting from the sky
(We’ll feast! On your blood and flesh!)
(To heal all of our wounds!)
JoJo, here’s a lesson for you
This battle will be an exercise—
SPW: We’re not here to play around, have you lost it?
ZEP: You shut your trap!
The north wind made the vikings!
JACK: I’ll kill them!
DIO: Ah—wait, wait—
Will this wine make a viking out of you?
Make fear your own!
Here’s a battle lesson:
Muster up your courage! When the time
comes, don’t let your breathing go awry!
Make fear your own!
Here’s a battle lesson:
Search
The hymn of humanity is a song of courage!
The greatness of humanity is
the greatness of courage!
Search
Don’t let your breathing go awry!
This wine will be my north wind!
(Give us your blood!)
I can feel it flow, I’ll find my
way through the darkness!
With the power of the sun!
Pa-pow-pow-pow with unrelenting heat!
Over...
Data
Sunlight yellow, sunlight yellow
Overdrive!!
Kisamara's life too
The ripple of the sun! Dio!
This is the power
that will defeat you!
Dio Brando?
上書
Let me say this to the Stone
Mask that awakened your brain:
Don’t get carried away!
Perhaps you can heal this
wound in my stomach, JoJo.
You’re the one who put it there!
Then I’ll be completely healed from
the damage you dealt me in that fire.
I’ll be using your lives...
To purge this wound!
You bastard!
Just how many lives did you
extinguish to heal that wound?
Severe living activity is born
Do you remember how many slices of
bread you’ve eaten in your lifetime?
Won't open
I’ll make you submit!
By the ripple of the sun!
Utterly pathetic!
Pow!
It’s freezing?!
Hmm
I am able to control my own body at will.
If I freeze up all of your veins,
Then you won’t be able to use that power!
I can’t—I can’t catch my breath!
Mr. Zeppeli!
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
soon
Breathing techniques? Ripple?
If you’re going to be
blowing all this hot air,
You ought to use it to
play me a little fanfare!
Looks like your companions
are just as weak as you.
Grz
JOJO: What did you say?
DIO: Companions...
That’s right. Do you remember?
The story of the knights
your father told us that day?
The tragic queen who was sentenced
to beheading by Elizabeth the First,
a?
After a failed assassination
plot in the 1600s...
But
Mary Stuart!
It was about the ones who served her!
Father told us...
Which has been passed down for
generations in our great England.
Long ago, 300 years before today
Two queens battled for the throne
And the other, the beautiful Mary Stuart
Offering up their swords to serve Mary
Tarkus’s strength cleaved
through rocks like butter
品積品積!
Bruford, with his skill and spirit,
cut down foes like a phantom
Without any family, the
two honed their powers
They swore their loyalty to her
Of murdering her husband,
and she was captured.
In order to stop those two heroes,
Elizabeth made an appeal:
“And I will spare your master’s life!”
“You two, surrender at once!”
This, we cannot refuse
But in the moment they
were to be executed—
For our queen is our life!
Your master isn’t being held in the tower.
I cut off her head myself just yesterday!
Look at her lying over
there like a piece of rubbish!
Dad's
Now
Look at her lying over
there like a piece of rubbish!
After all, if she was left alive,
we’d risk a rebellion!
You’ve betrayed us, Elizabeth
We curse you with our grudge!
We curse you for all eternity!
Bruford, filled with regret,
ensnared them with his hair
As though it were alive!
Bruford, filled with regret,
ensnared them with his hair
And that is the story,
Of those knights who lived
according to their hearts
Until the very end!
Oh, what loyal hearts!
In the end, they couldn’t do
anything from down in the mud.
There is nothing that is without meaning.
The same can be said about the
fact that you came here to this house.
Everything is connected!
I want to believe that they
kept on looking at the stars!
All people live in a prison called fate
Reaching out through those bars,
Do they see the stars? Or the mud?
Either one—
Could be said to be correct!
I turned those two
Even history bends before me!
It can’t be!
I'll scoop up the maid
Such grotesque forms!
It’s the perfect form for
taking their revenge!
Don’t you think so?
Wow
Play me a fanfare with their screams!
Our pride!
And you, Tarkus!
The way you feel—
Your pride, your resentment.
I can’t even imagine it!
But I also bear my own burdens!
I’m gonna be the one to eat ‘em!
Would like to be the one to bring
an end to this brave man’s life!
Alright, go ahead!
We’ll duel as knights!
Run away, you two!
Mr. Joestar!
I won’t let you interfere!
I want to believe
People are like destiny
A wedge driven into the
wasteland of my memory
At dawn, a blood-red sun
rose over the Atlantic Ocean
Gradually
Don’t come any closer!
There’s nothing I can do,
I’m a mere spectator
Come on, get real,
even at a time like this?
Even if I give up, the pain
will just be for another day
And tomorrow, yes tomorrow,
Honourable knight,
Is that what you take pride in?
Now’s the time, to let
courage resonate in my heart
I’m not scared of pain
I must find the strength to stand up
Tomorrow is right now!
Old man!
Melt!
I didn’t follow you to
become a hindrance!
And look the enemy in the eyes
Won’t wait for a distant tomorrow
Find the strength to
get back on my feet
Tomorrow is now!
Find the strength to
get back on my feet
Tomorrow is now!
Please... This knight’s proud heart,
Let it somehow be restored!
I am the Dark Knight Bruford!
This pain means nothing to me!
Osa
Why aren’t you moving?
Just now,
You said “pain”.
That means that now,
You can feel pain!
Pain?
Don't mess with me
Even at a time like this
That’s why...
Come
I stopped fighting you.
That’s why you stopped your sword.
Remember
You are a great knight.
You are human!
Pain...
Is proof of life!
So this is what it means to be human?
already
Because of this pain, I can also feel
the joy of being alive in this moment.
regain
Because of this pain, I can also feel
the joy of being alive in this moment.
Tomorrow
Now
I feel a bizarre sense of peace now.
When
Bruford...
Luck!
And also...
Pluck!
Don't wait for tomorrow
To think, I had to kill him
in order to save his soul...
JoJo!
girl
I can’t believe you actually
defeated the Dark Knight!
Just as I thought...
I, Dio, will—
Hey baby!
Your ripple is more vulgar than frog piss!
Watch out, Mr. Joestar!
pain
What an embarrassment of a knight!
He never got his revenge!
What did he have to be joyful about!
What I saw
Sennorakashi
How could you!
For victory!
I’ll get you!
I’ll get you for this!
JoJo!
My... dying wish is...
That you take my ripple
and continue on, JoJo!
Let's go
He collapsed.
Come
Affection
I’ll vanquish your wicked soul!
Drown in the murk of history, Tarkus!
To think he would defeat Kurokiko
Old man!
The Stone Mask must be destroyed!
I lived my own life to the fullest.
In the end,
You are my hope.
At the beginning of the season
Once again, life is
spilling out of my arms
Loss of motivation and enthusiasm
驚
You taught me that humanity’s
greatest gift is courage
From now on
The light you’ve given
to me will shine through
Into my spirit
JoJo
From here on...
Everything is connected
JoJo!
Wow
always
Even this pain
My father left to me
what you leave to me now
The golden light that
shines from within me
It’s the one thing in my heart
that I can hold on to now
I see the stars
The way to you...
Light up the way to you...
The light that was received would seep in. In my heart, I felt as if I was both dead and breathing at the same time.
From now on, I'm coming into you. Thank you very much.
I can’t hear you
You and I are different
You’re not so changed,
you did it to survive
I’ll use any means
DARIO: What will you want next?
What do I want?
I want...
So you’ve come...
The world you wished for?
What?
I’ve dominated death, and even history too.
You’re just afraid.
Of being human...
That’s why you rejected your humanity.
I’ve transcended humanity!
You ran away from it.
It's my fault.
That changed until
The ends justify the means.
I will win,
All of this is fate!
This is just how you
chose to live your life!
What will your legacy be?
Such righteousness!
And then died!
Just like...
Your father.
That’s right.
what,
Now I, Jonathan Joestar...
For the sake of revenge...
I will kill you!
No! I’ve come to right your wrongs!
I’ve accepted this as my legacy!
Ironic, isn’t it? Now
you’re the have-not, JoJo!
Become my next meal!
I’ve lost so many loved ones but
their light lives on in me, Dio!
I’ve come to cleanse
your corrupted ambitions
I obtained this power
If you think about it, you’re just like me
You were just like me,
two sides of the same coin
Like fire and ice, my body is burning
JOJO: I’ll kill you
DIO: You’ll kill me
But
JOJO: You’ll kill me
DIO: I’ll kill you
You did it! You defeated Dio!
Not a chance!
Utterly pathetic!
Give me strength
dead
With this, you’ll become
one of my undead servants
Just as I thought, you were
running away from humanity
My fist... Just from hitting him!
I transcended humanity!
None of you are on my level.
JOJO: No, for as long as I have faith,
DIO: Compared to me, Dio!
As long as we have faith, we can grow
JOJO: That’s what he taught me
DIO: You can’t reach me!
DIO: I’ll chip away at this body to prove it
JOJO: I’ll burn up this body to prove it
He put his hand in the
fire! If he does that—
Like fire and ice
My lost friends, my father’s spirit
With my life on the
line, I’ll prove it now!
for that
pain
“I was only trying to be friendly!”
“I think my finger went in his eye.”
I won’t stop beating you
until you’re finished!
The heat is coursing through me!
This is impossible!
I can’t be...
Watch out! He’s shooting
hot liquid out of his eyes!
緊弱緊弱
Lord Dio...!
It's so tense, but it's actually deceiving you
Dio...!
Now you too will come to me, and death will resonate with you
You ran away from humans
Extra, extra! Read all about it!
(In 1888 on December the 4th)
(The London Press reported)
There was a small incident
(That little village, there was
a missing persons incident)
In just one night,
they abruptly disappeared
Moaning could be heard from underground
That the following day, below a cliff
Men were seen burning clothing
It seemed to be a stone mask
(In 1889 on February the 2nd)
(In the announcements section)
(The Joestar heir)
(Jonathan Joestar, of Liverpool, was wed)
Yagaragaragara
(To the Pendletons’
daughter, Erina Pendleton)
In a small notice, they announced:
The honeymoon would be a trip
to the United States by steamer
(Now, on to other news...)
I’ll always be there for you!
Happy honeymoon!
I can’t wait to hear all about it!
And try to dig up some oil for myself!
Damn it...
But after this, a fateful
moment was soon to come...
This story will be passed down
until the world has come full circle.
That will be the life’s work
of Speedwagon the meddler...
But, the one to tell you what
happens right now won’t be me...
Yo
Let my hand always be in yours
What’s wrong?
When you’re next to me...
I feel the same.
I’m happy!
Well, let’s go and eat!
713 people
Jonathan?
That’s...
Erina,
Don’t forget to lock the door!
The day after the incident
Running under
Men burning down the district
and
It was repeated so much
I have lured him here.
Have you come?
Dio...
JoJo...
I dare show myself in this pitiful
state in front of you for a reason...
I used to despise you so much,
But now I respect you...
That’s because I’ve realised something!
If there is a God that controls fate,
Then there’s never been a relationship
orchestrated as perfectly as ours...
push up
You’re the reason I got this power,
And you’re the reason why...
The world has slipped from my grasp!
When will it...
That’s exactly what our destiny is!
I’ll obtain the body of the one and
only person I respect in this world.
And live in eternal glory!
Are one and the same in this world!
Please look!
And restart it all
I can’t speak—can’t breathe—
Erina! Not you too!
This is the start of his mythos!
This ark is swarming with his followers!
Please, spare the child!
Shall we torture him to death?!
Wang Chan!
I won’t tolerate any insults!
My friend, Jonathan Joestar—
Your blood will become my future!
I’ll tie our futures together
JoJo
With my final ripple!
JoJo!
Because I realized that
I felt it tear. Something
important inside me just tore
ERINA: How could this be?!
JOJO: Get out of here!
I won’t, JoJo...
I will burn with you
Until everything turns to ash
JoJo
Everything is connected
There’s a meaning to it all!
The one to spin the thread of fate
(Light and darkness flicker and flash)
I’m still alive!
In the end, I, Dio, will triumph!
(Light and darkness flicker and flash)
My mythos begins here
JoJo!
If you do that
I know what you’re like...
I figured...
You would strike...
Before I...
All people
Lost consciousness.
That neck
JoJo?
Inaccuracy
Let me go, JoJo!
You
He’s...
My
Dead...
This child
Someone
all
Dose
Something inside me snapped, something decisive
That proud life of his
Vanished into the dusts of time
His golden spirit
(Phantom Blood)
All live
Like two who make one,
Isn’t that right, Dio?
Hey, JoJo
Keep looking at the stars
Guided by this hapless fate
We’ll reach out to the stars
Our two fates
Speak
Have become one
Is born anew
I’ll live
(Living in the shadow of history)
(Even when the world resets)
(This bizarre adventure)
(Our golden spirit will shine)
Dead
Speedwagon coolly withdraws.
Of course,
Something in my eyes
Two in One
Feeling the friendship of a dog
That's right
Without you
Because you were there
something
Now I
want
Find
To your favorite destiny
Beautiful Mikade
In the stars
I drink
The two
That fate
It was terrible
Another breast
Quietly unknown
One saw the stars
Tour
Is it polar?
pick up the station
my frightenedzz
Speedwagon is so cool!
Yuishie, Yoishie!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Thank you for coming
to today’s performance.
The musical will close tomorrow, though.
And foremost, the people
who came every day—
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Nah, it’s probably okay.
Back in February, right?
Opening night was delayed.
Isn’t it seriously amazing that
he did this role without a double?
You were just that wonderful.
Thank you everyone in the cast!
Thank you from the bottom of my heart!
Yeah, I’ll watch too.
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
The best thing about this park was that the smiles of all the customers were the biggest smiles. I felt that very strongly at the park.
I was truly happy that such a miraculous park had been able to survive to the very end.
Thank you for watching.
Now, Mr. Kong, please.
Great staff, great cast.
Then they brought the outbreak to the theater.
I'm glad to meet everyone who has watched the video.
I easily overcame the progression.
The players were able to go home after today's academy.
I'm happy for people.
I let it happen.
thank you.
And I was struggling as a single person.
My son!
That's amazing!
I'm so happy!
It's great.
thank you.
Then, I received the greeting I just mentioned.
Thank you for watching.
thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Everyone, please check out Fauci's Prround Funding.
thank you.
[INAUDIBLE]
MAMORU: It’s already over.
Thank you! Thank you!
Shotaro, do your best tomorrow!
MAMORU: Do your best!
MAMORU: Thanks!
So Misha, please.
yes.
It was a huge hurdle.
I'm not sure if I can speak well,
This is Elina Tendul and her character Shimis Misha.
Thank you very much for coming to the audience today.
Brought to you by Ossan Subs
Proofreading
Bug, FlanPucci, Jama Kitten, Kitkuni,
Mayo, Ne0ntetra, S_Mage, and Twincam
Transcription & Translation
Bug, FlanPucci, Jama Kitten,
Kitkuni, S_Mage, and Twincam
Subtitling
S_Mage and Jama Kitten
Special thanks to our wonderful
Japanese friends who helped us along the way!
Please do, everyone.
Please look at the stars, everyone.
So please have a great war.
yes.
It's your job to burn the speeder!
It was my first experience and it was really difficult for me.
But really.
It was really hard, but
Already, somehow,
To get support,
Thanks,
It was really hard, but
Already, somehow,
To get support,
Like supporting them,
Supporting each other,
Those words truly mean,
It just seemed to enter my body.
It's a really wonderful place,
Thanks to that,
I was able to cut it thickly.
So, I have nothing but the best to say,
With everyone here on stage,
As Kochi-san also said,
Not at all.
Although he's not here now,
The staff who helped me create it,
and,
This role,
For five months,
I really put it together,
I want to make it a treasure in my life.
Love women,
Thank you for taking an interest in Speedwagon again.
Including everyone who loves me,
Really,
thank you very much!
Shirae-san...
Good job, Dig putting is burning well.
I certainly understand.
Honchitsu,
To Sepulija,
RPM improved office
Wang's school committee came to the event.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you very much.
Really,
The first thought is,
There were a lot of different things that happened.
The two of them, Shotaro, and now, here
The one who finished the tree, and another Teperi,
Hiro-kun and I accomplished so much on our own.
Mom, this company is a one-lens camera for people.
With the determination to align
I came here with the aim of becoming a teacher of Wang's music.
Really, without anyone calling
Of course, I'm really grateful that I've come this far.
Medical support from staff
It is the result of your efforts.
Every single stage, really
I just want to omit it.
The applause of the Baraline and 5000 yen are us
Now the cast is
The truth is, it's your Hamon energy.
How much courage it gave us
I think that's what we really feel.
I was really close to Hantoshi and Okabetsu right now.
It really is like a family
It means that today will be a valley from tomorrow onwards.
Hey hey
Annie
A little Syriaria please
Just a little bit
I feel lonely though
I really love myself
This woman's world
And with these beloved members
In this theater
Being able to breathe the same air
That's right.
The one who touched everyone's hearts was
I have become a treasure too
I am proud to have been able to do this with you all.
Thank you so much everyone
thank you
It will end again
Blatzer
Please watch
I changed my boss's environment.
Another ironworker
Thank you for today
It's totally free
So many
As you have written earlier,
Right from here on
As in the title above
It was a strange adventure.
There are so many people like you.
Only the curtain of Hara
Born at the Imperial Theatre
The Imperial Theatre
The current theater is closing.
As a final review
By producing
Not Minami
Memories
Participated
My friends are cast members here.
It is staff
And the original author
The main cast members
And here are the books.
After five years of work
Apparently it was rewritten 17 times.
It was in this flow that I was born.
This work
Being accepted by everyone like this
Like this
Many musicals
We have some works from overseas.
Such works are
Zahiozic Zero is
On Broadway and in the West End
That's what we're here for
In books
While making large replicas
Let's fight
Japanese style
We provide information.
This work is
What you all saw
Exactly
From zero to one
Became Zahiozic
I think it's a work of art.
This work
Someday again
Inherited
It may be a big performance,
This Zahiozik
I was at Zero 1
The friends here
Really I
It's just for the time being.
Zayn
I feel like a son or daughter to you.
Only one person was different
Since they share the same father
One as a father
Mud and Stars
University
A work ticket
As a friend
from now on
At the Shibutoku Musical
I want to survive
Truly amazing
Two sons
Like this
I can have it
A little bit today
You might be watching from anywhere
Also serving
As a son
Nice to meet you
Truly amazing
Yesterday
As a father
I was able to participate
Hello everyone
If you have any worries
Finally
What is it?
Within myself
It's all connected
That it all has meaning
a little bit
If you think so
surely
Beyond that
There is light
There are stars
If you think so
I think it's that kind of work.
thank you
Well then
I will do my best
Where should I start?
Already
But anyway
I'm glad we met
Hotz
We
Entertainment and
I'm trying not to
Sometimes after all
There are times when it's difficult
There are times when it's scary
but
The Minister just said
As you said
Something
In the purely literal sense
Don't do it right away
In the truest sense
Do it now
That's what it means
I am this
I felt it at Campari.
of course
A lot of things happened
Something like that
Only in those words
I might not be able to tell you right now, but
And more
I
now
As a treasure
I was able to have
Above all
It
so
lots of
To humans
That you can enjoy it
After all, it's ours
It's the happiest thing
It
With this member
It can be closed on paper
I am happy
Women
Giant player fun
I welcomed
My father just now
As you said
We will continue to do so
Look forward
Surely soon
Each on their own path
Various expressions
I think I'll pursue it
Not yet
It will be useful
Dad too
Let's definitely meet again
and
Also this woman
I think it would be a good story if we could meet.
It's all connected
I dream of such a day
Today is really
To everyone
I want to express my gratitude
everyone
thank you
amazing
I'll say something good.
I think Bappy will decide.
thank you
Woman
I pushed the woman down.
This is Arisa Shotaro
everyone
Really
Those who noticed
I don't know, but
I
Because I'm this kind of person
Even if I stand in the middle
After all, everyone
Many people
For holding me and supporting me
already
Warm
Someone like my older brother
He was already a family man
People like
Because that's fine for you
You can go with that humanity
Just those words are enough
I really have come this far
But still
When I look around,
After all, this time everyone
After all
Cress
I've seen your face after all
Really everyone
too
After all, the curtain won't open
There were many things that caused me anxiety.
I think there is.
That voice also reached me
It arrived directly after all
However, I also received a lot of criticism from the people around me.
What's going on?
Ride and enjoy
There are various messages
I saw the power of seeing.
just
I
I really believe in everyone
I'm working hard here
Because I've been watching everyone
Watch it.
Feelings
I just want you to wear it
That's really the only feeling
Not
Together
There are so many different
Overcoming a big wall
already
Even if the conversation doesn't change
Invisible
It's a bond
That's already the case
Don don don don
That means we're connected
I've been feeling this trend for a long time now
After all
Makuha is open
Jonah Joshi's
What is the other Yuya-san?
Really
We've talked about a lot of things up until today
Yesterday's Yuya's war loss
Watching Hiro's wartime success
After all,
There was today
One more
I feel like I've really completed it.
I got into the mood.
I've seen some really amazing things
on second thoughts
I'm glad I worked hard
Really already
As of yesterday, I felt
So today, everyone
so
I can see that face in Chi-up
Really I
With a heartfelt joy
There are lots
As it was at the beginning
I
I think it's a historic evolution.
To the world
Really already
We all worked hard to create it
already
This guy
This guy gave it to me in the field.
Together
I want to keep up
already
try as hard as one can
Climb, climb, climb, climb up the mountain
today
Really
I think I was able to make everyone happy.
Thank you so much
Me too
Really
I spoke without thinking
Maybe
no
That's not true
Some people may think that
This is definitely
already
It's my feelings
Campari's feelings
I
today
It may be a mistake
I think I've made everyone happy already.
It's okay to think that
Me too
where
Everyone did their best.
everyone
thank you
I
To dry this
Also
I hope that I will be able to meet you all in person soon. I also hope that this work will continue to remain not only in Japan, but all over the world.
I want to teach with big dreams.
Thank you very much.
So, I hope to finish it again soon, and thank you for watching today.
Thank you for watching.
Everyone, everyone and a little bit of everyone.
Because there are a lot of things going on.
Thank you everyone!
Thank you for watching.
Artwork
Gabies
。
I love you