hard
This is also on screen and can be spoken about.
It's okay. It's okay.
You are watching this.
Yes, you guys.
You have been chosen.
I decided it was trustworthy.
I leave this record to those who will carry on my legacy.
Now I'm heading to the ruins in Mexico.
Time that had stopped for 49 years has begun to move again.
That's why now.
This record must be kept.
If something happens to my eyes in the future.
No, let's get back to the topic.
As you all know,
This Foundation is a sub-structure of humanity,
Medicine, government studies, high school studies, etc.
It was established with the aim of bringing women into various fields.
What's your mood?
Yes, that's the impression.
Please listen carefully.
I founded this foundation here in the United States.
All the things that steal Shiv from the world,
It is like discovering the secret of something.
That thing is a stone screen.
The mood is,
The Foundation's purpose in death,
That is to do the secret of the stone screen.
And today, I am recording this.
A story awaits behind the mask,
And there it was,
The story of the spirit of radish,
This is so that they can follow the lead.
It all started with the 16th generation.
A part of the central park of the purpose formula.
For tiles that can hear the voice of time,
About once in Afteka.
Dear Osamu,
Blessed man,
The power of life,
The insects are afraid,
Appearance.
When will it be time to breathe history?
The spirit dances with power
We are sunlight and sweat
I sweat twice as much in the sun
Widespread
But at one point, the department was replaced by Kotzentos.
All of that and more are in the Stone Mask.
This story awaits in the Stone Mask
The two are the boy's favorite fateful adventure
To do this, first
1868 Years Old Ronto's son
Watcher!
It's Ikeame
I won't leave again
I have to apologize for doing it
I'll finish you up, Ikeri
Today is
I'm sleepy
I don't understand the sun
Who is it?
Isn't it the birther who is the self?
Everyone's still gathered
It's coming
The first person will go
wait a minute
Okay tease
hang on
Hurry, hurry
Wooooooooooooo!
That's more than that
I'm sorry for not being friendly with you
What are you talking about?
It's a rich man, it's a fast one, so I'm going to look for him.
Wow, that was fast.
It's a beautiful necklace. Thank you.
Oh, it's in this box. It's the next best thing.
What is this? It's your bad wall. I don't need this.
Come on, come on, my head is still alive
I don't want to get into that kind of trouble, I'll find something valuable.
The valuables are gone, Yuriya and I are scared
It's a hole in the hand of a certain person's house. It's a hole in the hand of a certain person's house.
Look, find it
Just one night
No thanks
Brother, do you believe me? What were you doing?
I won't see you
Passion
Oge
Did you buy it?
People who like hot weather have it.
He was trying to calm me down.
What about Red?
Morning
I helped
Is this also a dream?
Race saved my life
My name is
Used
This treasure must never be attacked.
Naroruhodoromonchya, no offense, but Brand!
Ah, Dario, beat Brando!
Time passed, and in 1880
The time was filled with enthusiasm
Let's talk, it's terrible
I'm getting on well
People were dreaming
Now is a great time to go to college
Take him in your hands
People were reaching out
The park I went back to the other day with a super stick
I don't watch it, but it's out of date
When will ordinary darkness come, I'm waiting
That voice, even
A suspicious voice
Come on, find out who I am
Press the middle button and listen carefully
Let me explain
Kupy's Wamoerea
This More Gutary
O'Cataly
Why does Tsugumono
While leaving it to high school students
I'd like to tell you guys too.
To the people, to this country, to Basa, to this era
This will also tell you what is happening
Now in this country, Basa, in this era
Let me teach you more about Pee's
Now, let's finish with the second pass.
Don't be thrown off
Hakumeyuno
This is so nostalgic
Color is important
Oath hai ga ga
Dinosaur Light Song
Sugar block
I was born now
The
Heaven's deadline
Skill Reference
Love, if you will
Failure
izz If you want to start
This is my place, just mix it up
, properly 'me' no more
and there is no
It was a nightmare, but it didn't work
The reporter is a big fan.
Untied umenoita
My friend's bouquet
what is it
How do you feel?
merged e me
Congratulations!
Behind me,
I'm in a car rush
yeah
oh!
hang on!
Killing him!
Hey!
Makusuki!
It's crazy!
Makusu!
ah!
oh!
What should we do?
I'm not going!
I'm really going to do it!
Go!
nice!
Let's do it!
This idiot
oh!
At this level, the arrow of life is returned!
I can't breathe after I collapsed!
White mountain.
Yours is the best
I don't want that to happen!
Masseuse in the front
It would have been better if they had sold it.
Oh no!
I can't hear you!
What's wrong?
a
Medicine
The medicine is now
I have something important to tell you. Are you here?
Oh no
I've been here for a long time now
I know
Hey
Since I disappeared as a new
All I care about is you
Ah, so that's it.
Oh, I'm getting this
Oh, dear dear dear dear
Ah, the good one
It's a rule
Moreover, it's a human
That's what I have ongar
Okay?
When I die, send him that letter. Go to him.
Go to that guy
He’ll take care of you, you can
go to school. Sounds good, don’t it?
It's a surprise to the school
That's nice
It can be stuck even if you cut it properly.
investigation
Now, the father is being rude
Okay, Dio
You have good balls
Seriously to no one
Become the richest
Dio
Father and grandparents
Ask yourself
Stolen
Keep going
That's right
Unbeatable
I feel nauseous
It's hell now
Hakie wo Moyoko
Even so, it was my mother's translation
Let go of your pride
He hugged me
Nedio
“Hey Dio, look up at the stars”
My mother kept saying that
It was terrible and he died.
openly
Why don't you have anything in your hands?
Not only will it be stolen
What a star
Do you have it?
Is that sky blue?
It happened
Blowing in my ears
The worst father
Not losing has always been losing
Under this cloudy sky
I was already running and dying
Let's receive Issan now
Use all
I think it's a crossover
I may have nothing in my hands yet,
Let's start there
It happened
You have it
Boredom in that sky
That's it.
Usually
Just a Star
Come on, I already have some good ones
Come on, I heard your family trades in medicine for your wife.
My father is a proper doctor.
I don't know. But the high stars.
Oh, stop, your mother gave that to you on a single sheet too.
Do it!
What are you doing?! Take this!
Oh, do it!
Don't act all high and mighty just because you're in front of my house.
Hey, is anyone doing this?
It's Jouster Keljouna.
More copy and copy parts under the eyes.
After all, this is Jouna from Jousterkel!
It's Kanemochiki Day for both of us!
what?
Dear breakfast!
Um, are you okay?
Leave me alone.
It was something I wanted to do.
I didn't do it to be thanked by you.
I'm aiming for true passion.
You were a girl and it was a problem.
So I just stood up.
Someday you'll be able to win.
Okay, let's go!
Ah, wait a minute!
Jona-san Jowstar.
Okay, let's go!
Hey, Dani!
You...
You're Diopransola!
That's you, Jona-san Jouster.
Everyone calls her Chocho.
Looking forward to working with you.
This is my friend Danny.
Let's go.
It's okay because it won't sag or fall off.
friend?
Danny!
What are you doing?
Gyul-san!
I've been waiting for you, Diopland.
Enter Jowstar today.
This is the haven where you will live from today onwards.
What's wrong, Jojo?
You must be tired from London, Dio.
From today you are our family.
Maybe you could live your life like Jojo.
Jowstar, thank you for your service today.
BLADDOG!
It's the Cape Archer!
police?
Is something wrong?
The Jowstar movement is a long-standing friendship.
I heard Danny cry just now.
That was sudden!
The surprising display hit my leg.
Danny is an excellent selling point for the Jowstar line.
He's quite friendly, but it was great that he surprised you.
JoJo, I'm already happy with Danny.
Jojo also lost his mother.
It's a year like that.
Please get along well with each other.
Now, let me show you to your room.
BLADDOG!
JoJo!
See you, JoJo!
So, this is my Geass game!
Don't touch my bag.
I'm driving.
Well, your hands are sticky like a dog's.
Sorry, but I don't want you to touch it.
Listen, JoJo.
First up is Number One, my favorite.
No matter who it is, I won't let anyone act arrogantly in front of me.
I just try to be friendly.
What are you both doing?
One more thing.
I hate dogs.
They are trying to curry favor with humanity and ignore their enemies.
Don't let that Ahoina get close to me.
I'll get to work on the jaw now.
Thus, the two proofs met and the two players began.
Hitaka Jojo.
Dioc.
Okay?
I aye raa
A little dancing,
Still no good, get it on your hands.
Why is it just one day?
To prevent us from connecting with each other
Wait and see next time
No matter what, I want to do it to you
Being reborn and illuminating
Please, head to the waiting room.
How many times has this happened?
This is the sixth time
All of the answers are correct.
Because I liked reading books
This much
It's still not easy to play,
Ikane
We are
Here as a high memory
real
Check it out
That's not enough
Pesh thing
I almost believe
Don't do horsetail
Nothing is always
Without passing by the beauty
Wait and see next time
Whatever happens
To be loved
Really high
Azukasa
a little bit
nevertheless
Do you believe it?
Look at it
I'll tell you
Perfect supporter
Shockley, too.
Aventine
That's it
Riwo
I don't see it
I
Embarrassing
You
I was spoiled
Such
My mother gave it to me.
always
Correct the festival
Ikane
We are
Were you born?
As a memory
Philosophy
However,
The exit
Always in mind
This is transmitted to England
There are two models
One day
Their master
By the enemy
Captive
It became
The enemy is
Huge power
have
The two models
fear
I put forward the conditions
Instead
You guys
Once menarche occurs
At one time
Life is
To try to guarantee
where
To the two of them
It's a problem
yes
To save my master
Offer yourself
Captive
It became
The stars?
Corridor
Railway City
First
What I'm looking at
In front of me
Will it be a draw?
Or
On the diagram
Shine
want
I wonder
Which one?
think
I wanted
Draw?
I
Draw
I was watching
I think
Why
I think so
in the end
They have
For the Lord
Death unexpectedly
There is no choice
If I die,
There's nothing to be done
you can't
that's why
no matter how
Even if you put down the work
Alive
Something
Nasaneba and
I thought
I
I was looking at the stars
I think
They lost their lives
Two people
It's a kiss
In history
It will be engraved
So
How did you live?
How it happened
Cherish it
in the end
They
Himself
Nothing in hand
Not included
the
解鋼
Helplessness
They
What I saw
It's a draw
They
Teaching
Alive
What
this
He was proud
I was looking at the stars
That's how we should live
He is teaching me
Thank you
you
It's a rule
It's a thing
Take it away
I'm alive
If so
To fulfill that responsibility
Alive
What to do
Shouldn't you think about it?
I
Both of them
That far
At this time
There is no right answer
Is that okay?
People
A country of eyes and colors
live
So
Reach out
What you can see is
Do you want
Or
Which one
Both
To the correct answer
Lyrics
Don't you want to drive?
It's spose
moreover
I came with you
Eskikar
Hive Zekiar
a lot
It's the voice.
Today is exactly
Shukyo
If you lose
yes
Basso
Everyone
That far
The Winner is
That's how we deal with each other
Who
Decide who is the king
Return
The conch sounds
Today's Challenge
So
Come out
What do you think?
Let's do it!
If Gru sees Bastiv on the screen, he's defeated!
With this rail, it keeps coming out!
It's Hong!
It's Feeket!
Yay!
Nodknocky!
I've never seen that before!
It's a washer!
Ah...
thing!
Y-y-y-take ra!
Feeket!?
Hey, how are you?
D ص PAR!
Ichikowa
Everyone! Everyone!
My finger seems to have landed in his eye.
It was a foul on my part.
It's all about sharing ideas, it's boring!
Wow, that was amazing! I'm going to do that move!
So why don't you stop!
Hubber, everyone!
For some reason, Dio is trying to get me to fall for him.
I feel like I'm being trusted more and more
I want to see your heart when you sleep
I'm full of anxiety
If I continue to trust you like this
Will everyone cry?
You are always warm
Thank you for being by my side
If I had a mother, would it be like this?
Is this how you loved me?
You were in trouble
My half
Hey, what's the flower pressure?
I'll be here in the morning too
If you'd like, come too.
Are you curious?
Sorry for touching you without permission.
I don't care
The stone screen was apparently excavated from Mekishiko Stone.
Mekishiko
When girls were just born
I bought it at the London Art Museum.
On the way back, I had an accident at the location.
It was when your father helped me.
Are you interested?
Aie, nothing in particular
that
The girls always go out with Danny.
Danny's attitude towards women
There's friendship and trust
Friendship Is it a dog?
Danny was a young girl
I won it.
At first I was still scared of unfamiliar places and people.
It didn't go well with either girl.
But one day
A woman once woke up in the river
My voice is all alone and no one can hear it
Just as I die
The way he listened to the princess was one thing.
Danny jumped into the river.
Danny jumps into the river
I saved a girl's life.
I know what life is
Danny's spirited actions
A young woman
Danny's feelings
I was moved
Since then they
That's why I have great confidence in him.
is that so
Dangaso too
ah
it was
Believe
Butterfly
The two resumed
love
That wonderful effect
I took a few actions.
The two who are waiting to win
I was in love
Danny
Be well behaved
You eat in separate scenes
What are you digging up from the top of your sister's neck?
no
Nothing
Why hide it?
If you say so, I really want to see it
You'll laugh
I won't laugh
I'll tell someone
I won't laugh, so show me
No.
butterfly
Elina
Just call
Feelings
Relax
What kind of music
The sound
I'm falling in love
What's going well
already
Laugh like that
Morning or quite
Bab
The sky gets higher
Elina
butterfly
The happiness of being there
The clouds are heartfelt
The wind is a little sweet
butterfly
Elina
I'm short of words
This one
Overflowing
forever
One word
I'm happy
I want to hear
With your voice
Here
tickles
you
People who can't hear
I don't know
I'm being asked by you
Put on Jariun
The reason for the two of us
Hands and
My hands
Touching
be confused
Towards tomorrow
To be continued
This little courage
Trembling
Red ringing
surely
compete
Hawatsu
Preconceived notions
It's already this late
Because a customer is coming today
I have to hurry back
Elina
see you tomorrow
Huh, okay?
Huh
compete
Suyoku
you
That name is
Isn't that right?
here we go
Ugh
It's Erina Pendleton.
Today is
With my superior
They were just playing
that
something
wall
Ugh
Udo Yaa
here we go
Cling
today
What can't be done on broken ground
Do a transformation and get out
I can see it locked there
Wait, have you kissed me yet?
Not yet
My first partner is not Chojo
This is Dio
If it's ratey, what does that mean?
You understand, right?
This guy!
This woman!
Are you saying soroagaarau on purpose?
Wow!
What's going on?
Why are you giving me alcohol?
Who is responsible for Peter's food shortage?
Namaruka
yes
Because I can't win now
Why would you bother to say that?
What's the big sale?
Kanaki Koiyori
Please give me an illustration that doesn't look like a kaza.
It's no good if you eat well
I've been seen before, I'm a useless man
Izawa Hiamatress
宙zech
You go buy some alcohol
Already money
Eni
The alcoholic beverages have arrived.
So the name is scary and I guess
at least
Eat money to buy medicine
Your mouth is big
How long will I remain?
I thought he was shy, but
Magara
Crack
Well, my breasts are always twisted and swaying.
I noticed it too early and stepped on it
Yes, it's Joes.
If you see a hand
Follow
I am
With you
Haa
Why is this happening today?
Hurt her
Haa
I want to go
What did you do?
Why?
Oh
Haa
You are amazing
Much more than me
I respect that.
Only in my heart
One thing is for sure
There is something burning
Oh no
Haa
Many people's names
Easy to wear
A small person
I heard that
My love
you
Kyusana
I'm the one
I don't care
nine
Haa
Stand up to it
No shoulders
this
I can't lose
Oh
Emotions
Dominate
Not like him
Slippery Heart
Her name
Get it back
Oh no
Generation rate
Battle
I'll make you understand
Oh no
Haa
you
I miss you
Get to know
That's a good impression.
Haa
This heart
You
Give it to me
Only
Oh no
You
Until Naku
like this
Lost
Don't bend
Haa
often
too
To me
Bukase
surely
Konoha
Better
Like this
Like winning
Cheap
This me
this
Looks good on you
Like this
Like winning
Cheap
This me
This suits you
Haa
One
What's going on?
Both of them
Give a penalty
Go back to your room
Haa
Let's go, we'll make friends over there too.
He looked down on women.
His explosive power
I need to develop that mental strength even more.
So that I can hold my head high in faith
I need to calm down and control my mind more.
To get it all
But
What's that sound?
Is there anyone in honesty?
Are you going to try to go outside?
Oh my god
Someone please
Hmm
Then Pan Seventies
First place
Bistriest
Ride behind
Aprekaeru Korori
What about artificial?
Timekeeper Piakorak is a building star
No one can stop us
Cake Rosie in the Flow
Melting Up Ten
Listening to British culture
Chaochao
Wartwack Osaka
Top Runner
Cattrell Dawser
Rowan peas on index finger
I'm sleeping
Port Levy
A bright and cheerful team
Same as the current situation in Maldea
Focusing on the darkness
It feels like it's shaking
That's Portobello
Port's own market
Is that correct?
Stone Turtle
Excavated in Mexico
I think it was Mexico
It's been a long time
It was a while ago.
You made it clear
But there's no doubt about it
The wife of the late Soroshinshi
I hate it
I got it back after a good run.
Okay
I did it
I bought it
in
Where is Soroshinshi now?
It seems a bit suspicious
Generally you
What is it?
This is a gracious
My name is
Seteri
It's a downshake
By the stone turtle
I'm from Italy
All the way from Italy
Northern rules
Like I said
I'll do some research
Please wait
April
Ha
I'll give you a little China.
Will the sun soon set?
You'd better not go beyond that street.
Kiri appeared
The sun stops
Until then
When I'm in town
topknot
Please drink it
I don't know you
Kiritomo Sky
Not yet
chase
Second-rate
Reach out your hand
Voices around
I don't want to fall
Laughter and no laughter
Mix it up
Drinking stops
Thrown away in the dump
Better
Talking about Autumn
Legs
This darkness
Worth going
Something's wrong
I'm sure it's because I'm dry
Until then
surely
Itchy
give
Kisakisa
Seriously awesome
Hated and scorned
Hateful Agebokoe
Right now
Immediately
Magical
That's it
Inagein
Ageing
Save Trafalda Stare
I can hear
Iodine
Shoot
Canelo
From the high party
The rich
My eyes still smile
Kirino
Shokiri
Kirashiyo
Firmly
Red
surely
Kobotuya
The flow also came
That's it
Kut
Hii
butterfly
Trafalda
Nun
Choyo
Firmly
Red Ant
So
Sasa is
What is it?
Woah!
Hey
Oh
Uuuuu
Just bring my smile back a little closer
First delusion
Dark dark girl
Ba be rinen
Silence
Get your mind back
Recruitment is against
Night night night night night Shalal ...
I chose the outfit and it was a hit.
I want to meet you, that's it
Just a little
The best thing about bad behavior
Chochocho Maca's family car
So it's the last game
Winning the championship
a little bit
It's on the bottom right
Thanks to your parts
First, let's tell Dad about this victory.
Magician's Palace
Thanks to you
In the school scene
Can you tell me about your friendship?
thank you
Please change your mind and wait for me
Let's go home together
Like water you don't ask for
Time passed
You
With Dad
Since I started calling
To me
Those familiar words
think
7 years
Checking your calculations
You are
beautifully
It was believed
Make my Elio come true
Friends
think
Elinae's
Ayamachi
You are
I was eating
Danny's replacement
You are
He supported me.
Ahead of me
Your back
there were
7 years
Where
walked
However
Why am I
To you
I don't feel any friendship
Thanks to
How do you like it
Just the wind
If it continues this long
teeth
I'm getting old
Not yet
ah
oh yeah
That's quite something
Skilled
Dioplant
they
It seems that he won
Dio is already one of Joestarke's
Joe was Dibbala Singh Singh
It was a brilliant stop in the field of high school studies.
Dio-kun is the number one in law.
Graduation
I respect you
Danda-sama
I just got home
Dio is back
And Jojo too
Are you okay, Dad?
My sanity won't stop
Today the doctor recommended I be admitted to hospital.
I'm against it.
Hospitals these days are all about making money
Apparently it's a problem in Longbourn too.
It's definitely safer at home
There was a time
The swelling in my hands and the pain in my chest will subside.
Congratulations to both of you on your wins
Do you already know?
Archer Cave there told me.
I want to hear it.
Cave
we
I just want to see your happy face
I could have just stoned it.
I'm here
Really big nose
wonderful
There are already few
Especially Dio
You did really well
After the measures
Be what you want to be
To me, born of poor origins
Give it a chance
thank you
So I'm going to use this cable.
Thank you for always coming.
thank you
The tip of the cut is exposed.
It's the sound that has made lies a part of the world.
No, this is Liverpool.
anywhere
Like that guy
There are people who don't have the full amount.
So
do
staff
It's a living mechanism that responds only to
Who and for what purpose?
If we solve this mystery
Maybe I can make something happen on my way home from here
If you do that
Also for the shape
There's something destined
I am
Dario Pland
I'm always sorry
Rio-san
About giving medicine
Speed
thank you
I
I don't want to take a picture
I am now
Located in Yamai
perhaps
You will die
My heart hurts
Hands waving
The stone won't stop
My voice
A voice calling you
My mother died.
Two of my fathers
yes
Those shoes and
What
Pawn
It has changed
yes
Until that day
He died.
Zexal
I was separated from my wife by the moon.
Yes.
How to fight him
Right now
Lowering scum
Battle and
Aha
Hardness
Threw it
Assembled
Because I don't need it anymore
The match is
Without love
All those who were killed
Stolen
Shall I enter?
Name
It's different
On the body
Flowing
This hell
Zexal
white
This hunt
All
In these hands
Win
Human
To the End
Be prepared
Covering the wall
Enough
brando
Father
With the past
Sleep
all
Perfect
world
Get in and out
Come out
What happened to that medicine now?
What's wrong?
Are you okay
Name
Your
It's a letter from your father.
Death
Magi
Your father's
Symptoms
It's written in detail
Wow
Let me see it.
My
My father and symptoms
Same
You
To Dad
was carrying
What
Start talking
Answer me
you
Go
What
I want to say
This medicine
Let me investigate
Excellent
This medicine
When I looked into it
What to say
Our
Friendship
Doubt
As a belief
Your
地獄
My
Concerns
To my father
If you can get close
I
Never again
I won't talk about this
To that guy
close
From the very beginning
somewhere
Until the end
Infection
this
It's just Ceylon
yes
I hated my father
Above all, I was suspicious
It got cut
Joe John
Did Jojo do Jojo?
no
It's okay
No no no no no no no no no
No, no, no, no, no
I can't draw anymore
A perfect world
Get it
no
How about it?
What's going on? Yes, Master
Speaking out loud like that
Well, I'll be doing my second and third thesis. In the meantime, I've decided to give them a perfect tour. I will not be receiving any medicine or medical treatment except from them.
But please let him do what he wants. I don't know why, but I believe in my son. Thank you.
Seven years ago, this guy reacted to me, what happened?
8 years
Use this,
It was disguised as a research accident.
Gradually
Your research will kill you
field
Rainy time, hide Libby and jump out
Looking up at Koshio with the results already in mind
Master is the coldness of the world today Listenomuuran Build
I've arrived at this place in Soro
May 2nd: Where the Plague Comes
The country in front of me is on the other side of the world, there are reasons why I can't move forward
Lose your right hand to the past and look at the stars
It's finally here, Mr. Aird, Barabolet
It will continue for a while, but who is running away?
Who's coming? I'm the one who's good now.
Hoga Street - I'll do everything
Hoga Street All the main undertakings
I don't know if it arrived, but I'm sure there was a producer.
Treplatzitzcuiscocoscue
Hogar is the problem.
Just tell me the simple truth
I'm going to rip this Kilean Ajibainar off the spot.
If you resist, your life will be ruined.
Hoga Street, now I know we're just a little old
Bowery, life is Ongar
If you keep moving like this, you won't be able to escape to the cracks
Hikatonare Tsukkoikasa Hoga Street
Let's lose it in the game too
Hoga Street Now I know our image chronology
There is in the family
You lose a finger, that's average.
Hoga Street Scatsl is in love
I came to look for Dr. Equol.
Don't miss out, ruin the rich boy
But I'm an online nerd.
I made a mistake, but I'll put an end to it
Gantdown Slis Hwaga Street
Stop it
If you lay a hand on that parent and child, you'll have to wait a little longer.
Why didn't you kick it as you pleased?
I came here for the land
That's why Kelsim thought you must have a father or siblings.
I don't want to do anything that would make your father sad.
Bring your name closer
Jora-san, Joestar-san, in the case of Dokkuek, the name is Wanchi
If you're not careful, you'll get caught out. Be careful.
I'll guide you through the process of speeding you down
Why did I like you?
Gantdown Slis Hwaga Street
It's a hidden flame
Quickly take out the
See which run
This courage is what I'm talking about
With my pure heart, I will light up your darkness
February is over and it's a complete disaster
This plum blossom, this encounter,
Up
leisure
Please get it today
JoJo...
Huh...
…
Jojo disappears into Rondo...
…Are you a passenger?
…
Did you hear about the medicine?
Which one?
…
Just now?
Can't resist a drink?
Is it because of the earthquake?
My voice
A voice calling you
It's being born
You're the only one I care about
Become the richest
You and I are different
I didn't show it.
Oh no!
This is what I'm hearing
Kitsutsu's face is blue
When you first
I gave Bamma a good sleep.
I'm sure
This face
Back of face
Wow
It's not even possible that it will be born
Inside
Earthquake Floyd
Delicious
It's your fault
Wow
Make it plump
Pukula
Should I do it or paint it?
This white machine
Also, the company
Let me come over
It's a journey of success
Hehehehe
Well then
Your research is dissolved
I'll do it
Do it
Ah
, not easy
What
What is this, what did you do?
Benge Gong
Dead
If this much koshin is stabbed in the head, it's only natural that he'll be punished.
It's an ancient Guomon tool.
Not dead
Mamachi
What is this guy?
Sue
m
Change
Undevide apply
Dragon
then
in
Also
already
ambitions
I'm excited about you
graders
Are you flying?
andin Glish
ootlands
stay
maybe add orca Bureau
If there was nothing like that
me
I was saved
In sunlight
Did it turn to ashes?
This is
The Power of Isukamen
So, Deo
Apparently he hasn't returned yet
Support us right away!
Use your hair
thank you
Hey
That way of asking
Bring Wyche.
Chocho
It's great
This is my responsibility
picture?
I
If we put that guy in the Lutow family,
Deo's father
Dario Pland
That is to say
For you
I'll tell you
You
This is from my time as an Akanbo.
surely
This is my finger talk
But
No notification was submitted.
Finger speech
A man who fell in and out
Corresponding
The sign language is
Jostar Kyoga
With my wife
Now when I was given medicine
Something special made in pairs
Akira was the one who was the Eastern Conflict
picture?
This is yours.
This is a finger spelling I made with my wife.
Today is
My wife
Did you find it?
He had tears in his eyes.
I
If only I had caught Hajiri
Would you like to wish me a happy birthday?
Recorded items
What came off
The lineage of 10-year-old Rutou
It's a cultural fact
Understood
curler
Hey
Woody
Planned
Stop
Well then
Dario Pland is
Even with life and onjin
Nothing
Just
It's Nust
Just a lie
That
I know
Dio
I was being careful.
Why
I
Today's
At that time
On the current road
Tears
you
he
Didn't I say this?
This sign language is
He gave it to me.
There was a picture
Ugh
Yes.
this is
What I gave him
He is innocent
Yao's wife
It's hard
Mr. Pland
yes
This is yours
This sign language
hand
To my family
Please buy me something
Just a lie
Why that?
Deserveo
If I
In a strange way
suffering
If we had met
The same thing
Did you?
picture
For the ones I love
The stars in the sky
Light Yes
Eventually
The core speaks
This friend
Shibi
Darkness
I'll clear it up
Prayer place
thank you
you
You're too kind
This evil and
It's warming in my heart
Maybe so
But
Think the opposite.
Something called destiny
from
People
Tell me
Forget
That courage
That loneliness
Let's hug
Orimo
It's all connected
To everything
Garu
I
Believe in people
With a secret
For your viewing pleasure
Good
it is
someday
Kakaya
Gudarou
There is another
On the tray
I
Shichizuki
Aki's Ambulance
a
bothersome
Noroi
nine
I
Waiting for Dio
still
Can be stopped
You
I heard Nauwa-san
Frosia's man
Already the wall
He said he beat it up and destroyed it.
And the man
When exposed to the morning sun
Can't enter
I heard
It's the same as 30 years ago
Just like back then
Park of Memories
nailed down
Kusabi
Systemic training
That morning sun
Like this
It was red
Full of passion
Longing for the road world
My respected father
Hit the rolling sea
My beloved father
Voice of Things
At my exact moment
Day 1
From this hand
Take it all away
Including force
To get it back
Tomorrow for sure
Even if you open it, I'm thinking
There's a saying that this is who he is.
One day
If you find it
It will become irreversible
This hand...
Therefore
I was back from London, and I got the materials.
It's a shame, really.
You may not understand, but this is the truth
I understand, girl
You are that kind of guy.
I have a selfish request
It's the last one
Can you give me some time?
Time to train with the police
I
I'm eating my life
Born into a poor family
I got a palm.
I wore stupid color contact lenses
When words
Everyone is asking what they want to hear
I was allowed to introduce myself
I am
JoJo, I understand!
Anyone
I'm pretending to want to hear it
I was allowed to introduce myself
I am
I'm Speedwagon of Osekkaiyaki
I've been driving since it got stuck.
I've seen a lot of different people
So you can tell by the smell
This guy is Bakise
Really! The boy is already gone.
Dad! I heard the whole story!
I'll rest in my new room
or
I don't want to see you get caught
That man won't give up
I was born with that fate
Sores!
Girl, girl, I got it!
You'll be released, but at least
I want you to take over
We've been together for seven years.
Be careful!
Understood
I'll take the lead
For humans
There are limits
I am
I understand now
The more you recreate it,
The limits of life
What are you talking about?
I'm so frustrated
In this hand
There is nothing
The empty logo
With a glance next to me
I can't see beyond
No matter how much I write
Follow these eyes
Do you understand?
That smiling sky
I want you to know me
This hand is out of reach
I wrote that
On that beautiful day
This dumping ground will never disappear
So now is the time
Break this cage
The stars
Light
One
I am
Mom
Life
It opens
Right
Yes
please
Hahahaha
Yes
Initial battle plan
I'll take your mother's finger
Firmly
I will do it without betraying the user.
I've been hard on you
Maybe when I got home I felt it was fair.
Shoot
It doesn't seem bad
Gradually
The last one
In my son's arms
father
Do it.
After all, at that time
It was a mistake
I did everything when I died
Survey
Whether it's a hearing or not
I was always told
Proudly
everytime
I said I'd save you
I believe
Even though I was told
I'm powerless to have been unable to protect you
What do you believe?
Open the door
What is pride?
What's the purpose
Flowing through this body
Survey results
Always in judgement
continued to exist
Proudly
Yourself
Rishiki
The voice of darkness
Open and secure
Look up at the stars
Put everything into it
This engraved stone
Dance your heart out
Dance and shine
Send it to the stars that will become the future
Flowing through this body
Survey results
Everything is connected
It all makes sense
I'm sad about this fate
A single drop of courage
It's Keiban and Daiyan.
what up?
That's the corpse
Dion's body is missing.
It became
Satsuma
Get away from the window
Massage
Keiban
What is this guy, he's come back to life
Even though I was interrupted by forgetting
Be careful
I have some bookies.
Tomare
Utero
Don't be silly
It's early
I don't know above
It was what was happening now
Haa ...
Are you waking up?
Suddenly puffed up...
Hiriamado is hard to laugh at
You're J…
I've got such amazing power
From someday
Your father's power
A quick fix to the running.
He escaped, so that's why he got killed.
That running thing appears.
What do you think?
I can only get a bad taste from Misonoru
If it stops
If you peel off the head completely
Stop it!
Menoeka!
Already
It's stronger
Crab Cui Crab Cui
a!
Wow, that's fun
I'll enjoy this wonderful power for a little while longer.
I don't know how far I can go yet
Both specialists
Don't give in to useless longings
Did you say that?
If you let it bloom,
Humans have their limits
Well, don't hide in the shadows, come out
Kisamalabop
Let it be my life
I'm not even screaming that I can fly you
It's organic
I can't beat this day
Speed ​​Low
Run away from Toni Yasuki
Confusing
Don't run upstairs
ah
Run in the dark
It's going up
Well then
I'm here
Do you understand?
Ladies, ladies, you first
The more you run, the more light you scatter
Today is your strength
Finish eating
It's useless, it's useless
If you suck that life out
This flickering
Not from afar
Let's give one
Give me your strength
From now on, always
From your back
On my back,
There was someone in front
My player is Kimetomo
Final exam
He also decided on his own
Women
Women's Palm
You are burning
I'm dead
I lost it immediately
Other than this color
That too
Burning
Heat it up
That is
I'll close you
I'm sure Uehara-san is thinking about this.
More firepower
That Mamoru's recovery power
After placing it
more
More firepower
Throw away
The force of instinct
If you do
I will definitely lose it
Shit
Jasasasa
It's your fault, I almost fell into the basement
Where do you approach? I've grown fond of you
As I thought, this crying that won't let go was there
You're the type who stands up for yourself
My chest is insecure
I'll do things I hate
The one I saw was one I hated
Let's go live a life that will make you feel like a child
There was a lot of excitement.
If you do it again, you'll die
Janshah
Refreshing
Can you hear me?
I can hear you
I mentioned the Astika people before.
That was a 13th century mistake, not a 16th century one.
We must tell the story accurately
It was a great loss for someone in that position.
As someone said, I don't want to get old.
By the way, did you have a proper break?
it was good
I am the storyteller
Many different people have become drinkers.
And I continued to do
I want all the acrylic stunts
Refreshing
I did a complica
The story so far seems like a fairy tale
is definitely a reality
And it gets weirder from here
Yeah, strangely.
At that time, the mansion was almost completely engulfed and collapsed.
But Chosa was still there
I was attacked by Dio
But I lost everything
Then see
there were
Did you see it over there? If you have this screen
I can hear the voice of your face, the voice that reads you
I was rushed to the hospital and came to see Chosa, who was unconscious.
This is me, but...
Give me the hope to live
Something, this room is for visitors.
That's why I came
I have enough vocabulary
Please come on the 5th.
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Can you hear my voice?
listened to each other
Once again, when I see a vivid person
Your voice
I
Unfortunately, I continued to sleep.
All the mansions
Please stay calm now
We've passed the statistics, but times are still tough.
I'm glad you're alive
You've been nursing me
You are Yamasaka
But they look similar
Who do you think looks like me? Erina Pendleton
It's been a while
Female Joestar
Why
This is my father's hospital
India moved too far seven years ago.
I recently planned
It's really been a while
I was weak
It wasn't my first time with you
It was me who was young
I couldn't face you
That voice remains unchanged
This voice remains unchanged
Vivid reverb
The sky gets higher
Erina JoJo
The joy of being there
The wind left behind by the clouds rises a little
Elina
sorry
My mind is shaking and I lose consciousness
With me and my arms
I'll always support you
Eye to eye
If you touch it, it's there
Plainness is courage
Moving on to tomorrow
Hand in hand
Touch and there
When our eyes meet
Always Now
Touching Hearts
overlap
attract
fit
That day
Continue with the two of us
destiny
yes
The encounter of people
Maybe it's decided by fate
Kitty Dwagon
Cool!
lover
See you again soon
It's a camera
Heaven and earth are the same woman
A girl
Early afternoon
Its Appearance
The agreement is mutual
No movement or state of affairs, the truth cannot be grasped
Don't walk there at night like you do.
It's going to happen. He's going to appear.
London is also popular
It's getting chaotic, I don't know anything about it
Black people don't eat
If I could have it, I would have the darkness of the present.
Yes, but leave!
Chasing the ripples
I wanted to convey
This mod official
I won't go home early
I can see the celebration star
But there might be a Jap who will be the first to appear.
Is that a lie?
It's scary
Now you are like that
Even though we're talking
Play until the end of the night
Relax
Who is it?
you
I liked it
Because I was seen
I don't feel any pain
There's no more of that
Reborn now
Let's start my life
I have to heal my ache
I need life
So I feel less fulfilled
Don't you want power?
The Stone Mask...
I'll give it to you
Man is bound by all treasures
I fear great evil
But very rarely
Without all treasure
There is an evil elite
Me
You are
How about it?
Will this Diot come with me?
To you
What are you trying to say about me?
I understand.
So you
What's happening?
I can dance to your heart's content
Such
Covered in the distance
Lose too much
That's good enough now.
Who is it?
It seems like it will change
There's already one
Yes.
Well then
You don't have to worry anymore
More spinning than ever before in my hands
This is
Such as
do not have
It's crowded
Because of this
You
Come stretch
Jack
Zalipa
This hand
Anyway
Atanosa
Do you see the time?
Together
That's not right
There
To this time
This is a bit disappointing
nine
My
Restoration
That's it
Your
It's a hobby
Kekari
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
Messy tears
became
Like this
Ban Duan
That Ishika Village
他の棚同城細相信台
yes
It's okay
Are you okay
let's go
Huh?
what happened?
Who is it?
I've been here for a while now
Jora-san Choustar-kun
Huh? And
Miss Elida Pendleton
I'm surprised I survived
That Iskamen's power
Isukamen!
Wait!
Jola-san
Oshipa
Keep it open
By air
Wherever you go, you'll be disappointed.
Becoming a mites
That's lame!
The air seems to be tight
No appearance
I am Separi Danshak
All I have is courage
The Power of Isukamen
I'm your friend
Your breathing
To him
I suffered pain
I'm your perspective
Jora-san Jowstar
What is it?
What's that pain?
Why is my name
Appearance
Give me one
I'll show you the answer
Follow me
Just now I
Eyes change
Whether it shakes or not
I love you
What will happen next?
This breathing
The place to wake up
Now is the time to show it and run
Smart
Petuna Cokyurei
Country Petunassau
The concussion
Hackopping
Tyaeaars
Energy is generated
The name is
Hamon Energy
Horororororororororororororororororororororororororororo
Hamon's attack
Thank you
This miracle
Dropped
This is
The Power of Hamon
Kokum brings
The power of liquid
Smart
Cocuille
Everyone can create a little bit of energy in the flow of life.
Carrying heroes and adjusting responses
The bond force converts that small amount of energy into
Collected from the whole body
This is made possible by a certain breathing routine.
Breathing is the power of now
Yes, the power of breathing
Yes, I know
Thinking about it
I frown at this breathing technique
So I'm going to say it to you
Dios
Kamen is owned by someone who hasn't changed.
The amount of treasure we have now is
I now have enough of the world
I followed Kamen
Destroying and eating
Dio is alive
Just catch cute
If you don't destroy it
In the hands of destruction
Well, is there any more?
Yours
Your world
Fate is weak and sluggish
I finally found it
Tattered and worn
Do you accept it?
Eyes working hard
Everything was discussed
Sma
destiny
fight
That's my destiny
You mean me?
The will of the person
Extracting the power of the path from "no"
Leave the humans to rest
it is
You must take blood energy from others.
On the other hand, Hamon's power
Mizukaru's blood flows
Extracting energy
I was thinking
Same energy
Yeah
It's Smari
To remove this jamon
What do you think I should do?
I'm starting to understand
Jamon
If you hit another Hamon
They'll explode
And the tears of energy
It has the same shape as the sunlight
The power to defeat Dio
yes
There's no time
Develop an attitude that turns courage into strength
woman
Dio
Energy
I won't get involved in anything that gets you involved
Right now I just want you to stay
I'll definitely come back to this place
This is
Is it a female jamon?
Yeah
Haa
Clouds flow
The wind carries my thoughts
Measurement
go around
I nodded.
To your resolve
In sadness
Shining stars
I won't lead you to the fate you desire
I got stuck in the mud
I was here
Left behind
Living the dream
Wait by the window
Loneliness is
For whom?
Even if it doesn't reach
Even if it doesn't shine now
I want to scream
I
Even if it doesn't shine now
I want to scream
I
Because
you
There is light
anytime
Don't let your destiny lead you
I
Spending my days
Let's live
Looking up at the stars
While
This place
Someday you
He'll tell you
Proudly
Let's continue to exist
Your everything
Acceptance
Destiny and Love
yes
So that you can call
The stars
Daylight
Your
Don't let your destiny lead you
The stars
Daylight
Where
Even if
I
Me
Live on
Alive
Go
Kiev
Otsuku
Going
Go
Wear
Wihaha
Weано
Wear
What is that disease?
Maza KAL
Dion too
Spain
Wearcon
You
Stone Masked Secrets Too Dead!
That's it!
Sioster!
Aa ...
Oooooohhhh!
I was looking for you too!
Because! Because!
Dio was there!
I'm willing to rip off your value!
Licky?
Lick lick!
Lick lick lick!
Vero up and down?
picture?
Be careful of the skilled
This guy has a lot of power
What's with this weirdo Pojnock?
I'll come when I get there!
Gutega what's wrong...
We we we we we we we we we we we
Nadada și Ichinyo Tiny many
Humans are like this Jikro'a
Daizara doesn't have a phone
Gon!
My body...
Why this?
Ah! It's hot! Which one is it?
Oh! Here we go again!
見事だ、少少
I'm surprised I was able to see Hamogo on such a short trip.
yeah…
what up?
JoJo...
I've lost a lot
So I wanted power
But that's...
Not the same as Dio
To insult someone
It's fundamentally different from the power he was stealing.
Another is the same power
Things like this will go down like a ride
The one who came created the Vikings
A harsh coming will wake you up
Because I know the pain
The Vikings who heard it
Miyatsuka is different.
You
I know the pain
pain
The pain of dying
The pain of absorbing the rest
The sky of those I want to protect
Pain is life
Red
I'll listen to the pain
Believe me
I was always told
My father's back
everytime
I still don't know what to believe
Heart-warming
Dosuta no Chi
Hot
The day screen
Emits light
Perspective
Repeatedly, the liquid
Holding this pain
The screen is not a word
I happened by chance
Tonight in my memory
nailed down
rust
I will win
My Father and the Seven Rabbits
I handed it over
Quiet Leg Night
That screen
Emits light
50 First Time
My friends are
He had been murdered.
The masked man comes
Protect the darkness
Love you
At that time, the morning sun
What illuminated
It was my insect
In the red morning light
Illuminated floor mat
disappeared
At that moment it stopped
Embracing the pain of love
Catch up
Don't look back
Approaching excellence
I won't talk
Tomorrow is the day
With pain
The courage to own the pain
and
Back to school
Right?
The thought
I haven't forgotten
yes
I believe in the power of this conger eel
let's go
Let it clear up
I
depressed
Surprise fall
It's a horse
good
Ah, okay.
Wow, across the street
I'm a novice
Jousta-san is on änge
Don't invite me to 'Mytuke'
yeyyo yo yo harai ni imuka ouzhe
I occasionally watched it.
Reprate Ilashala Association
Ace Case Bead Wargo
You're a weak little Jousta
Of course I'll be your guide
There is no guide
Juul Lauction
Shaodar
Ron seto kara unconfirmed
Police wrote on the day of the month
Opposition Party Email to City
When you receive it, you can see
Sacrificial Mast Usue
This Wind Knight Roto
Teipenorosaimarniagit
Wind Knight Roar
Inrenga Show Tideion Ast
Dayon Arbunchiri
Code Oak Ostana Chili
Slow Lot Souji, who likes to take breaks
Dioteme
thank you
This information is from me
It seems he fled to Duan Chen ahead.
Dio will realize his empire here.
While there is Dio
If you can find him
I can see the tunnel
This is the entrance to the city.
The projection area is as planned.
Hey! Win the race!
Why stop place
Be careful
Dio doesn't have a strong hand here.
Look!
No no no rail
Summoner's magic is a demon bon
I fight
Reverse bone door
Jasuke Fighter Shikoda
Various drinks
This recruitment is for us humans
Children on the right path
Can you call that a yuke?
Goddess
Something I want to say and talk about
Republicans who saw the breath
Who is it?
Eye Base
Hamoho Country is an organic acid
Human oxidation is organic oxidation
The wonder of humans is the wonder of organics
How strong is
These zombies don't know anything about organic matter.
Drink and drink
Dolly
Hot Hot
Yackoma
Covering the other side
Cover
why?
Small tree trainer
Kutcha
Hide in the tunnel
Win's Light Lot
This is Kisstats' training ground.
There are various tricks
And there's a big deal at that time.
He is thriving
Who should be the one to end it?
Well, there's definitely a girl up there
This too
azz
so
surely
vague
I wonder
Be aware
Kun
Retreat
Sleeping Kissachi
Huh, uhh, realized?
Answer: Law, I want to make you my own Law
Now let's reveal the truth behind the parliamentary
Fuji Ha Well He vomiste
That is the world, this unshakable world
The world of the accompaniment The world of the accompaniment
Long clouds hang over this country. Now is the time to speak up.
A cry from the sky continues
Those legs are going to end and shake
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Raise this voice
Searching for
Searching for the other side
Match the search
I remember shouting from the sky
It's scary
Shout from the sky, "Losing!"
It's scary from the sky
This has taken my world away
Please come and see us soon
Even my mouth is still open
Hair Child and Varialli
Make history solid
Everything will be solid and firm soon.
I feel empty so I have to be strong
Scream from the heart
It's scary
Search
All seems solid
Two things that hold everything back
Now, with the current
I can't get it even though it's obvious
This world once again, the world of reason
It's shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking
But it's amazing Didhy
Igu Shichiraku Intercom
A strange child will jump out
Body de jai
Data
The water comes out here
Because, oh, it's true!
Popping out
The sun has set
Kisamara's life too
When you're bossing
I've been preparing for that moment
So it's going to be a Dosukuro Eki
You have to forgive me as a human being
上書
It's a fighting mindset
I'm bored
At first
Eclact is delicious
By this bisabigi
Bu-go attack
It's Lesland.
Sakasei
Let's ride a bike
went
It's just a good thing
From the other day, there was no enemy
Defeat that guy
I didn't come back later,
You are here
Hitakaze is a Viking
I'll book it and give it a go
That's dangerous
Yokkapinu
Hitatakawara Viking
Severe living activity is born
I wonder if this bath will have a buffet.
Where is my west today?
Warm thoughts
Have courage and breathe
Won't open
Human participation is
Courageous Participation
Humans are amazing too
The awesomeness of courage
All
Connect
resonate
Disturbing your breathing
Hmm
There's no cold
My Hallow
is
Vegetable warping
Shoes
Yana
Rug bespoke
Tears
It was a dream where I told my boss
It's gone
Cragbeshable
Society too
soon
Bullbearly
Instagram
Let's pull
Wrapped in cherry blossoms Wrapped in cherry blossoms
The color of the house
Don't ask for more yet
DRA I want to see
Grz
Gather at Gabo Japma Ra
Sun Feather From yourstag
This is the power that will defeat you!
Dio Brando!
a?
I don't know you personally
But
I woke up your brain
Dare to face a stone wall
It's so far away
Don't ride it
bard!
- If I can heal this wound
It was attached to you
Umm... I feel the injustice at the beginning.
At Kisamara's command, I will disinfect this wound in the air.
How much life did you suck out of that wound?
Do you remember the bread you've ever eaten?
I'll let you sleep.
The width of the sun!
bread!
品積品積!
This shows that the length of the arms and the energy of the arms are related to the product.
I can control my body freely.
If you let the results live later, you won't convey that power!
Breathe, breathe!
Help!
Waste waste waste waste!
breathe?
Conger eel?
Hehe, if that's the case, it would be fitting for you to play a fanfare for me.
Hahaha
There's no stock strategy that suits you, friend.
That's right.
Do you remember?
One day, Icha, your father told a desperate story, what, in the 16th century.
Elizabeth's assassination attempt
On the beard that was executed in the death knell
Mary Stuart
It was used there
Two people
It's about an angry Kishi.
Dad's
Now
We listened to it together
Jojon, Dion
Today, this tradition is passed down in England.
Let's talk about two Kishi
Living in the spirit of Shingeru
Kishi's
The rest of the story
Once upon a time, 300 years ago
Let's cheer on the two of us
Jojohn, Elizabethan
Beautiful Mary Stuart
Mary gave me that turgid
The elegance of two legends
Hahahahahaha
From now on
Ophiry like you
The sky
Deliberate Heart
Hit the target
Two without two
I conveyed that power
I think about it
The Dearie Situation
Find peace
Use clothing
Flowing Time
Their system and methods
By Elizabeth
A friend's container is placed on it
I'll be caught
I don't like the elegance of the two of them.
To save Mary
To stop the grace of the two
Elizabeth calls out
You guys should mess with us
Save Shugun's life.
To Elizabeth
There is no denying it
Our difficult story
Because of this order
It's so easy to get caught up in it
I'll scoop up the maid
This system is unacceptable
I bowed my head
It's possible that it's lying around here like trash.
I'll keep it cool
Because there is a semi-translated version
Wow
To Elizabeth who went behind the scenes
If I were to ride on the back of this
To Elizabeth
With anger erupting
That's why it resonates
Melt this neck
By Plaford's Hands
That hair gets tangled
I'll wait
This hair of my heart came alive
There isn't enough kishiro
A goosebump-inducing proposition
What a heart of sentient beings!
But they should have done better.
I couldn't do anything in the first match.
It can also be said that there is no waste.
You may be right.
But nothing is meaningless
The same goes for when you came to this house.
It's all connected
I thought they kept looking at the stars
I want to believe
People are like destiny
Reach out your hand to me, where I live
Are you seeing stars?
Or either one
Gradually
Say it's your fault
The two of them
The devil also created Bedbukhushki
I can fight history and die
Got it?
This is what you look like
To clear one's name
What an embarrassing sight
Don't you think so?
Everyone looks happy
A continuation of that day
Tarkus Bellaford
The secret name Fansuar
I'm tired
It's strange but delicious
That's it
Slow Idiom Kiss Bellaford
and Tarkus
I think that's a bit
It's too late, I can't imagine
But I also have something to carry
I'm the slowest person in the world
How many were filled?
The man's anger
I kissed and received it
My master
In this Braford
I would like to draw every day of this man's life.
Okay, that's good.
Make a good list and get it
If it hurts, run away
Survey
I won't let you get away with it
In the park of memories
nailed down
Wedge
Anyway
That morning sun
Like this
It was red
Osa
You live
Now
I can't do anything
I am, I am
Nothing to try
I'm not good
Wait a minute
Don't mess with me
Even at a time like this
Even if you give up
Come
Carefully
Continue
Tomorrow for sure
Make Irumide
I kept chasing
Remember
Is the gap your answer?
Is that your anger?
What will happen?
Kisana
I was just angry.
and
Once processed
That's what happened
So this is what it means to be human?
Get on the Tokoro Bull Bus
What's scary is
It's not pain
already
What you should know
regain
Morning tomorrow
Tomorrow
Now
There
picture
Tokewa
Even if I return
When
I guess he did it
Kiki's
Looking back at the station
Is it urgent?
Don't wait for tomorrow
I start walking
Should believe
It should be said that
Tomorrow Now
girl
The Beat of Decision with You
Why is it moving?
When I looked into it
That
Hiding
Pikima
pain
No or
You just said it hurts
You are feeling pain now
pain
That's why I stopped being that Sarakai
So you stopped the prefecture
You are a proud wrecker
Human
What I saw
Sennorakashi
This is a human being
Because there are similarities
I can feel the joy of being here now
I can be here now
I'll bother you
I feel now
Bravo
I will dedicate to you the words engraved on my prefecture.
Something like this
and
Let's go
To save souls
That I have to kill
Come
Affection
No way
To think he would defeat Kurokiko
also
You are this Dio
Haybay Day
The attack of the jamon that plant
I tempted you
What changes is not the outcome but the vile Hamon
It's dangerous, Tama
At the beginning of the season
Brami's brother
Loss of motivation and enthusiasm
驚
Lots of Ou
From now on
I tried my best.
I'll do it, I'll do it!
JoJo
Follow me for my last jamon
My companion
JoJo!
Wow
always
Search Chokil
Add to the sound of the sir
Please stop it
Carlton!
Oklaine!
Windows 4
Hey, Jebel, Jebel, if you're gone, I'll be sad, but one day I'll destroy my eyes, but hey, I'm happy with my life. Finally, I've entrusted it to you.
Hey, you're my hope.
Once again, the sun's rays are spilling out of my arms.
You taught me the meaning of my life, my destiny, and the greatness of being human - courage.
The light that was received would seep in. In my heart, I felt as if I was both dead and breathing at the same time.
From now on, I'm coming into you. Thank you very much.
Everything is connected, everything has a body.
This pain, this pain that I believed,
What your father gave you, what you gave you.
I speak of the light of application in my mind.
There is one thing that is so certain that it is in my heart right now.
Embrace it, because this moves,
Look at the stars.
What remains is the brilliance of humanity,
Light up the darkness and bring your return,
Come back,
happiness.
Can't you hear me?
I hear a voice calling to you,
I've already killed the past that I can't hear,
Call my name.
Unlike you.
It's my fault.
That changed until
Laugh to live,
Use and take everything,
Disobey justice,
To all of Wasa,
Use and take everything,
Disobey justice,
To all of Wasa,
You want me,
Laughing,
I want it,
it is,
no one,
Here it comes,
Well then,
Is this the world you've left behind?
what,
The world you lost long ago,
Is this a sad world hidden by dead people?
It's a wonderful world where I control everything
Lion
Even history
Is that why you have to steal from innocent people?
A distant sacrifice for the future I envision
You're just scared
Humans
That's why I gave up being human
To get it
Beyond human
All you need is results
I won
The only result is that you are in control.
It's all just a dream
But
How did you live?
Paying to Fate
What did you leave behind?
Rumbling, rumbling, rumbling
To me
Give me strength
dead
Your
It's my father
That's right
smile
Going out as a faithful servant
The current situation is
To tell the story behind
Ko how proprio
Isn't that the best move?
When I tell you the inside story like that,
I've been forced to ask you out
I'm good with tax
shake alone
hahhh
Finally, a name that stands out
What's left now
That life is mine too
務 manual you
But the light is certain
Holy and low
merged
for that
pain
No problem
I'll set my heart on fire to take everything
I've gained power, but this pain is gentle
This smile broke before, you're a sloppy person
I stopped thinking about this smile, and it made my body freeze.
Omelo, kill me
You threw me away and taught me the best, so I'll pour in the bargain sale in front of the meaning of selling you
Yes, I did it. I knocked my hand down. That's wrong.
It's a little rough, but it's a good hand
緊弱緊弱
Sasasa, no no
It's so tense, but it's actually deceiving you
JoJo
Now you too will come to me, and death will resonate with you
You ran away from humans
What's not making me spill right now?
This year just hit me
I have surpassed humanity
I can't keep up with you guys
I'm already curious, girl
If there is a picture of the day of death,
Stop that heart
Let's do it. Inlencer grows.
As long as there are humans
If you say that, you can just run away
Like right here
Let me sacrifice my life and reveal it to you
That was on my hand
Moderate street night
The place where I escaped
This very night
There are already people who have disappeared
Recently, on the street
Let me shed my life on this and reveal it to you.
Yagaragaragaragara
Yagaragaragara
I want to sleep
I'll make anything happen
Roughly
Megan
The meaning of our relationship has been stripped away
Yep.
Until I sip you
Osnagel's
My wife is tall
Huh?
That's why
My body is hot!
Pokentique!
Waking up!
This Tio
still
There's more!
Caution!
Then like this
I've unleashed my strength!
That's disgusting!
Yo
Simple!
Simple squid
Inezy!
AEG!
Bissenmart Force
London Cress Article
small incidents
Sowing Knights Lord
That little Maji
The Efrazy Case
Such a worrying incident
713 people
The person who disappeared
And then Kotzen disappeared
But the groans I heard coming from
No one yet
Not found
D.A.D.
D.S.M.R.F.D.
Wind Knights Lord Article
Complex Company Speaks
The day after the incident
Running under
Men burning down the district
and
It was repeated so much
The screen of the day
AEG!
Sempraridasekaamshakoland
Welcome
At night
Up and down
second-mover
Female Female
The insertion
Married
The other person is
Pendrcon species
More than a voice
Einar Pendrkon
Philisarnasilas
Harem is from Wing Day
Heading to America in the beginning of the month
Sirisana Sirus
Joster-san
Both of them
push up
I am
Always Hey Prussie
At this time
I can hide my hands anywhere
It's a ball
Harnem
Miya did sign language
Let's make it in season
America is great
Someday I will too
Try guessing students in America!
Shhhh!
And then the fateful moment comes
Tell this story until the world is a flash
That's the job of this meddlesome YATII Speedwagon introduction.
But it's not for me to say that now.
On planet Meguru, where Eien prays for today
My hands are always touching yours
How about it?
I'm happy you're here
It's the same for me, I introduced you to my father.
Now, let's go to the craftsman
Intruder
Oh no, the guest has returned.
Don't forget to lock it
[Retreat it to Eien with fire ash]
【伝ir】
I used him to collect it.
Wagapodi
Here you go,
JoJo
Therefore I will split this stone in pieces before you.
I now respect you for having made so many holes.
Because I realized that
If God controls destiny
There's no relationship more calculated than ours
I got this power because of you
Because you were there
I don't have it all
How far are you?
That's why this is destiny
I got the body of the only person in the world I respect
Living forever in the prefecture
JoJo
We are in this world
Because we are one
Please try, try, try, try
From light to darkness, this is where I die
End it all
Let's get it all started
The world of Pingo
No, John
I feel like I can't speak
There's no breathing
Only you
When the spirits scatter
If you do that
Elemental Creation
Only this child
If you search
How it works
Can you get the dial?
nevertheless
All people
I enjoyed it
fun
Need
Not given
That neck
Right next to the iron steps
Inaccuracy
I won't forgive
Long time
John
You
This child
My
Someone
all
Dose
Something inside me snapped, something decisive
Chomazo!
This is it!
Run away
Chocho
Until I burn with you
Until everything disappears
Flames run, everything is connected
Live for me
All live
Probably at the beginning
Now, I'm going to be in trouble.
Maybe this time
That's about it.
Sell ​​happily and live
But now something has snapped
Until you don't need it yet
Okay then
It's about you
Before I lose consciousness
I thought it would come
Speak
Talk to me
This guy
Dead
His noble life
Disappeared into the cruelty of him
The destiny and adventure
Dead
Let's talk forever
Of course,
Something in my eyes
Two in One
Feeling the friendship of a dog
That's right
Without you
Because you were there
something
Now I
want
Find
To your favorite destiny
Beautiful Mikade
In the stars
I drink
The two
That fate
It was terrible
Another breast
Quietly unknown
One saw the stars
Tour
Is it polar?
pick up the station
my frightenedzz
Speedwagon is so cool!
Yuishie, Yoishie!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuisi, Yuisi!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuishy, ​​Yuishy, ​​Yuishy!
Yuisi, Yuisi!
The best thing about this park was that the smiles of all the customers were the biggest smiles. I felt that very strongly at the park.
I was truly happy that such a miraculous park had been able to survive to the very end.
Thank you for watching.
Now, Mr. Kong, please.
Great staff, great cast.
Then they brought the outbreak to the theater.
I'm glad to meet everyone who has watched the video.
I easily overcame the progression.
The players were able to go home after today's academy.
I'm happy for people.
I let it happen.
thank you.
And I was struggling as a single person.
My son!
That's amazing!
I'm so happy!
It's great.
thank you.
Then, I received the greeting I just mentioned.
Thank you for watching.
thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Everyone, please check out Fauci's Prround Funding.
thank you.
please.
Everyone, you all were wonderful.
It was wonderful.
See you at the theater from there.
Thank you very much.
He doesn't even know!
He doesn't know either.
So Misha, please.
yes.
It was a huge hurdle.
I'm not sure if I can speak well,
This is Elina Tendul and her character Shimis Misha.
Thank you very much for coming to the audience today.
And thank you to everyone who watched the stream.
What should I say?
I was able to reach this great war retreat,
The strength of each and every cast member,
With the staff and
For supporting this work,
I think it's all thanks to you all.
Please do, everyone.
Please look at the stars, everyone.
So please have a great war.
yes.
It's your job to burn the speeder!
It was my first experience and it was really difficult for me.
But really.
It was really hard, but
Already, somehow,
To get support,
Thanks,
It was really hard, but
Already, somehow,
To get support,
Like supporting them,
Supporting each other,
Those words truly mean,
It just seemed to enter my body.
It's a really wonderful place,
Thanks to that,
I was able to cut it thickly.
So, I have nothing but the best to say,
With everyone here on stage,
As Kochi-san also said,
Not at all.
Although he's not here now,
The staff who helped me create it,
and,
This role,
For five months,
I really put it together,
I want to make it a treasure in my life.
Love women,
Thank you for taking an interest in Speedwagon again.
Including everyone who loves me,
Really,
thank you very much!
Shirae-san...
Good job, Dig putting is burning well.
I certainly understand.
Honchitsu,
To Sepulija,
RPM improved office
Wang's school committee came to the event.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you very much.
Really,
The first thought is,
There were a lot of different things that happened.
The two of them, Shotaro, and now, here
The one who finished the tree, and another Teperi,
Hiro-kun and I accomplished so much on our own.
Mom, this company is a one-lens camera for people.
With the determination to align
I came here with the aim of becoming a teacher of Wang's music.
Really, without anyone calling
Of course, I'm really grateful that I've come this far.
Medical support from staff
It is the result of your efforts.
Every single stage, really
I just want to omit it.
The applause of the Baraline and 5000 yen are us
Now the cast is
The truth is, it's your Hamon energy.
How much courage it gave us
I think that's what we really feel.
I was really close to Hantoshi and Okabetsu right now.
It really is like a family
It means that today will be a valley from tomorrow onwards.
Hey hey
Annie
A little Syriaria please
Just a little bit
I feel lonely though
I really love myself
This woman's world
And with these beloved members
In this theater
Being able to breathe the same air
That's right.
The one who touched everyone's hearts was
I have become a treasure too
I am proud to have been able to do this with you all.
Thank you so much everyone
thank you
It will end again
Blatzer
Please watch
I changed my boss's environment.
Another ironworker
Thank you for today
It's totally free
So many
As you have written earlier,
Right from here on
As in the title above
It was a strange adventure.
There are so many people like you.
Only the curtain of Hara
Born at the Imperial Theatre
The Imperial Theatre
The current theater is closing.
As a final review
By producing
Not Minami
Memories
Participated
My friends are cast members here.
It is staff
And the original author
The main cast members
And here are the books.
After five years of work
Apparently it was rewritten 17 times.
It was in this flow that I was born.
This work
Being accepted by everyone like this
Like this
Many musicals
We have some works from overseas.
Such works are
Zahiozic Zero is
On Broadway and in the West End
That's what we're here for
In books
While making large replicas
Let's fight
Japanese style
We provide information.
This work is
What you all saw
Exactly
From zero to one
Became Zahiozic
I think it's a work of art.
This work
Someday again
Inherited
It may be a big performance,
This Zahiozik
I was at Zero 1
The friends here
Really I
It's just for the time being.
Zayn
I feel like a son or daughter to you.
Only one person was different
Since they share the same father
One as a father
Mud and Stars
University
A work ticket
As a friend
from now on
At the Shibutoku Musical
I want to survive
Truly amazing
Two sons
Like this
I can have it
A little bit today
You might be watching from anywhere
Also serving
As a son
Nice to meet you
Truly amazing
Yesterday
As a father
I was able to participate
Hello everyone
If you have any worries
Finally
What is it?
Within myself
It's all connected
That it all has meaning
a little bit
If you think so
surely
Beyond that
There is light
There are stars
If you think so
I think it's that kind of work.
thank you
Well then
I will do my best
Where should I start?
Already
But anyway
I'm glad we met
Hotz
We
Entertainment and
I'm trying not to
Sometimes after all
There are times when it's difficult
There are times when it's scary
but
The Minister just said
As you said
Something
In the purely literal sense
Don't do it right away
In the truest sense
Do it now
That's what it means
I am this
I felt it at Campari.
of course
A lot of things happened
Something like that
Only in those words
I might not be able to tell you right now, but
And more
I
now
As a treasure
I was able to have
Above all
It
so
lots of
To humans
That you can enjoy it
After all, it's ours
It's the happiest thing
It
With this member
It can be closed on paper
I am happy
Women
Giant player fun
I welcomed
My father just now
As you said
We will continue to do so
Look forward
Surely soon
Each on their own path
Various expressions
I think I'll pursue it
Not yet
It will be useful
Dad too
Let's definitely meet again
and
Also this woman
I think it would be a good story if we could meet.
It's all connected
I dream of such a day
Today is really
To everyone
I want to express my gratitude
everyone
thank you
amazing
I'll say something good.
I think Bappy will decide.
thank you
Woman
I pushed the woman down.
This is Arisa Shotaro
everyone
Really
Those who noticed
I don't know, but
I
Because I'm this kind of person
Even if I stand in the middle
After all, everyone
Many people
For holding me and supporting me
already
Warm
Someone like my older brother
He was already a family man
People like
Because that's fine for you
You can go with that humanity
Just those words are enough
I really have come this far
But still
When I look around,
After all, this time everyone
After all
Cress
I've seen your face after all
Really everyone
too
After all, the curtain won't open
There were many things that caused me anxiety.
I think there is.
That voice also reached me
It arrived directly after all
However, I also received a lot of criticism from the people around me.
What's going on?
Ride and enjoy
There are various messages
I saw the power of seeing.
just
I
I really believe in everyone
I'm working hard here
Because I've been watching everyone
Watch it.
Feelings
I just want you to wear it
That's really the only feeling
Not
Together
There are so many different
Overcoming a big wall
already
Even if the conversation doesn't change
Invisible
It's a bond
That's already the case
Don don don don
That means we're connected
I've been feeling this trend for a long time now
After all
Makuha is open
Jonah Joshi's
What is the other Yuya-san?
Really
We've talked about a lot of things up until today
Yesterday's Yuya's war loss
Watching Hiro's wartime success
After all,
There was today
One more
I feel like I've really completed it.
I got into the mood.
I've seen some really amazing things
on second thoughts
I'm glad I worked hard
Really already
As of yesterday, I felt
So today, everyone
so
I can see that face in Chi-up
Really I
With a heartfelt joy
There are lots
As it was at the beginning
I
I think it's a historic evolution.
To the world
Really already
We all worked hard to create it
already
This guy
This guy gave it to me in the field.
Together
I want to keep up
already
try as hard as one can
Climb, climb, climb, climb up the mountain
today
Really
I think I was able to make everyone happy.
Thank you so much
Me too
Really
I spoke without thinking
Maybe
no
That's not true
Some people may think that
This is definitely
already
It's my feelings
Campari's feelings
I
today
It may be a mistake
I think I've made everyone happy already.
It's okay to think that
Me too
where
Everyone did their best.
everyone
thank you
I
To dry this
Also
I hope that I will be able to meet you all in person soon. I also hope that this work will continue to remain not only in Japan, but all over the world.
I want to teach with big dreams.
Thank you very much.
So, I hope to finish it again soon, and thank you for watching today.
Thank you for watching.
Everyone, everyone and a little bit of everyone.
Because there are a lot of things going on.
Thank you everyone!
Thank you for watching.
Artwork
Gabies
。
I love you